Chapter 568: Mo Yao’s Will

Fang Yuan carefully observed calamity beckoning Gu.

This Gu was a rank seven Immortal Gu and after going through the nurturing process in the giant vermillion bowl, it had already completely formed.

It was the size of a little finger, was completely grey and looked very delicate like a silkworm cocoon.

As Fang Yuan played with it and calamity beckoning Gu continued to absorb his aura, he could sense that the connection in the depths of his mind with calamity beckoning Gu was deepening further.

Ripples appeared in Fang Yuan's heart.

It would be a lie to say that he was not moved.

In his previous life, he had suffered untold difficulties and slaughtered many lives to refine a rank six Spring Autumn Cicada. And now with the advantage of his rebirth, he had yet to become a hundred years old but had already obtained calamity beckoning Gu which was a rank higher than Spring Autumn Cicada.

Although the use of calamity beckoning Gu was extremely peculiar, offering oneself as a sacrifice by attracting earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations, Fang Yuan believed firmly that the use of a Gu depended on the wits of the Gu Master.

Like Chainsaw Golden Centipede which would be used in a different manner in the future by a rank four mortal Gu Master 'Chainsaw Mad Demon'. So, why would Fang Yuan not be able to create new uses for calamity beckoning Gu?

"Not speaking of other things, just the existence of calamity beckoning Gu proves that the legendary luck path truly exists."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was extremely lucky his whole life and it was rumored that this was because he had created unique luck path Gu worms.

However, there had never been conclusive evidence regarding this rumor.

Now, Fang Yuan was holding calamity beckoning Gu, a luck path Gu; an Immortal Gu refined by refinement path grandmaster Mo Yao by interaction with the divert disaster Gu of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Divert disaster Gu and calamity beckoning Gu were luck path Gu worms.

The ink text in the bowl was a very strong piece of evidence.

Mo Yao even directly wrote in the ink text that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path Gu worms could steal other people's good luck and transfer it to himself, and could also transfer his bad luck over, bringing trouble to others.

As a complete path, luck path also had a methodical structure, including aspects of offense, defense, movement, healing and others. It was only that what it targeted was the incorporeal and formless luck which everyone possessed.

After Giant Sun Immortal Venerable innovated the luck path, he kept it hidden and made great profits without making any commotion.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stole luck wantonly and with his death, the luck thief had finally perished." Mo Yao poured her feelings in the text, this strange woman had quite a temperament, daring to criticize an Immortal Venerable like this.

She even speculated Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path inheritance was very likely to be in the treasure room of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!

"If I can obtain this inheritance, could I duplicate Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's success?" Fang Yuan's heart thumped in excitement.

He pondered for a while before placing calamity beckoning Gu in the giant vermilion bowl again.

Although calamity beckoning Gu had completely taken form, Fang Yuan could not refine it.

The connection between them had thickened to the extreme, but there was still a gap before he could truly become the master of calamity beckoning Gu.

Fang Yuan was still a mortal currently and did not have immortal essence to refine it.

This situation was different from when he refined fixed immortal travel Gu.

At three kings blessed land, he was able to refine fixed immortal travel Gu with the assistance of the land spirit, he was the leading refiner. Thus when fixed immortal travel Gu was born, it became his Gu. But he could not use it, and if not for the land spirit's help, Fang Yuan would not have been able to travel to Hu Immortal blessed land.

The whole process of refining calamity beckoning Gu, however, was done through the backflow of the heavenly power of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Fang Yuan was an assistant at best; this was already extremely great considering he did not have the help of a land spirit.

"I can only truly refine it when I become a Gu Immortal. Before that, I can only leave it here."

Without advancing to Gu Immortal, there would be no immortal aperture to store calamity beckoning Gu. If it was brought out openly, the Immortal Gu aura would spread which was sure to attract countless coveting people.

Fang Yuan was not worried about Hei Lou Lan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the others; he had many wolf groups now and his strength path cultivation was also sufficient.

What he was worried about was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's will in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Previously, the Immortal Gu was in its early form and had a weak aura, but now it had already taken shape, so if it was brought out, it might stir up Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's will and awaken it.

Fang Yuan was not willing to take that risk, more so when his main plan had yet to be completed; he needed to keep on hiding and waiting.

"Who would think that this nameless valley holds a rank seven Immortal Gu? But for now, I should first refine a part of this Water Pavilion before leaving." Fang Yuan pondered.

Water Pavilion was a famous Immortal Gu house. It looked like Fang Yuan was overestimating himself by trying to refine it as a mortal, but this attempt was greatly feasible.

Even the formidable Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had a crack, allowing Fang Yuan to study it in-depth. While Water Pavilion was now a ownerless object, it could naturally be easily exploited.

But to talk about this, we need to know about the inherent nature of Gu houses.

What is a Gu house?

Not mentioning Fang Yuan's past life, after the rebirth alone, he had encountered many Gu houses.

The most common among them included the Gu house three star cave. It would turn into a seed when it was collected. After planting the seed, it would grow into an enormous hollow tree with three floors.

There was lizard house Gu with the appearance of a lizard, sporting different colors. Its eyes were windows and its mouth was the door; it could move by its own will.

There was also the mushroom forest Gu house which was formed by planting a large number of mush room Gu. Many mushroom houses would form into a courtyard.

These were mortal Gu, there were also Immortal Gu houses like Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and Water Pavilion.

There were too many complicated Gu houses to talk about in their development till this day. But if one were to investigate their origin, the publicly recognized founders were the seven Lui Gui siblings.

These seven were demonic Gu Masters of the olden antiquity era, they were born as septuplets, and from birth to death, they moved together.

They were experts in defence and each of them was a rank five peak stage Gu Master. They also had a defensive killer move formed by combining their strength called 'turtle house'. Relying on this move, they were able to defend against three attacks from a Gu Immortal, establishing a tale called 'three moves pact' in history.

And this turtle house was the first Gu house in Gu Master history!

Thus, basically speaking, Gu houses were killer moves formed by the combination and solidification of ten or more various kinds of Gu worms.

Mushroom forest Gu house was a model example. It was a courtyard formed by the gathering of large numbers of mush room Gu.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was the apex of examples, possessing the ability to defend, gather, store and other effects. It was formed by countless small towers, divert disaster Gu being one of the main cornerstones. Sacrificing the gathered wild Gu, it created a power that would form the main body.

There was also White Bone Chariot.

Back then, Proud Bone Demon Lord Shen Jie Ao had outstanding and shocking talent. When he became a rank six Gu Immortal, he lacked a rank six Gu. So he came up with a killer move known as White Bone Chariot.

The White Bone Chariot was formed from many rank five Gu, such as the White Bone Wheel, and had power comparable to a rank six Gu!

This White Bone Chariot was actually a Gu house!

As for three star cave, lizard house and large lizard house, they were all branches developed from simplified forms of Gu houses.

Normal Gu houses were formed from the combination of several Gu worms. As three star cave and the others were formed from just one Gu, thus their might was greatly reduced and became commonly used Gu houses.

Water Pavilion was a rank seven Immortal Gu house, this signified there was at least one rank seven Immortal Gu among the Gu worms used to create it!

"With my current level, I cannot refine Immortal Gu. But refining the mortal Gu is still possible."

This was where Fang Yuan's confidence in refining Water Pavilion lay in.

There were not many difficulties during the refining process.

Water Pavilion was one of the symbols of Spirit Affinity House, wielded by Fairy Mo Yao back then.

Mo Yao betrayed the sect for her love and refined calamity beckoning Gu, sacrificing herself. This Immortal Gu house thus became ownerless.

As such, to Fang Yuan, Water Pavilion was like a little beauty that had its arms wide open and he was free to play with it.

"Amazing, there were actually no less than three thousand Gu worms used in the assembly of Water Pavilion. And every Gu worm was closely interrelated and had a faint resonance between them. The core was rank seven Water Harmony Gu which allows the Gu Master to completely merge and hide in water; as long as the water was not extinguished, they won't die. Besides this, there were also two assisting Immortal Gu - rank six movement Immortal Gu Worldly Wave Trace and wisdom path Immortal Gu Delight in Water and Mountain."

The process of refining was in fact, the process of deepening his understanding of Water Pavilion.

Refining an Immortal Gu was far beyond Fang Yuan's ability, so there was no need to attempt it in vain. What he could make a move on were the rank one and rank two mortal Gu.

Fang Yuan spent six hours in refinement till he was dizzy, completely refining five hundred rank one and rank two mortal Gu.

"I now have ten percent control over Water Pavilion. Even if someone discovers it, this ten percent of authority will be able to block them for a while. This time will be enough for me to be alerted and rush here in time."

He refined for another two hours and increased his control authority to thirteen percent.

The difficulty of the refinement continued to increase at the later stages.

"Unfortunately, I have Spring Autumn Cicada which is like a ticking time bomb. I cannot use time path's instant success Gu and other Gu to help me in the refining process, otherwise my progress would not be just this."

Fang Yuan felt his head spinning and knew he had already reached the limit. The primeval essence in his two rank five peak stage apertures was also almost exhausted.

But just when he thought of pulling away, a figure suddenly appeared in his mind.

"After such a long time, I finally meet the fated one today."

Following the indistinct sigh, the graceful figure of a woman with a slim body, shining dark eyes, and a veil covering her face, appeared in Fang Yuan's mind.

"This is Fairy Mo Yao's will, when did it enter my mind?!" Fang Yuan was inwardly shocked.

So much time had passed, Mo Yao was not a venerable but she was still able to leave behind her will, one could tell how strong a cultivation she had back then.

Fang Yuan actually already had taken precautions, but Fairy Mo Yao clearly had some special methods that allowed her will to silently enter Fang Yuan's mind.

Such an ability was not trivial.

Mo Yao's will had entered Fang Yuan's mind, if she wanted to unceremoniously create difficulties for him, then Fang Yuan would absolutely have to suffer the consequences.

Fang Yuan was not a wisdom path expert, only wisdom path Gu Masters had the power to subdue this kind of will.

The most crucial thing was that when people pondered, their thoughts would first emerge. These thoughts would clash with each other in the brain and then transform, creating a new thought. This was the process of thinking.

Now, Mo Yao's will had entered Fang Yuan's mind which meant she could hear all his thoughts clearly!

What would happen once Mo Yao's will learned of Spring Autumn Cicada?

"No need to be afraid, fated one, I have no intention of harming you. I only want to ask you a question." Mo Yao's will faintly asked.

Fang Yuan did not even need to guess to know what she was going to ask. He told her about the fact of Bo Qing's defeat on the spot.

When she heard this grievous news, Mo Yao's will shook to the point of collapsing!

Fang Yuan was rejoicing covertly, but he had to be disappointed because Mo Yao's will was able to maintain her form in the end.

Her dark as night eyes were filled with tears. Fairy Mo Yao's expression was extremely complex; there was sadness, but there was relief as well.

Like she said in her poem 'too long has passed, emotions and hatred have already lasted for a long time', her love and hatred with Bo Qing was a long tale that was touching and deeply intertwined.

"Fated one, since you can refine calamity beckoning Gu and also found this place and have begun refining Water Pavilion, you should already have a general understanding. Since he is already dead, then let everything go. Sigh... maybe this is the fortune of the living."

Mo Yao's will paused before continuing: "I have already let down Spirit Affinity House, my only wish now is to return this Water Pavilion. As compensation, I will impart my life's refinement path attainment insights to you. Besides this, I will also tell you the secret information of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

Chapter 569: Six Arm Heavenly Zombie King

The entire sacred palace was shrouded in an aurora.

The light was dazzling and shone for the radius of a hundred li.

Looking at the top of the sacred palace, two layers of the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had already formed, huge numbers of people were entering and exiting daily.

Retracting his gaze, Fang Yuan softly closed the windows.

Half a month had passed since he refined calamity beckoning Gu and returned from the Water Pavilion.

During this period, Hei Lou Lan opened up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and did not charge any fees, allowing people to enter as they wished.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building — Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's inheritance ground, it had incredible attraction to all Gu Masters.

Countless Gu Masters with Giant Sun's bloodline entered like torrents of water, even if they could not get through, they wanted to observe the glory of the event.

Especially after Eighty-Eight True Yang Building underwent a transformation and formed two layers, it triggered the people's desires to explore.

As for outsiders, they could only enter using the guest token.

The guest token was a one time expenditure item, it could only be obtained on occasion when getting through a round.

Until now, there had only been seven guest tokens obtained. Each fetched an astronomical price, but it did not deter any of the expert Gu Masters who did not have Giant Sun's bloodline.

Fang Yuan had the glass owner token now, he could freely enter and exit Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and even enter the treasure room. But in order to conceal himself, not long ago, he still paid a hefty price to buy a guest token.

"Young man, I would advise you to prepare the ink transformation killer move that I taught you. That way, once you enter the central control hall, you would have less trouble."

A female voice resounded in Fang Yuan's mind.

It was none other than Fairy Mo Yao's will who had stealthily sneaked in.

Fang Yuan heard this and frowned, in his heart he snorted and replied: "This killer move is too outdated. Some of the Gu worms have already disappeared, if I want to collect them now, it will take quite some effort, how can it be rushed?"

Mo Yao's will laughed: "Young man, you are quite fortunate to have Hu Immortal blessed land. You should make good use of treasure yellow heaven, it is not hard to purchase these Gu worms."

Fang Yuan frowned even more tightly.

He deciphered the code and obtained Di Qiu inheritance, even successfully refining calamity beckoning Gu, but he also gained a huge problem known as Mo Yao's will.

Mo Yao's will was now lurking inside his mind, it was a huge threat.

When Fang Yuan thinks, thoughts would be generated.

Mo Yao's will could read these thoughts and understand Fang Yuan's secrets.

In half a month's time, she learnt about many of his secrets, including Hu Immortal blessed land.

Right now, Fang Yuan could only use space thought Gu to think.

Using space thought Gu as the main component, and other Gu worms to assist it, the thoughts formed had the power of space imbued in them, Mo Yao's will could not read them even if she caught them.

But such a situation was only temporary.

Will ruled above thoughts, Mo Yao's will was inside Fang Yuan's mind, after interacting with these space thoughts for a long time, she would become familiar with them, and this line of defense would not be able to stop her.

"Young man, you are young but you have many secrets. Hehehe, really interesting." Mo Yao's will floated in the air, moving up and down.

She laughed as she covered her mouth, her eyes were watery and her posture was alluring, she was truly a past generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House.

After staying with Fang Yuan for a while, she became more active, and even more curious, her nature of wanting to probe people's secrets showed itself.

Every generation of Spirit Affinity House's fairies was the cream of the crop, one out of ten thousand, she would be talented and beautiful, pure and elegant like a sacred lotus. But Mo Yao was different, her dark pupils contained some craftiness, if she was in the demonic path, she would definitely be a demoness.

She created an illusory robe, covering her body while showing the contours, she looked at the bubble-like thoughts as she grabbed one of them.

Next, she exerted strength and with a 'pop', this thought exploded with some force.

But she did not gain anything, because this thought's content was two words, 'eating dinner'.

She gasped lightly, her beautiful lips curving into an arousing angle: "Young man, you are not cute at all. Every time you think about something, you will make up all sorts of random thoughts to conceal the important points. Do you know that this will, in fact, make this big sister even more curious?"

"Hmph, with your age, you have the face to call yourself big sister?" Fang Yuan snorted, threatening, "You are dead, you should rest in peace. Don't think that I cannot do anything to you now that you are in my mind. Who knows, I might make your will perish the next moment."

"Hehehe, so scary..." Mo Yao patted her plump chest, laughing without any concern: "But during this half a month of time, you attacked me twenty-eight times using nineteen methods. Don't tell me, you are not only a strength-enslavement dual cultivator, but you also cultivate in wisdom path?"

"Hmph!" Fang Yuan's heart was surging with killing intent.

"Aiyaya[1], young man, don't be like this." Feeling Fang Yuan's sharp killing intent, Mo Yao waved her fingers: "I am your benefactor, isn't calamity beckoning Gu your Immortal Gu now? You are still a mortal, it is an amazing accomplishment to have an Immortal Gu. Don't worry, don't worry, once you return this Water Pavilion to Spirit Affinity House, my wish would be fulfilled, and this will would no longer have any reason to exist."

Return the rank seven Immortal Gu house Water Pavilion?

The juicy meat had already entered Fang Yuan's mouth, why would he spit it out?

Fang Yuan did not want to do so, obviously, but he had no other choices.

Not mentioning the piece of Mo Yao's will in his mind, there was also a portion of Mo Yao's remnant will inside the Water Pavilion.

That meant, this Mo Yao was quite impressive.

History said that she was a refinement grandmaster. But in terms of wisdom path and soul path, it seems she was even more skilled in them. Fang Yuan's multitude of mental attacks were all easily dispelled by her.

Fang Yuan had a huge headache now.

Even though he obtained Di Qiu inheritance, he did not earn much.

He took a huge risk and made great investments to carry out Gu refinement. In the end, he obtained calamity beckoning Gu but it was unusable. Mo Yao's will even entered his mind, causing him to refrain from shooting at the rat for fear of breaking the vase, this was his greatest burden at the moment.

"Had I known this, I would not have gone after this dogshit Di Qiu inheritance."

This thought was not concealed at all, Mo Yao easily read about it.

"Young man, that is not true. The refinement path killer move ink transformation that I taught you over these days is priceless. Didn't you want to make use of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's loophole, hehe, you are so daring, almost at the same level as me. Don't worry, I will help you, as long as you return Water Pavilion to Spirit Affinity House." Mo Yao urged.

"Hmph, calamity beckoning Gu is mine, but I also want Water Pavilion, even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building might become my possession! You are a mere will, how can you stop me, a living person?" Since they had fought for dozens of times already, Fang Yuan rejected her outright.

But this time, Mo Yao did not make fun of him, her gaze shone as she recalled something.

Her expression was lonely as she sighed deeply: "Sigh, are all men like this? Even if they did something wrong, they would act in such a confident manner, unrelenting in their convictions being right."

"In this world, what counts as wrong? Who is right, who is wrong? Everyone's way of life is just different."

Mo Yao's expression changed, she laughed cheekily: "Young man, this is an interesting answer. But I've heard another answer, it was much more domineering than yours. He said —'In this world, anything I think or do is right. Those that differ from me are wrong.' Hehehe, is that domineering enough?"

Fang Yuan's gaze shone: "Sword Immortal Bo Qing said that? Unfortunately, he did not succeed in that final step."

These words made Mo Yao sink into silence, her face was full of sadness as she shut her eyes, memories were pouring in her mind as her long eyelashes were slightly trembling.

She hid her figure, vanishing from Fang Yuan's mind.

"Damn it, she did this again!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, every time Mo Yao's will hid herself, it would be like she did not exist, no matter how Fang Yuan tried to find her, he would not even see a trace of her.

Mo Yao's attainment in soul path and wisdom path greatly exceeded Fang Yuan's. This resulted in her having free reign in his mind.

But this time, he was not going to leave empty handed.

In his mind, he found one of Mo Yao's will's thoughts.

The content made Fang Yuan's heart shudder.

This was a killer move, named — Six Arm Heavenly Zombie King!

Fang Yuan had been trying to find a way to combine strength and enslavement paths, he thought hard and obtained an initial result, it was his strength path killer move — Four Arm Earth King.

Using this move, he went on a killing spree in the final battle of the Imperial Court contest, defeating Ma tribe army and pushing Hei Lou Lan into Imperial Court Blessed Land.

But four arm earth king was only a casually created killer move, it was full of flaws and after Fang Yuan improved on it, it became the killer move four arm wind king.

After that, he found a crucial borrow strength Gu inside the treasure room of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, allowing the killer move four arm wind king to gain a huge improvement.

After Mo Yao's will entered his mind, he purposely exposed a portion of his secrets, among them was this killer move, as well as his thoughts about improving this killer move.

"Fantastic!" Fang Yuan praised.

With his foundation, and Fairy Mo Yao's attainment, six arm heavenly zombie king was a killer move nearing perfection.

It used borrow strength Gu as the core, six types of flying zombie Gu as the supplement, and another thirty-six Gu worms in order to design this killer move with an amazing and specialized structure, Fang Yuan was in great awe.

"However, I know about the five great flying zombie Gu, but this killer move needs a sixth flying zombie Gu? What Gu is that?"

The killer move in the thought was not complete, it still lacked the final crucial step.

[1] Eng: Tsk tsk. Japanese: Ara ara. Back

Chapter 570: Compromise

In the dark secret room, there was a soothing sandalwood smell.

Fang Yuan sat on the cushion, holding an east window Gu in his hand.

This Gu was of the information path, rank four and shaped like a ladybug, the armor on its back was square, like window panels, specially used to store important information.

This Gu was purposely bought in treasure yellow heaven by Fang Yuan.

The content was all about wills.

Ever since Mo Yao's will had lurked in his mind, Fang Yuan had been buying and collecting information in this regard, he spent many immortal essence stones.

This east window Gu was not the first.

Long after, Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes, his gaze clear as water.

After reading so much precious information, he had a deeper understanding towards wills.

Thought, will, emotion, the three were of the same branch, the former two belonged to the wisdom path and had much connection to many paths.

Wisdom path, when first created, was a path for Gu Masters that seeked wisdom solely.

When people think, thoughts would appear in their mind, when these thoughts collide, fuse, or cancel each other out, new thoughts would be formed, this would be the thinking process.

These thoughts were classified into different categories, they were all different and had their own specialities.

Among them, the most famous one was the obsession.

When a Gu Immortal dies, their lingering obsession would combine with the heavenly power and form the land spirit within the blessed land.

Gu Masters used these thoughts to create countless related Gu worms, like Dong Fang Yu Liang's star thought Gu, and Fang Yuan's space thought Gu, as well as Gu Immortals' commonly used divine sense Gu.

A few thoughts gather, forming 'will'.

The saying goes: Will can be understood, but not described.

Will cannot be expressed in words, the essence of will has surpassed the limits of written expression, only by using one's heart, using a human's spirituality, can it be felt.

Initially, wisdom path Gu Masters created heaven's will Gu. This Gu was used to comprehend the mechanics of the great Dao of heaven and earth, allowing one to further gain knowledge about heaven and earth, in order to improve on their own attainment.

After that, as the path continued to develop, more Gu were created, killing intent Gu, casual Gu, one's wishes Gu, proud Gu, evil intent Gu, painting idea Gu and others.

Among them, the most famous one was recorded in the legends of Ren Zu, the legendary unexpected Gu.

As wisdom path continued to develop, generations of Gu Masters continued to research, and they found out that when a few 'wills' merged together, they become 'emotion'.

Estrus Gu, gentle feelings Gu, and emotion poetry Gu were all from this path. Enchantment path was derived from this.

The most famous Gu in this path similarly came from \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> — Love Gu.

"Thought, will, emotion..." Fang Yuan sighed.

The more he learnt, the more he understood — with his current foundation in wisdom path, he could not get rid of Mo Yao's will!

The difference between them was too great.

For example, in terms of their attainment in will, Fang Yuan was like a mound, while Mo Yao's will was like a tall mountain. As for how tall this mountain was, or how grand it was, Fang Yuan could not tell as it was shrouded in a thick layer of mist.

Mo Yao's attainment had greatly exceeded Fang Yuan's understanding. During these days of interaction and probing, it left a deep impression on Fang Yuan, he felt that she was truly on another level, her attainment was as deep as an abyss.

Facing such great trouble, if he could not get rid of it, what would he do?

Sitting on the cushion, after pondering for a while, Fang Yuan's gaze turned cold as he made a decision.

His consciousness entered his mind, and with just a thought, Mo Yao's will felt it and her alluring figure appeared from within the pitch-black area in the mind.

"I accept your suggestion, I will return Water Pavilion to Spirit Affinity House." Fang Yuan transmitted his second thought.

Mo Yao's eyes flashed with a peculiar light.

She did not expect that Fang Yuan would compromise so quickly.

According to their interaction these days, she understood clearly that Fang Yuan was that type of person with immense willpower, he was very assertive and his personality was tough and bold.

Character decides one's fate, this kind of person would either become a conqueror or a hero, they were destined to be a man above man, an elite among the elite.

She left behind the six arm heavenly zombie king killer move, but she had some reservations and did not give him the entire thing. Instead of a bait, this was more like an indication of her attitude.

She knew that with Fang Yuan's intelligence, he would understand what she was trying to say.

She had estimated that Fang Yuan would choose to negotiate with her in about seven or eight days. But in truth, he came to look for her after a day's time.

"Sigh, a wise man submits to circumstances, a great man is one who is resilient... Unfortunately most people in this world think too highly of their own abilities and refuse to lower their head due to pride. Throughout history, countless experts knew the logic of taking a step back and compromising, but it was easier said than done, when it was their turn, how many people could take that step?" Mo Yao's will sighed as she said with deep emotion.

"Although Water Pavilion is good, it is not useful to me. You know my situation, right now because of Hu Immortal blessed land, Immortal Crane Sect has declared that I am a member of their sect. Spirit Affinity House and Immortal Crane Sect are both part of the top ten sects in central continent, it will not be easy for me to return Water Pavilion to them." Fang Yuan said.

"Hehehe." Mo Yao's will chuckled: "Young man, I know what you mean. Don't worry, you are my inheritor, the calamity beckoning Gu is yours, I have no intention to harm you. Returning the Immortal Gu house is a huge matter, I understand the risks clearly. To accomplish this mission, you need to be a Gu Immortal at least. I will do my best to help you become a Gu Immortal, and I will also assist you in obtaining Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. As for my refinement attainment, it will depend on how much you can learn."

Mo Yao said so as she waved her hand, and a thought floated in Fang Yuan's heart.

The content was the final crucial part of the killer move six arm heavenly zombie king.

Fang Yuan immediately asked unhappily: "Earth chief zombie? Are you serious, this is the so-called sixth flying zombie Gu?"

Earth chief zombie Gu, he knew about it.

This was obtained by killing an earth chief beast, using its skin and tendons as the materials, combined with tens of Gu worms, and using the yin soil that was nine hundred li deep in the ground, as well as mountain absorbing grass that were hundreds of years old, dark tide flowers and other materials to refine.

Although it was quite strong, a rank five Gu just like asura zombie, heavenly demon zombie, blood wight, nightmare zombie and plague zombie, it could not fly.

Without flying abilities, how could it be a 'flying zombie' Gu?

Facing Fang Yuan's suspicion, Mo Yao laughed arrogantly: "Ordinary earth chief zombie Gu would not do. But who is this big sister? Hehe, I modified the recipe long ago, and refined a new earth chief zombie Gu. When a Gu Master uses it and becomes an earth chief zombie, even without wings, they can make use of the natural magnetic field to soar into the air, and fly as they wish."

Saying so, she transmitted another thought, it was the recipe of the modified earth chief zombie Gu.

Fang Yuan looked at it and his eyes shone.

Mo Yao had daringly added several new materials into this Gu recipe, among them was original magnetic essence as the main ingredient. That was the most important element in this modification of the Gu.

Fang Yuan thought about it and with his five hundred years of experience, he knew that this Gu recipe was usable, he could not help but praise in amazement.

Mo Yao's will was in his mind, she laughed smugly: "Young man, you really know your stuff. Not bad, you have some talent in refinement. But you have to be careful, this killer move was only created based on what you provided me, I would advise you to test it out on a few people before trying it yourself."

Fang Yuan nodded.

The killer move six arm heavenly zombie king had great power, it was about ten times as strong as four arm earth king and four arm wind king.

Because it was so powerful, once it fails, the backlash would also be equally powerful.

Fang Yuan could test the four arm earth king himself earlier because the risks were not great, he could endure them. But this six arm heavenly zombie king was another story.

　　...

"The third layer, the third layer has formed!" In the sacred palace, cheers resounded throughout the area.

The rainbow colored aurora was still thick as ever.

As time passed, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was forming faster and faster, especially the newly formed third layer, it made everyone's urge to explore it go wild.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's floors each have a hundred rounds, the earlier rounds were easy. But as they progressed, they got harder and the rewards were greater.

Most Gu Masters do not have the strength to tackle the later rounds, but the earlier rounds had rewards that they would fight for.

A group of Gu Masters, about a dozen, were leaving the palace in a hurry.

When they were about to get past the sacred palace's eastern entrance, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's third layer formed and these Gu Masters stopped in their tracks.

Jiang Dong looked at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building which was at the peak of the sacred palace, snorting and saying to Ma Hong Yun who was in the group: "You Huang Jin tribe Gu Masters are so lucky, any reward inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building can allow you to soar to success and gain great riches!"

Ma Hong Yun laughed sheepishly: "Leader is right, hehehe. Sadly, my bloodline is not thick enough, I cannot enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Otherwise, I would go in to expand my vision."

Even though Huang Jin tribesmen were Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's descendants, they were not guaranteed entry into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

If their ancestors had diluted the bloodline too much by marrying outsiders, they would not reach the requirement and would not be able to enter.

Jiang Dong heard this and the bitterness and jealousy in his heart lessened. The other Gu Masters in the group also looked at Ma Hong Yun more gently, someone even patted Ma Hong Yun's shoulder and consoled: "You are really unlucky, but never mind, you can earn a fortune this time by coming with us to kill the earth chief beast as well!"

"Yes, yes, yes." Ma Hong Yun nodded as he bowed, laughing apologetically.

He had saved Ma Ying Jie coincidentally. After Hei tribe forcefully took over Ma tribe, due to a series of events, he changed his surname and became Ma Hong Yun, finally allowed to cultivate.

Right now, he was a rank one Gu Master, his aptitude was neither good nor bad.

Of course he could enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, but with his strength, there was no point in that at all. During his stay in the sacred palace, he could mix around with hunting groups daily and go out to hunt, it allowed him to earn enough to cover his daily expenses and accumulate primeval stones to cultivate.

As for what he told Jiang Dong, that was Zhao Lian Yun's instruction before he set off.

Chapter 571: Deserves death without pity

Boom boom boom...

The earth rumbled, wolves charged out like tides, they were endless like the flood water, charging forward relentlessly.

Tens of thousands of wolves sprinted, the wolf group was in chaos. There were wind wolves running like they were flying, water wolves with their snow-white bodies, night wolves who were slim and stealthy, turtleback wolves who were stable and sturdy, vermillion flame wolves who were burning fiercely.

Hundred wolf king, thousand wolf king, and myriad wolf king led the army along with the mutated wolves, they were travelling in packs and were very conspicuous.

Like the blood forest wolf, with a bone forest on its back, tall as a mountain. The shark fin wolf with with skin like that of an elephant, while being amphibious. The frenzy wolf with three silver-grey eyes, being a battle maniac.

Inside Imperial Court blessed land, in the light golden sky, there were azure wolves running in the air, howling as they gave off a strong aura.

Fang Yuan sat on an azure myriad wolf king's back as the strong winds could not affect his determined and resolved expression.

His eyes were dark like the abyss, he was looking down with his thoughts unpredictable.

Although the wolves were scattered when he first entered Imperial Court blessed land, Fang Yuan had been handing out missions to others and had been recalling the old wolves as well as recruiting new wolves since. By now, he had about five hundred thousand wolves running below him like the tides of the sea.

At this point, he was truly at the peak of the mortal realm.

During the Imperial Court contest, he was one of the five beast kings together with Jiang Bao Ya, Ma Zun and others. After the Imperial Court contest, just looking at northern plains alone, he was the current generation's number one enslavement master.

Other than his enslavement attainment, he also displayed great technique in his strength path cultivation, and was also a flying master, it was truly a shocking achievement.

Who did not respect and revere the great Wolf King Chang Shan Yin?

In the entire northern plains, how many could actually put up a challenge before him?

But at this moment, in Fang Yuan's mind, there was a voice 'discouraging' him.

"Hehehe, young man, you want to combine strength and enslavement, that is really a tall order. I would advise you to give up on that as soon as possible."

Mo Yao's will continued: "Strength and enslavement are very distinct from each other. The combination of strength and enslavement has been an age old problem. It was not easy for you to even dual cultivate them, why don't you change them now while it is early, there is no need to do something so meaningless and troublesome, I had gone through this back in my days. You need to know, there are countless paths and ways to be a Gu Master, our strength is not reliant on the number of paths we are on, but the depth of our attainment."

Mo Yao explained to him patiently, but Fang Yuan scoffed, arrogantly refusing: "Problems are meant to be solved, what is there to be afraid of? Enslavement-strength dual cultivation is an age old problem, that is because I had not been born back in those days. I will eventually have the world in my palms, my name will go down in history, just like Star Constellation, Red Lotus, Paradise Earth and others."

Star Constellation, Red Lotus, Paradise Earth were all rank nine venerables. In the long history of mankind, the river of time flowed endlessly, but there were only ten of them throughout the ages.

Fang Yuan was a mortal, but he was aiming to be such a person, it was like an ant trying to become an elephant.

Such lofty ambitions and tone, even Mo Yao's will was tongue-tied when she heard it.

　　...

"Howl!"

"Kill, kill all of these earth chief beasts!"

"Where is the healing Gu Master? Someone is injured, quickly come and help!"

The beasts were growling, the Gu Masters were shouting, a small-scale fight was reaching its climax.

On the relatively small battlefield, there were holes on the ground, broken limbs and blood everywhere. Five to six Gu Masters were surrounding the earth chief beast king, engaging in fierce combat. There were large numbers of earth chief beast corpses surrounding them.

These earth chief beasts had a humanoid body and a snake tail, their face resembled bats, and their nose were pointed up. They had large ears and a black body covered in flesh armor. All around their chests, there were five to six flesh whips, ranging from tens of centimeters to meters long.

The whips were like hands, agile like snakes as they flung with huge force, both offensively and defensively.

The earth chief beasts lived underground, but they only lived near the surface and not deep underneath.

They had great value, be it their eyes, fur, or tail, they were rare and valuable Gu refinement material. What was most rare was their flesh whips, the longer they were the better, whips that were six meters or longer were often priceless, almost none were sold in the market.

Right now in northern plains, earth chief beasts were almost going extinct. But in Imperial Court blessed land, they lived in huge numbers, for example at this area, for the surrounding ten thousand li, there were earth chief beast groups living underground.

Money moved people's hearts, because this was close to the sacred palace, many Gu Masters often gathered in groups and hunted at this place.

This battling group was one of them.

The Gu Masters in the group had hunted down the earth chief beasts for several times already, they were quite experienced.

But this time, they encountered trouble. Although they attracted an earth chief beast group, there were only a hundred of them which was manageable for them. However, the beast king was not an ordinary hundred beast king, but an old thousand beast king. Although this old beast king could not battle and was old and sickly, it had many wild Gu in it, and had truly the battle strength of a rank three.

Among mortal Gu Masters, rank one were students, they had just started and were weak, being the most commonly seen ones. Rank two were the foundation of tribes, the main source of manpower, they were quite common.

Rank three were elders, they were the pillars of support for the clan, and were much more rare than rank two Gu Masters. Rank four were the leaders, capable to leading ten thousand men. Rank five was the peak of the mortal realm, they were the rarest of the mortal Gu Masters.

Earth chief thousand beast king was not a problem by itself, but the rank three that it had were too much for this group to handle.

During the start of the battle, the leader Jiang Dong was decisive and had great experience, ordering his group and bringing some people to break into the beast group, stalling the earth chief beast king, while the others slaughtered the earth chief beasts. Otherwise, the group would have crumbled already.

"Everyone, put in more effort! This old beast is going down, we will win if we can endure!" Jiang Dong shouted to raise the group's morale.

Everyone replied quickly, raising their concentration and mental focus.

From the start of the battle until now, an hour had passed. The Gu Masters were almost out of primeval essence, but because of northern plains' culture, these Gu Masters all cultivated strength path as well.

The Gu Masters fought bravely, using close combat primarily, only using their primeval essence when they had no choice to save themselves or others.

Howl!

Right at this time, the old beast king swung its snake tail, causing the air to crackle. The snake tail hit one of the Gu Masters and sent him flying. When he landed, this Gu Master's chest was smashed and his bones were all broken, he was beyond dead.

Humans had intelligence, beasts had their craftiness too.

The old beast king was really weak, but that did not mean it was powerless. When it burst out its remaining strength, it killed one person immediately.

The Gu Masters were stunned, their morale fell rock bottom.

"Oh no, we were already at a stalemate earlier, that that we are one man down, and my primeval essence is less than twenty percent left, what will we do?" Jiang Dong's eyes rolled as he thought of escaping.

This hunting group was only established at a whim, although running away would ruin his reputation, what was reputation compared to death?

Northern plainsmen were battle lovers, it was true that they were ferocious and brave, but they were not stupid.

"In the past, life was tough and I could only fight desperately to survive. Now that I am inside Imperial Court blessed land, with ample resources lying around, I should be accumulating my foundation and soaring into the sky. How can I sacrifice my precious life here?"

"I have parents and children back at home, although these hunting gains were good, the primeval stones are only enough to sustain my own cultivation. That rascal at home will be starting his cultivation journey in half a year... thus, sorry everyone!"

Jiang Dong's gaze shone for a while, as he retreated suddenly, using all his remaining primeval essence on his movement Gu.

He tore through the air, with a 'swoosh' sound, he vanished like the wind.

The remaining Gu Masters were stunned again, the leader ran away in battle, what can they do now?

Immediately, everyone scattered as morale became non-existent.

The earth chief beast king growled, chasing after them.

"The f*ck!" Jiang Dong looked back and cursed, his soul almost flew into the nine heavens.

This old earth chief beast king chose to chase after him out of all the people, most likely his ruthless attacks and fierce offense enraged the old beast.

"Oh no, my life will be over at this rate!"

The two ran and chased, as time passed, his primeval was expended and Jiang Dong fell into despair.

"Lord Jiang Dong, please run!"

At this time, a voice could be heard from afar.

Jiang Dong turned around and saw a young man at the left, it was Ma Hong Yun who had joined the group not too long ago. He had rank one cultivation and was a support Gu Master with little battle strength. From the start of the battle, he had been dispatched and was used to investigate the area.

"What a foolish lad!" Jiang Dong was overjoyed, he changed directions and ran towards Ma Hong Yun.

Ma Hong Yun's eyes were wide open, he saw the old earth chief beast king chasing Jiang Dong and had the urge to remind him. To think that Jiang Dong actually lured the old beast king towards him.

Ma Hong Yun ran immediately, but Jiang Dong was even faster, in a few breaths' time, he got close to him.

Jiang Dong laughed loudly: "Lad, you saved my life today, your death is not in vain."

Saying so, he used his Gu worm and knocked Ma Hong Yun unconsciously, stretching out his hand and tossing him behind.

But the old earth chief beast king ignored that free meal and still chased after Jiang Dong non-stop.

Jiang Dong's laughter came to an end, his mood went from heaven to hell.

Just as old earth chief beast king got close to him, he could hear rumbling in his ears as the ground started to shake.

Next, from far away in the sky, a line was getting bigger and clearer.

Wolves!

Why are there so many wolves?!

The wolf tide rained down from the sky, the grand aura it gave off was like flood water that was engulfing the world.

The old thousand beast king froze, after being in a short daze, it shuddered and turned around to run away.

"Vermillion flame wolves, turtleback wolves... such a wolf group, that's right, there was an announcement, Wolf King was going to hunt at this area! Ahahaha, my life is not meant to be over, I am saved!"

Jiang Dong cheered loudly after his initial shock. He sat on the ground, his body shivering in excitement, the hope after despair was making him feel great relief as tears flowed out of his eyes.

But the next moment, the wolf tide came without slowly down, charging like a waves as it tore him into pieces in a few seconds.

In the golden sky, atop the azure wolf, Mo Yao's will spoke in Fang Yuan's mind with a sorrowful sigh: "Fang Yuan, you allow these wolves to kill every living thing in their path, be it enemy or ally. Your killing intent is too strong, are you not afraid of going against the natural order, are you not afraid of other Gu Masters' opinion?"

"Hmph, I announced my hunt long ago. These people are overwhelmed by greed, they are like ants, there is no pity for them when they are blocking my path." Fang Yuan replied plainly.

Chapter 572: Successfully refining the Earth Chief Zombie Gu

The wolf group was like a tsunami leaving a trail of blood wherever it went in the blessed land.

Fang Yuan was sitting indifferently on the back of an azure wolf king, turning a blind eye to the massacre happening in front of him.

In his mind, Mo Yao's will frowned slightly.

She was a fairy nurtured by Spirit Affinity House, a person of the righteous path; she was naturally not happy at Fang Yuan's casual massacre.

"This young man could disguise his identity and sneak into Imperial Court blessed land under the eyes of northern plains' Gu Immortals; he is a dauntless and crafty person. He also deciphered the clues of my inheritance and refined the Immortal Gu, he was not only fated but also had extraordinary methods. Even more importantly, he knows to bow and submit, when he knows that things cannot always go his way, he immediately compromises, this person is extremely shrewd as well! What is his origin?"

Mo Yao's will could not help but wonder about that question.

She had just recently come out of Water Pavilion and resided in Fang Yuan's mind; she had analyzed many of Fang Yuan's thoughts and immediately learned numerous secrets of his.

However, Fang Yuan's response was quick and he immediately took preventive measures, making her progress slow down greatly.

Thus, Mo Yao's will learnt of Fang Yuan's secrets but what she knew was limited.

Among them included the secrets Fang Yuan revealed to her of his own accord.

She still did not know that Fang Yuan possessed Spring Autumn Cicada, thus she had no way of knowing Fang Yuan's biggest secret of being a transmigrator.

This was the world of Gu.

Mo Yao had already perished and what was left was only a portion of her will. Unable to use Gu worms, Mo Yao's will could only take advantage of Fang Yuan's low attainment in wisdom path.

"I had just recently awakened, I do not know what his background is. This young man has absurdly firm willpower and is extremely opinionated. I should just bide my time and guide him to return Water Pavilion to the sect first. It will not be too late to persuade him to do good once we arrive at Spirit Affinity House..."

Mo Yao's will had inherited some intelligence of the main body and immediately kept quiet when she realized any persuasion would be in vain.

There was no resistance at all; Fang Yuan's dark and eerie gaze slowly retracted, closing his eyes to rest on the wolf's back.

He was not someone who slaughtered willfully.

There were reasons for letting the wolves massacre at full force today.

One was to attract the earth chief beast groups underground. Earth chief beast was a wild beast, the thick smell of blood would attract and stimulate their savage nature, making them risk emerging from the ground.

Second was that the massacre would produce large numbers of souls. Since the start of the Imperial Court contest, Fang Yuan had been using soul burial toad to collect the souls. He had Dang Hun mountain, and as long as Dang Hun mountain did not die completely, the more souls he had, the better it was for him.

The third reason was aimed at Mo Yao's will in his mind, he was trying to probe her.

As for the nasty repercussions from wantonly killing Gu Masters, Fang Yuan was happy instead of afraid.

Not mentioning that he had already made a public announcement, making the consequences clear to everyone, even if the public stirs and the resentment and hatred towards him rises, so what?

He was at the peak of mortals, the famous Wolf King Chang Shan Yin! He was no longer the minor character several years ago who had to act cautiously.

In this Imperial Court blessed land where Gu Immortals could not enter, his one shout could cause countless Gu Masters to tremble. His stomp could shake the sacred palace. With one thought, the wolf groups would instantly create a bloodbath.

There was a famous saying on Earth — Political power comes from military strength.

A strong fist is power and power is the truth!

But on Earth, power was concentrated in the masses. Besides violence and fists, one needed to use righteousness to conceal the truth and compromise according to the public sentiment.

But here, individual strength was far above the group. Public sentiment and righteousness were much weaker. Not mentioning anyone else, just take the current Fang Yuan as an example — who cares about your dogshit hatred and grudges, whoever comes will face decimation! Whoever is not pleasing to the eyes, they can be slaughtered with no care at all!

Looking disdainfully at all lives, trampling on the public sentiment, without restraints and free like the wind!

But in Fang Yuan's pursuit of the Great Dao, he had no interest towards casually slaughtering ants. Today's large scale massacre was no more than a small step towards his majestic target.

As he thought of this trip's goal, Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes.

Howl!

A beast roar echoed to the skies.

A mound bulged up from a distance before bursting open; mud and stones splattered around as a fifty feet tall earth chief myriad beast king jumped out.

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with a chilly light as he sneered: "You shall be the one."

At once, he commanded the wolf group to attack, endless thoughts flew about in his mind like an endless drizzle.

If one looked from a high altitude, one would see an extremely spectacular scene of innumerable wolves rushing forward like an endless tide.

As they neared the earth chief myriad beast king, the wolves suddenly split into several groups like ants trying to climb up an elephant. At the same time, azure wolves howled and flew down, spiralling around earth chief myriad beast king like birds.

Earth chief myriad beast king jumped towards the wolf group and started rampaging, soon, wolf blood splattered and wolf corpses covered the ground. Its four giant legs would leave behind terrifying blood pits in its trail.

Fang Yuan had a smile as he observed the battle from the skies.

Under his control, the wolf groups advanced and retreated, sometimes slowly and sometimes quickly, as they charged forward wave after wave, forming a situation of ants devouring an elephant.

Earth chief myriad beast king roared again and again while valiantly charging all around, causing large numbers of casualties in the wolf groups.

In Fang Yuan's mind, Mo Yao gave a soft exclamation of surprise, slightly shocked at Fang Yuan's enslavement path attainment.

"Wow, I had not expected this kid to have so much talent at this young age, commanding these wolves as naturally as breathing, and with such ease like he is moving his arms, he has mastered the art of attrition battle of enslavement path, fighting the strong with a weak force, this is a master level attainment..."

But it was nothing more than a slight shock.

Mo Yao had seen and experienced a lot in her life and was not an ordinary Gu Immortal, but a certain generation's fairy of Spirit Affinity House; her horizons were broad and masters as young as Fang Yuan were not few in her memory.

The battle lasted for a while, earth chief myriad beast king was roaring again and again, its energy was consumed by the wolf groups and it could no longer display its fierce might...

Large numbers of earth chief beasts jumped out of the underground and joined the battle.

Fang Yuan chuckled indifferently, commanding the wolves with ease as he had already expected this.

The outcome of this large battle was foreordained from the start. How could a myriad beast scale earth chief beast group be his match?

Such a large battle covered a range of a thousand li, but this was ingeniously divided into dozens of sections of battle circles by Fang Yuan; using the weak wolf groups to surround and then using the strong and vigorous mutated beasts to form an arrow head that charged forward.

The first section of the battle circles was taken down by the wolf group, as they joined with the next group to destroy the second section, and the third section; the dominance accumulated and the scales of victory were inclining more and more towards Fang Yuan. Finally, the wolf group's annexing speed increased faster and faster till they butchered earth chief myriad beast king.

"This kid's enslavement path cultivation is indeed not ordinary. Although his commanding ability is exquisite and bold, using sharp and mild tactics together, he is still far away from grandmaster level attainment." Mo Yao thought inwardly.

Gu Masters nurtured, used, and refined; no matter which aspect, they were all very profound and deep.

Gu Masters might be using the same Gu worms, but some Gu Masters' performance would be extremely outstanding to the point that it could be called an art. These people were known as masters!

Master could be discovered but not sought, and could not be cultivated just by investing resources. Not only did it require innate talent, the Gu Master also needed to have capability.

But above master was grandmaster.

Comparing master and grandmaster was like comparing grass and tree. Besides talent, aptitude and resources, grandmaster attainment also required fortuitous opportunities and comprehension.

As long as one reached grandmaster level, they could learn about any path using their own as a foundation, they could understand about yin-yang and heaven and earth, they could learn about the profoundness of the universe, surpassing the mortal realm and become immortals among immortals, sages among sages.

Mo Yao was a refinement path grandmaster, although she had perished, her broad vision still existed.

She had seen countless masters in her life; the main reason why she felt Fang Yuan's attainment was impressive was because of his young age.

Not long later, earth chief myriad beast king fell down loudly, having died due to the heavy injuries.

Blood flowed out rapidly and soon formed into a pool of blood beside it.

Fang Yuan descended and personally skinned it, immediately started refining Gu next to the blood pool with wolf groups surrounding him.

Mo Yao's modified earth chief zombie Gu required the freshest flesh, with the flesh of earth chief myriad beast king being the best, thousand beast king being the second best and hundred beast king being the last option.

Thus, Fang Yuan moved out in a large scale and personally killed the earth chief myriad beast king.

The Gu refinement continued for three days and three nights before succeeding perfectly.

After Fang Yuan reached his goal, he dismissed the majority of the wolf groups to hunt in the wild, only taking the elite mutated beasts with him as he returned back to sacred palace without stopping.

The battlefield fell into deathly stillness; suddenly, a bloody person made his way out of a hill-sized blood forest wolf corpse.

The bloody person swayed unstably as he moved and had only walked a few steps before falling down to the ground.

He gasped roughly, an incredulous look in his eyes as he muttered: "I am still alive?"

He vigorously rubbed his face, revealing his appearance.

It was none other than Ma Hong Yun.

After he had been knocked unconscious by Jiang Dong, he had remained down on the ground.

That old earth chief beast king ignored him and chased after Jiang Dong.

But soon after, the wolf group engulfed the area and slaughtered all living beings, and Ma Hong Yun ended up in a wolf's mouth.

If it had been an ordinary wolf like turtleback wolf, water wolf or wind wolf, Ma Hong Yun would already have been torn into pieces and would be lying in the wolf's stomach.

Fortunately, it was the hill-sized blood forest wolf that had eaten him.

This wolf opened up its large mouth and with one lap of its tongue, directly licked the ground within a hundred steps. Ma Hong Yun along with the old earth chief beast king's corpse went down into the blood forest wolf's stomach.

If it had continued normally, Ma Hong Yun would already have been digested by the blood forest wolf sooner or later and turned into a pile of wolf faeces.

But in the following battle with the earth chief beast group, this blood forest wolf was attacked from all around and died on the battlefield; its chest and belly was torn open which allowed air to flow in.

Ma Hong Yun dizzily woke up and hurriedly drilled his way out. At this time, the battle had already ended and the battlefield was covered with beast corpses. Occasionally, some wild beasts that were at their final moments would gasp for air, emphasizing the deathly stillness in the surrounding.

After Ma Hong Yun breathed enough, his strength started to gradually recover and the thick bloody odor assailed his nose.

He realized the situation was anything but reassuring: "I need to leave this place quickly, wild beasts will be attracted by the odor of the blood not long later."

Ma Hong Yun had been born and raised in Northern Plains, this piece of common sense survival knowledge was already deeply ingrained in his bones.

He immediately stood up, made sure of the direction towards sacred palace and quickly set off.

But he had just taken a few steps when he stopped.

His sight was attracted by a Gu worm.

This was a wild Gu on the corpse of an earth chief beast.

The earth chief beast had died, the wild Gu on it should have perished or flown away, but this wild Gu was unexpectedly held back by a fractured bone and could not fly away.

"This should be a rank two... something something Gu." Ma Hong Yun could not remember it clearly, but it did not hinder him from knowing the value of this Gu.

"Good Gu worm, this is a good Gu worm, after getting it, even if I can't use it for myself, I can sell it for a lot of primeval stones."

Ma Hong Yun felt a rush of excitement and immediately walked over, easily grabbing the Gu worm.

Chapter 573: Human Experimentation

The silver light shone on the garden where the plants were swaying gently.

In a pavilion, Fang Yuan was fiddling with earth chief zombie Gu.

This Gu's shape appeared like an earthworm, bright yellow in color and was the size of an infant's forearm. Right now, it was twining around Fang Yuan's fingers like a wriggling snake.

Through Mo Yao's improved recipe and the flesh of earth chief myriad beast king's corpse, its refinement was successful.

But Fang Yuan had not used it.

He was cautious in nature, this earth chief zombie Gu was refined from a modified recipe, what would he do if there was a problem?

Although he had reached a compromise with Mo Yao's will, Mo Yao was a fairy of the righteous path's Spirit Affinity House as well as a refinement path grandmaster; he could not put his guard down.

'But grandmasters are truly worthy of their name, my refinement path attainment has already reached the master realm, but when compared to Mo Yao, I am young like a child.'

Recalling the process of refining earth chief zombie Gu, Fang Yuan was still feeling moved.

During the whole Gu refinement process, Mo Yao only spoke three sentences, but they were the crucial guides, the vital finishing touches. Fang Yuan was able to gain a lot of insight from them.

He, however, did not know Mo Yao was also inwardly moved at this moment.

'Double master attainment... I had not expected this kid to not only be an enslavement path master but also refinement path master. Double master attainment at such a young age, such aptitude and talent are rare even in my memory. No wonder he has such grand ambitions of wanting to rise to the realm of venerable, equal to Thieving Heaven, Paradise Earth, Giant Sun....'

'It is also natural to be arrogant and conceited after getting success at this young age.' Mo Yao still scoffed at Fang Yuan's 'goal' of being equal to venerables, but she understood.

'Becoming a master can't be done with just talent and aptitude, it also requires sufficient resources and even guidance from great teachers. It seems this kid's background is quite deep.'

Previously, Mo Yao already knew the secret of Fang Yuan possessing Hu Immortal blessed land. Now, with the intel of 'double master attainment', she sensed the deep origin of Fang Yuan.

"Lord Wolf King, Ge tribe's and Chang tribe's leaders have come forward to have an audience." Right at this time, a servant reported from outside the door.

Fang Yuan collected his thoughts, these two had been called by him. He indifferently said: "Let them in."

"Yes." The servant respectfully retreated.

Not long later, two people came forward and kneeled, kowtowing three times to pay their respects, an extremely respectful and fearful expression could be seen on their faces.

Going through the baptism of Imperial Court contest and being at a high position with no lack of resources, under the shade of a large tree like Wolf King, Ge Guang and Chang Ji You were already rank four Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan glanced and asked without allowing them to rise: "Have you completed the things I told you a few days ago?"

After Fang Yuan succeeded in his expedition and returned to the sacred palace, he gave an order to the two tribe leaders to gather all their tribe's Gu Masters to clean up the battlefield.

"As per Lord Wolf King's words, the battlefield has been cleaned up, altogether..." Ge Guang was about to report the gains, but was interrupted by Fang Yuan.

He did not care about these battle spoils, asking: "How many Gu Masters did you arrest?"

Ge Guang did not reply this time, instead signalled Chang Ji You who was at the side, with his eyes.

Everyone knew Chang Ji You was Chang Shan Yin's own son, and after Fang Yuan took control of Chang tribe, he appointed Chang Ji You as the tribe leader.

Ge Guang was letting Chang Ji You reply to Fang Yuan's question, in light of this relation and to express his goodwill to Chang Ji You.

Chang Ji You spoke with a respectful expression, his gaze revealing a crazed fanatical worship: "People's hearts are unfathomable with insatiable greed. Despite lord father's public announcement, there were still many Gu Masters who sneaked into the battlefield to steal beast corpses or wild Gu. Over these few days, I and tribe leader Ge Guang combined our strength and were able to arrest over one hundred and eighty Gu Masters who are locked up in the prison now. But there were still many crafty and treacherous scoundrels who took advantage of when we were not on guard to sneak in and make some free gains. I have interrogated the prisoners and have much intel on them already. As long as father commands, I will definitely spare no efforts to lock up all these escapees!"

Although Chang Ji You was kneeling on the ground, his upper body was upright as he spoke in an unafraid tone; his aquiline nose, dark brows, broad back and thin waist gave him a heroic aura.

Fang Yuan smiled, he had no interest in capturing these escapees: "The battlefield is vast and is not restricted with doors or obstacles, you have already done great by capturing so many Gu Masters. As for the others, it is their skill that they were able to escape, there is no need to chase after them. You can leave now, and bring those detained captives here."

"Yes, this subordinate (this child) heeds your command!"

Not long later, the two escorted close to two hundred captives to Fang Yuan.

With Fang Yuan's command, a large hall had been created to lock up these Gu Masters.

"You guys go out and close the door, guard the entrance and don't let any outsiders enter within a hundred steps. If some experts arrive, inform me in advance." Fang Yuan dismissed everyone, the hall now only had him and the captives.

The door was locked and as no lanterns had been lit, the hall sank into darkness.

This no doubt increased the unease and anxiety in the captives' hearts.

"Lord Wolf King, what are you intending to do by capturing us? I am a Hei tribesman and talking of relation... Hei Lou Lan is my older cousin!" Among the captives a young Gu Master shouted.

Fang Yuan sneered and with a snap of his fingers, activated a Gu.

Tch. A soft sound was heard and the young Gu Master's head burst out like a watermelon, spurting out white brain matter.

A huge clamor instantly occurred as the captives were terrified and fell into panic.

Soon, someone took the lead and the others also followed suit, kneeling down one after another.

"Lord Wolf King, I deserve death!"

"I shouldn't have gone to steal lord's battle spoils, my conscience was blinded!"

"Lord, please forgive us, lord have mercy..."

Fang Yuan had a terrifying reputation, and now he casually killed without even saying a word.

None of these Gu Masters were experts, most having only rank one or rank two cultivation. Their background was not good and they were unable to enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, facing a rank five peak stage expert like Fang Yuan and trying to resist would only be looking for death, so they could only ask for forgiveness.

"Noisy". Fang Yuan shouted in a soft voice, but his voice echoing in the hall.

He casually waved his hand, killing the person that was begging in the most mournful voice, even though they were quite far apart.

"I will kill anyone who dares to make more noise." Fang Yuan indifferently said, his voice was not loud but it lingered in the captives' ears.

The whole hall instantly fell into deathly silence out of fear; even the sound of a pin dropping could be heard.

Fang Yuan only then felt satisfied and asked Mo Yao's will in his mind: "Now how should I experiment?"

Mo Yao chuckled: "This is easy, little brother just needs to arrange Gu worms according to my instructions."

She directly addressed Fang Yuan as 'little brother, giving a feeling of intimacy. Fang Yuan snorted inwardly, but did not retort and followed Mo Yao's instructions.

Every time Mo Yao notified, Fang Yuan would respond by sending out a Gu worm.

These Gu worms were the Gu worms to form six arm heavenly zombie king killer move; earth chief zombie Gu, asura zombie Gu, heavenly demon zombie Gu and so on. Some were thrown towards the roof and some were placed in the corners.

As the Gu worms made an arc through the air, trails of colorful light appeared in the captives' eyes.

These people were very anxious, but they did not dare to ask anything. They stood on their spots without even daring to move a little just like little whelps.

The headless corpses of the two captives Fang Yuan had killed were still around them, the odor of blood gradually pervaded the hall as the blood flowed out of the severed necks.

After arranging these Gu worms to their spots, Fang Yuan successively started to pour primeval essence into them according to Mo Yao's instructions.

This process of pouring the primeval essence was quite specific; one moment, he had to choose a Gu worm in the southeast and the very next moment, it would be northwest, and suddenly, it would be the Gu worms to the sides. The main Gu at times, and the supporting Gu worms at times.

Even Fang Yuan felt baffled and had inwardly put up his guard.

When all the Gu worms were activated, the light from them gradually linked together and soon formed a pale yellow light house that covered the hall, including all the captives within.

"This is?!" Fang Yuan's thoughts shook and his pupils widened.

Mo Yao's will softly smiled as she explained: "This is a Gu house."

Fang Yuan involuntarily blurted out: "Is the essence of this six arm heavenly zombie king a Gu house?"

Mo Yao chuckled: "Foolish kid, could it be that you don't know the true nature of a Gu house is a killer move? ... Six arm heavenly zombie king is a killer move, a Gu house is also a killer move, their essence is the same, so they naturally can be mutually switched."

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed brightly as he sensed the unspoken implication of Mo Yao's words, immediately asking: "From your words, couldn't all killer moves turn into Gu houses?"

"Of course." Mo Yao unhesitatingly replied, "Man is the spirit of all living beings while Gu is the essence of the world, carrier of the Great Dao. A Gu worm has one ability. What is a killer move? It is an assembly of different Gu worms stacking their abilities; it can raise the strength of one ability to a very high level or produce multiple abilities which can handle different aspects."

Mo Yao did not explain further, whether Fang Yuan could have some comprehension from this was his own matter.

Fang Yuan stared blankly, inspirations started flashing incessantly in his mind!

Mo Yao's words seemed to pierce through a paper window, allowing his insight to rise to a whole new height.

"Right! A Gu house's essence is a killer move which has solidified. For example, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building can be compared with Water Pavilion. The former covers the Imperial Court, influences northern plains, plunders resources and holds inheritances. The latter can be concealed, and has the ability of defense and storage. These functions were not provided by just a single Gu worm, but were the result of Gu Masters assembling these Gu worms."

"From another perspective, a Gu house is just one form of manifestation of a killer move. Since six arm heavenly zombie king can only take effect on me, one person, why can it not form into a Gu house and simultaneously take effect on many people?"

At this thought, Fang Yuan looked ahead.

In the Gu house, those Gu Master captives' bodies were already beginning to show changes.

"Wha... what is happening to me?!" Everyone was shouting in fright as they saw golden scales growing out rapidly on their skin.

"Ahhh, it is painful, it is painful!""It itches, it is too itchy, I can't endure this, just kill me!" Soon, they fell down to the ground one after another; some madly grabbed their skin and tore off their clothes, while others bent their body like shrimps, covering their chest tightly as blood flowed out of their mouth and nose.

"This, what is this thing? Why is there a monstrous arm growing out of my back!" Not long later, the alarmed screams reached the peak, the soundwaves even shaking the roof.

All sorts of arms started growing one after another; some were dark green, some dark purple, some yellow, and their thicknesses were also different, the deformities looking very unsightly.

But Fang Yuan had never bothered with these minor details to external appearance, his eyes slightly squinted when he felt the dangerous aura the Gu Masters started releasing; he felt very happy as well as apprehensive —

"Mo Yao's understanding of killer moves is extremely profound. But why do others have no such comprehension? Is it because most Gu Masters and even Gu Immortals don't have the skill to casually transform killer moves into Gu houses? Refinement path grandmaster... this is truly a terrifying realm!"

Chapter 574: Mo Yao’s weakness

In the deeply secluded hall, only Fang Yuan was standing.

There was a deathly silence.

The faint yellow light merged into one, forming the shape of a Gu house, inside the house of light was a floor of corpses.

Almost two hundred Gu Masters died a terrible death.

Among these corpses, some had scales on their bodies, some were hard as steel, some grew weird limbs and had a grimacing expression, some self-detonated and caused their broken limbs to fly all over the place.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim, he questioned Mo Yao in his mind: "This is the killer move that you thought of?"

Mo Yao replied with unphased confidence: "These Gu Masters were certainly going to die. Six arm heavenly zombie king is a strength path killer move, it has high requirements towards the body. Now it seems, even with your strength path foundation, it is unable to endure such an intense move."

Fang Yuan scoffed, expressing his unhappiness: "This is your explanation? You think I could not tell? This killer move has so many flaws, initially fifty to sixty people died, midway about a hundred had died, and towards the end we were only left with six to seven Gu Masters. There are at least seventeen flaws! Do not forget that we have an agreement."

"Hehehe." Mo Yao chuckled, she felt nothing from being threatened, as she replied: "Little brother, don't be so rash, six arm heavenly zombie king has only been created roughly, it is normal to have flaws. As we continue to improve on it, it will eventually meet our expectations."

She replied to Fang Yuan as she thought: "This lad is not simple, he could detect seventeen flaws... with his refinement master attainment, he should only be able to find eleven at most, it seems that his strength path attainment has also reached the edge of master level."

Mo Yao did not know that Fang Yuan was playing mind games here.

"I could only see seven flaws, I purposely added ten in order to probe her, it seems that this killer move's flaws are more than just seventeen." Fang Yuan assessed in his mind.

Mo Yao was testing out his level of attainment, but Fang Yuan was also probing her foundation as well.

Six arm heavenly zombie king was full of flaws, all of the Gu Masters used for the experiment were dead, but Fang Yuan was happy instead of being worried.

"Logically speaking, Mo Yao has refinement grandmaster attainment, even if it is a roughly made killer move, there cannot be so many flaws! But while Mo Yao is indeed a refinement grandmaster, this is only a part of her will that she left behind..."

Fang Yuan's compromise was real, but he had never given up on his goal to get rid of Mo Yao's will.

Through his current probing, he found out one weakness of Mo Yao's will.

"Although I am not familiar with wisdom path, I had spent a great fortune and bought much costly information from treasure yellow heaven, they are valuable knowledge."

"Wisdom path seeks the path of knowledge, it is split into 'thought, 'will', and 'emotion'. Thought is the foundation, when a person thinks, thoughts are created. When many thoughts are gathered, will is formed. With many wills intertwined, emotions would form. Thoughts are like weeds, they can be easily created or destroyed, will can be everchanging, firm as steel, empty like vacuum, or fierce like fire... As for emotions, they are like water, a small stream when thin, but cannot be cut easily or steered by reason. When deep, they will be like the sea, having great control and power over oneself."

"Out of these three, emotion is the hardest to get rid of, while thoughts are most easily destroyed and created. I should be glad that what is inside my mind now is Mo Yao's will and not Mo Yao's emotions."

"When a person thinks, thoughts are created. When thoughts collide, they either get destroyed or fuse. The eventual thought would be the result obtained from thinking. Then what about a portion of a person's will? Hehehe."

Fang Yuan thought of the brilliant part and he snickered in his heart continuously.

Wills do not form by just gathering randomly scattered thoughts together. But will is truly the linking together of countless thoughts.

When a will thinks about a question, it will use its own thoughts to fuse and create new thoughts, getting the results of their thinking.

"Mo Yao is a refinement grandmaster, her will also inherited her grandmaster attainment, but the flaws created in thinking about six arm heavenly zombie king were not due to her limited abilities, but because she did not dare to think too deeply as she had to worry about her own safety."

By now, Fang Yuan had discovered Mo Yao's weakness!

A living person would feel weakness in their body if they thought about things non-stop, not to mention a simple will?

The more a will thinks, the more damaged they would get, and the weaker they would be.

If Mo Yao was alive, the expenditure that her will incurs would be replenished by her main body. But now — Mo Yao was already dead!

Why did her will sleep inside Water Pavilion, only awakening when Fang Yuan entered?

That was because her will could not stay awake all the time, one thinks extensively when they are awake, the more she thought the weaker her will would be, and the faster it would perish.

Look at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, this majestic rank eight Immortal Gu house, containing Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's will.

Even for someone as strong as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, the will that he left behind was also slumbering!

Be it Giant Sun's will or Mo Yao's will, they were without a power source, they could not be replenished and could only weaken as time passed.

"While my wisdom path attainment is low, I have the greatest advantage in that I am alive! At this point, I cannot contest with Mo Yao's will, but as long as I have enough time to stall it out, I will definitely win."

After pondering to this point, Fang Yuan stopped this train of thought.

After all, Mo Yao's will was inside his mind. Reflecting for overly long would create more thoughts, although he could use space thought Gu to hide them, there was no guarantee that Mo Yao would not find a way around it.

"Sigh..."

In the grand hall, Fang Yuan's sigh could be heard.

Mo Yao was a huge burden, Fang Yuan had to be wary all the time when he thinks.

Originally, getting into Imperial Court blessed land and taking Immortal Gu Landscape As Before was already taxing on him, having to make so many considerations. Coupled with such a huge enemy now lurking inside his brain, Fang Yuan had to be very careful of the danger while attempting to solve it, every time he thought about a problem, he would have to mix in some random thoughts to conceal his intentions.

This kind of thinking would be easily achieved in the past if his heart was calm. But now, Fang Yuan felt that it was very taxing, he felt a strong mental fatigue.

Mo Yao's will heard this sigh and misunderstood Fang Yuan, consoling: "Hehehe, little brother, you are so young, but already so hardworking, why are you sighing? I have revised the killer move, you need to change six Gu worms and add in three more."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's brows rose, he said expressionlessly: "I am listening."

Mo Yao told him the details.

Fang Yuan had Hu Immortal blessed land in his possession, it was not a problem to connect to treasure yellow heaven and exchange for a few mortal Gu.

At the same time, Fang Yuan instructed Ge Guang and Chang Ji You to secretly bring captured Gu Masters into the hall.

Three days later, another round of human experimentation begun.

The experiment's result was better than earlier, but there were still flaws.

Mo Yao summed up the results and gave another revised suggestion.

Fang Yuan acted accordingly, he showed no impatience even after many rounds. He knew clearly: Mo Yao's will had refinement grandmaster attainment, but the more she thought, the weaker she would be, the rounds of experiments were so that they could replace the strain on her thoughts by using test subjects.

But even so, Mo Yao's will had to think of the revision herself. When she thinks about this, thoughts would generate!

The more she does this, the weaker her will would be.

Fang Yuan did not intend to alarm her, he was prepared for a drawn out battle.

After half a month, during the fifteenth experiment.

In the hall, corpses were scattered everywhere.

Fang Yuan kept the dozens of Gu worms used for six arm heavenly zombie king, looking around and giving a satisfied nod.

The test subjects had low cultivation level, they could not endure such a strong killer move like six arm heavenly zombie king, they were sure to die.

But how they died, and what happened to them after they died was the important thing.

Right now, among these corpses, some has turned into zombies, some had yellow scales, some had six arms on their backs, some had sharp spiky scales, some had thick arms with bulging muscles, some had pitch-black claws on their hands, created by their sharp nails.

"Six arm heavenly zombie king uses borrow strength Gu as the core, and the six flying zombie Gu as the foundation, with eighteen Gu as the complements. Strictly speaking, this is a transformation path killer move, gathering the zombie energy to turn a person into a flying zombie. That way, the Gu Master's body becomes more than ten times as strong, and can hold even greater strength." Fang Yuan spoke slowly, concluding his gains from these previous days.

"But precisely because of this, the zombie energy is extremely dense and the backlash of this killer move is very severe. Even if we had three life force type Gu among the complementing Gu worms, we can only sustain the killer move for seven minutes. That's about it, right?" Fang Yuan asked Mo Yao's will in his mind.

Mo Yao laughed: "Little brother makes much sense, that is true indeed. Using borrow strength Gu to borrow the strength of the natural phenomena in heaven and earth, but even a rank five strength path expert cannot use it casually. Thus, I thought of using a zombie body as the strength of a zombie body surpasses living flesh, it has great regenerative abilities and complements borrow strength Gu really well."

"But Gu Masters are alive, while zombie energy is the power of the dead, the longer you maintain the six arm heavenly zombie king transformation, the more zombie energy would be in your body, and when it devours your lifeforce, you will turn into a zombie completely, unable to change back. That is the backlash of this killer move."

"Sigh, life force and death energy, they are entirely distinct from each other and like archenemies. The fusion of life and death is also an age old question, it is out of my capabilities. It was my limit to place three life force boosting Gu worms in the killer move. If we put more of these Gu, it will disrupt the zombie energy and the killer move's power will fall, or even completely collapse. If we use too few of them, the time you can use this transformation will shrink, and it will turn into an impractical move."

Fang Yuan heard this and nodded on the surface, expressing his agreement, but he was chuckling in his heart.

These words from Mo Yao were a suspicious change in topic.

The fusion of life and death was indeed an age old question, there had never been a case of a person being simultaneously dead and alive, the two could not co-exist.

But Mo Yao was a refinement grandmaster, could she not think of any other killer moves?

Why must she use six arm heavenly zombie king? That was because this could greatly reduce the thinking she had to do, since Fang Yuan provided the base of the killer move 'four arm wind king', she just had to improve on it.

Fang Yuan was almost certain, with her grandmaster attainment, Mo Yao could easily start all over again and think of a brand new killer move.

"Mo Yao is a variant human, she is an inkman. As someone of a different race, she definitely has a different standpoint. These days, we used up to a thousand Gu Masters to experiment, she is a righteous path person, the fairy of Spirit Affinity House, but she watched coldly by the side. Her lover is the great Sword Immortal Bo Qing, it seems that within her affection, there was also the element of being attracted to the strong?"

Bo Qing was the 'pseudo-Immortal Venerable who split the five regions with his sword', compared to him, Fang Yuan was only a mortal, in Mo Yao's heart, was he about the same as those test subjects who died?

"Thus, in this world, one has to depend on themselves. Only you yourself are the most reliable person." Fang Yuan sneered in his heart, but he did not point it out, he asked Mo Yao instead: "So, has the killer move six arm heavenly zombie king been completed?"

Mo Yao shook her head: "Not yet, we only experimented on low rank Gu Masters, we still need high rank Gu Masters, preferably rank five, if they are a strength path rank five, that would be the best."

"Rank five strength path?" Fang Yuan frowned, other than himself, there was nobody he knew who met the criteria.

Fang Yuan shook his head, he decided to put this matter aside: "No rush, I have already obtained the materials for ink transformation. It is time to explore Eighty-Eight True Yang Building again!"

Chapter 575: Entering True Yang Building again

Fang Yuan entered the central control room once again.

As the name implied, the central control room was the important control center of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The secret room was round and its walls were flickering with starlight, with a white jade round table at the center. There was an exquisite model of the whole Imperial Court blessed land on the round table, just like a military sand table.

Not only did it depict mountains and rivers and the sacred palace at the center, even the small towers in the blessed land were clearly visible.

"I have returned once again." In Fang Yuan's mind, Mo Yao's will sighed with deep emotions.

Fang Yuan ignored her and looked towards the white jade round table.

He had first used the guest token to enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, then passed with high grade evaluation which allowed him to enter the treasure room. He then refined the guest halt stele and found the glass owner token, using it, he then entered the central control room.

But because of Di Qiu inheritance, he chose to momentarily halt his plans for Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, eventually refining calamity beckoning Gu.

All in all, Di Qiu inheritance provided both benefits and harm to Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan was able to obtain an Immortal Gu, but its ability was quite unique in that it harmed oneself to benefit others.

And then there was Mo Yao's will which had sneaked into his mind; Fang Yuan could not get rid of it and as such the internal pressure on him was huge. But undeniably, the pointers given by Mo Yao's will reaped him much gains, not mentioning the insights regarding refinement path, just the six arm heavenly zombie king and ink transformation killer moves along with the improved earth chief zombie Gu recipe were extremely valuable!

Besides these, there was also an enormous benefit; Mo Yao's will would be of huge help to Fang Yuan's plans in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

After all, Mo Yao was a refinement path grandmaster who had researched Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in-depth. She was a legendary character who, back then, had infiltrated into Imperial Court blessed land and created a loophole where she set up Di Qiu inheritance!

Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories along with the video of the central continent Gu Immortals attacking Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he also had first hand information from Lang Ya land spirit and now, a great assistant was with him in the form of Mo Yao's will.

As such, he was fully confident in this trip.

But shortly after, his gaze paused as he let out a surprised gasp.

He clearly remembered that the sand table on the round table had been covered with a layer of sticky black liquid and the black liquid had formed into a whirlpool which then slowly entered towards a hole in the sand table.

This hole was none other than the location of Di Qiu inheritance.

But now, there was no trace of the black liquid on the sand table and the location of the Di Qiu inheritance was also completely restored in the sand table, with no trace of any hole.

This sight was like a heavy punch to Fang Yuan's confidence.

His mind was jolted and as he was about to make guesses, Mo Yao's will chuckled, already knowing his intent: "If there are gains, there will be losses as well. Little brother, you have already taken Di Qiu inheritance, and with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's might, it was bound to have fixed that flaw; the cave in Di Qiu inheritance exists no longer and a small tower should have been reinstated there."

"Without the loophole, how can I refine the glass owner token into one-edge owner token?" Fang Yuan asked for advice.

"If there is no loophole, then just create a new one." Mo Yao proudly smiled, "Why did I impart you the refinement path killer move ink transformation? You should have already guessed it, the black liquid covering the sand table you saw back then was caused by ink transformation killer move."

"If there is no loophole, make a new one?" Mo Yao's words revealed the bearings of a refinement path grandmaster, causing Fang Yuan to raise his brows.

Although it sounded easy from her words, how should he create the loophole?

At least, Fang Yuan who was a refinement path master did not have such ability.

Mo Yao continued: "The loophole cannot be casually created. Carelessly doing it will only awaken the slumbering Giant Sun's will. If his will awakens, then we will face a tragic end. Fortunately, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has gone through many changes, it is already no longer as perfect as before, time has created all kinds of blemishes in it; back then, I chose the Di Qiu location because the blemish in it was the largest."

"So it was like that." Fang Yuan nodded, inwardly happy.

Mo Yao's will was like a water without a source, if they wanted to look for the blemishes and the loopholes, it would require large amounts of thinking, and this would cause her will to be greatly exhausted.

But Mo Yao did not satisfy Fang Yuan's intention and instead said: "Little brother, use your mind to explore the sand table according to my instructions, I will tell you the secrets of the workings of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and help you find the blemishes."

"Okay." Fang Yuan's gaze flashed.

This action of Mo Yao was not out of his expectation.

She cherished her existence, but it was okay that she was not thinking. Fang Yuan could use this chance to learn from her and increase his understanding of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The marvels of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building were extraordinary; as Fang Yuan entered the sand table with his mind, he felt like he was a small boat on an ocean, only sensing its limitless and unfathomable vastness. Every corner and side of it was a lesson to be learned and pondered upon.

He instantly felt that he was a minute existence and gasped in amazement.

According to Mo Yao's directions, Fang Yuan found a total of fifty-four blemishes, and thirteen blemishes among them were relatively larger, forming into flaws that were comparable to the Di Qiu location before.

This result made Mo Yao sigh: "So many years have gone by and even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building cannot escape the damage from the river of time. Thinking of back then, I could only find thirty-eight blemishes with only six that had formed into flaws."

Pausing for a moment, she then continued to give directions to Fang Yuan: "Little brother, now you can use the killer move ink transformation to refine these several flaws."

Fang Yuan followed her words and with frequent shifting of his mind, over eight hundred Gu flew out of his aperture.

There were Gu worms from rank one to rank five of metal, wood, water, earth, rule, soul, blood and other paths, among these dark path was of primary importance.

Although they were all mortal Gu, but for ten or so Gu worms among them, some were already extinct during Medieval Antiquity Era and some even went as far back as Remote Antiquity Era. Thus, they were extremely rare and were completely extinct from the five regions, with only some Gu Immortals having them in their collections.

Fang Yuan had to spend a considerable amount for these Gu worms, spending at least one and a half immortal essence stones.

Immortal essence stones were extremely valuable and could directly replenish a Gu Immortal's immortal essence and help them cultivate. At the same time, they were also a currency used by Gu Immortals.

Even during Fang Yuan's peak period in his previous life, he had only been able to collect just over sixty immortal essence stones.

In this life, he gained profits from risk, and since obtaining Hu Immortal blessed land, his highest amount of savings was twelve immortal essence stones.

Now, he only had two immortal essence stones left.

There was nothing he could do about it, too many fields required the use of immortal essence stones.

Purchasing wolf groups, gathering the intel on wisdom path, purchasing Gu worms and so on, all required immortal essence stones.

Close to a thousand Gu worms fluttered about in the air, like a light drizzle.

Fang Yuan put all his concentration in commanding and arranging these Gu worms and when the time was ripe, he shouted softly: "Ink transformation!"

The Gu worms turned into a dark cloud and rain started falling down from the cloud and made pitter-patter sounds as they hit the sand table, turning into drops of inky liquid.

The ink drops started to add up slowly and covered the whole sand table.

Fang Yuan's concentration was gathered towards a specific flaw, urging the inky liquid to flow towards the flaw.

The primeval essence of a rank five peak stage aperture rapidly decreased, and the inky liquid was also exhausted by over half before it was able to break through a layer of indistinct obstruction and formed into a whirlpool, slowly pouring into the hole in the sand table.

At this scene, Mo Yao spoke: "Throw in your glass owner token."

Fang Yuan did as told and threw in the glass owner token.

The glass owner token sank into the inky whirlpool with no trace to be seen, the inky liquid also started being consumed even more rapidly. After about an hour, the dark cloud was the first to dissipate. After four hours, the inky liquid disappeared completely, and a completely new owner token slowly flew out of the hole.

Fang Yuan grabbed this owner token that had already changed its appearance. On the edge of the previous surface, a sharp protrusion appeared like a horn.

"One-edge owner token, sure enough fits its name." Fang Yuan mumbled.

"In Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, after a descendant of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable passes a floor, the owner token will advance into one-edge owner token and be able to grasp control of a floor. At the same time, the descendant can enter the treasure room and take a treasure within, without the need to exchange. If the descendant can pass through ten floors, the owner token will become a ten-edges owner token which allows the descendant to retrieve a Giant Sun inheritance from the treasure room." Mo Yao introduced.

"Giant Sun inheritance?" Fang Yuan's heart thumped in excitement.

Mo Yao continued: "Right, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made arrangements for his descendants, arranged the rules of the Imperial Court contest, set up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and left behind eighty-eight inheritances in it. An Immortal Venerable's inheritance is naturally not a small thing. But in history, the Imperial Court winners who were able to pass ten floors were extremely few. When I was alive, there were still fifty-three inheritances left out of eighty eight, I am not sure how many remain now."

"Hehehe, speaking of this, even I am envious of your luck. There are altogether thirteen flaws we found. Every flaw after the ink transformation can advance the owner token by one edge. If you can use them all, you will obtain a thirteen-edges owner token and can totally take a Giant Sun inheritance! Sigh, it is not like back then, when there only were six flaws."

When Fang Yuan heard this, his fiery heart felt like it was doused with a basin of cold water, he bitterly laughly: "Using all the flaws? I won't conceal it from you, I only have two immortal essence stones now, I can only support one more ink transformation killer move."

"Oh, it was like that?" Mo Yao's gaze flashed.

While Fang Yuan was probing her, she was also probing Fang Yuan.

Immortal essence stones were one of the important standards of evaluating Gu Immortals. Fang Yuan might still be a mortal but with Hu Immortal blessed land, he was already treated as half an immortal in Mo Yao's heart.

"So this kid only has two Immortal essence stones? Are his words true or a lie?...It should be the truth. The temptations of Giant Sun's inheritance is not something normal people can resist. He is a refinement path master, he naturally knows the more flaws he refines and the higher grade his owner token is, the more convenient it will be for his plans towards Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. The most crucial point is I am hiding in his mind, it will be impossible for him to hide from me and secretly refine them."

"Now, he would ask for help from the forces behind him. Hmph, this brat conceals too deeply, he will have to reveal his background at that time, and I will be able to know a thing or two."

While thinking this, Mo Yao had a pleasant and benign expression as she gave an idea to Fang Yuan: "There is no need to hurry. Owner tokens can mutually annex each other. As long as you annex the current alliance leader Hei Lou Lan's owner token, who is to say you might not be able to gather ten edges?"

She indeed lived up to the name Mo Yao, knowing so many behind-the-scenes details.

Fang Yuan's gaze turned sharp and he intentionally said in a higher voice: "You want to make me go against Hei Lou Lan? Are you thinking of pushing me to my death? Although Hei Lou Lan is easy to deal with, the Hei tribe behind him is a super level force with many Gu Immortals looking after him!"

"Hey, you are an audacious lad, you can disguise your identity to infiltrate Imperial Court and yet you are afraid of mere Hei Lou Lan? Moreover, I did not say you have to kill him, you only need to take the owner token from his hands, that's all."

Fang Yuan's gaze changed: "Hei Lou Lan cannot be killed, killing him is like poking a hornet's nest, Hei tribe is not something I currently can provoke. But that owner token, he definitely treasures it as dearly as his life. Tell me, what should I do?"

'Can't provoke currently, isn't he saying it might be a different case in the future? This kid's ambition is truly big...' Mo Yao acutely sensed the key word in Fang Yuan's speech.

As for the problem Fang Yuan mentioned, she did not want to think too much, so she spread out her hands in Fang Yuan's mind: "How you take the owner token from him is your problem."

Chapter 576: Killer Move Reward

"Kill!"

"Damn it, another myriad beast king!"

In the huge desert, the heat in the air was distorting one's vision, as sandworms crawled out from underneath the golden sand terrain.

The Gu Masters were occupying the small area of a sand dune, desperately defending themselves.

This was Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's seventh floor, the eighty-ninth round.

Every round was a new area entirely, filled with all sorts of tests.

A sandworm myriad beast king entered the battle, causing ripples to form in the Gu Masters' defenses.

"Hold on, just forty-five minutes more and we will get through this round!" Sole Blade General Pan Ping shouted as he tried to boost morale.

He was a demonic Gu Master who had joined Hei tribe to become their external elder.

He had great battle strength, but this round was focused on defense.

It required the challengers to stay on the specified dune for twelve hours, facing the attacks of the sandworms in waves. Unlike Gu Immortals, mortals had limited strength alone, thus it was the best if more people challenged the round.

But Pan Ping's words had little effect.

By now, there were great losses to the Gu Masters, they were all tired and reaching their limits.

"The f*ck, another myriad beast king, how are we going to survive?" Big Beard wiped the blood and sweat off his face as he shouted.

Nobody knew his real name, because his beard was really thick, he was simply called 'Big Beard'.

In the earlier rounds, he had gotten through the sixth floor's eighteenth round, thus becoming a little famous from his previously unknown background.

He was originally a rank two Gu Master, as common as a pebble in the sacred palace, a true fodder, but because of the reward for clearing the round, he rose to rank three realm.

It was different when a Gu Master becomes rank three.

Rank two were common, rank three were rare, they were mostly elders.

When Big Beard became rank three, his situation improved, and his high quality primeval essence caused his battle strength to surge, allowing him to obtain more battle rewards. Not only this, many middle-sized tribes gave him an offer to join — small tribes could not afford to have an external elder while large tribes had no use for him.

"This is the eighty-ninth round, if we get through this, the reward will be shocking! People like us will not obtain it, but the reward for the mission would allow me to obtain two rank three Gu."

Big Beard thought about this and his heart was burning with desire, as he battled, he looked at the higher-ups on the peak of the dune.

It was them who sent out this mission, gathering a thousand Gu Masters to get through this difficult round.

The sandworm myriad beast king rushed into the defensive line, engaging in fierce combat. Golden light, rain of arrows, flames, all sorts of attacks were unleashed on the myriad beast king, but the beast king's body shone with a yellow luster, as its defense rose and blocked these attacks easily.

It growled continuously, as it whipped up a storm while barging into the people's territory.

Chang Biao stood on the mound, frowning.

"The situation is a little out of hand." He spoke: "This myriad beast king has a rank five golden armor Gu, if we allow it to continue rampaging, our defenses would crumble."

By now, this was the ninth myriad beast king.

According to the Gu worms on the myriad beast kings, their battle strengths differed. This myriad beast king was comparatively problematic because of the good quality defensive Gu in it, but it did not have a strong area of effect attack.

In such a situation, usually Gu Master experts would choose to strike it themselves as that is the only way to hurt it.

After all, soldiers fight soldiers and generals fight generals.

Chang Biao had this intention as well.

Ma Ying Jie who was standing beside him stood up and spoke: "Then I shall do it."

No one objected.

During the appearance of the myriad beast king, everyone took turns to strike, this was what they agreed on, and according to the order, it was Ma Ying Jie's turn.

He was the worthily famous Ma Ying Jie indeed, when he personally struck, he led the pegasus group and easily blocked the sandworm myriad beast king, stabilizing the situation.

"Young Ma Zun is really impressive." On the sand dune, everyone praised.

"Brother Chang, what do you think of Ma Ying Jie?" Pan Ping secretly asked by transmitting his voice.

Ma Ying Jie was once Ma tribe's young tribe leader, his teacher was Ma Zun and after Ma tribe failed, Hei Lou Lan forced them to submit causing the current Ma tribe to be weak, only being a mid-sized tribe.

Chang Biao knew what Pan Ping was saying, he wanted to recruit Ma Ying Jie into becoming a member of the Wolf Killing Alliance.

The Wolf Killing Alliance was a secret organisation to deal with Fang Yuan.

After Pan Ping's inheritance was snatched by Fang Yuan on Xing Jiu peak, he felt extreme hatred on the inside and wanted to take revenge.

Chang Biao had the grudge of Chang Shan Yin taking his wife, it was absolutely irreconcilable.

Fang Yuan had incredible power, he could contest with Hei Lou Lan. Even though Pan Ping and Chang Biao had great gains in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and obtained much rewards, both being rank four peak stage now, they had a low chance of success in dealing with Fang Yuan, thus they needed more help.

Seeing Chang Biao keeping silent, Pan Ping continued: "Ma tribe lost terribly because of Chang Shan Yin! Ma Ying Jie's teacher Ma Zun was killed by him as well, he and Chang Shan Yin have a huge grudge too."

But Chang Biao shook his head, transmitting: "No, Ma Ying Jie is a very determined person, but he is also a great leader. In my opinion, he has placed all his efforts on his tribe now, trying to revitalize the dying Ma tribe, he would not oppose the Wolf King if his intention is this. In fact, he might try to mend their relationship. Wolf King has a huge force, our biggest advantage is that we are a secret organisation, we cannot recruit people recklessly, if not, we will expose ourselves."

Pan Ping was not willing to give up, he continued urging: "Brother Chang, how can we as high achievers worry so much?! Chang Shan Yin is a scoundrel, he has his myriad wolves to defend him, in the future when we fight, our strength might be drained by the wolf group. Don't forget about this person's high attainment in strength path! Ma Ying Jie controls a horse group, he is called Little Ma Zun now, he has the talent to become an enslavement master, we need such experts to deal with the wolf group."

Chang Biao gave Pan Ping a look, feeling unhappy.

Pan Ping was a demonic Gu Master, he was called Sole Blade General, he acted without restraints and was daring and cruel. This was foolishness and rashness in Chang Biao's opinion, he could not achieve anything in life.

Actually, Pan Ping was unhappy too, he felt that Chang Biao was too restricted, he worried too much and was not a true hero.

This was the difference in their personality.

Chang Biao was good at enduring, back then when plotting against Chang Shan Yin, he used another person to achieve his aims. He also loved his reputation, after so many years, he did not dare to acknowledge his son Chang Ji You.

As for Pan Ping, from the Imperial Court contest when he challenged the armies and rushed forward in battle, one could see his personality.

But despite their differences, be it Pan Ping or Chang Biao, they could tolerate each other because they understood clearly that Wolf King was not someone they could deal with alone.

"Pan Ping is from the demonic path, how can he understand the thoughts of us righteous path characters! He wants to take in Ma Ying Jie? Hmph, wishful thinking! The moment we tell him about the Wolf Killing Alliance, we might get betrayed by him the next second, in order to appeal to the Wolf King. Sigh, how can I convince him?" Chang Biao sighed in his heart.

But he was very witty, he immediately had a plan.

He transmitted: "Brother Pan, Chang Shan Yin killed Ma Zun, but don't forget, who was the one who killed Ma Ying Jie's father?"

"Urgh..." Pan Ping was stunned, he went into a daze.

Ma Shang Feng was killed by Pan Ping during the chaotic battle in the end, because of that, he made a great merit and was given many rewards.

The battle merit back then became his biggest obstacle in taking revenge now, this was something Pan Ping did not expect.

But Pan Ping was an obstinate man, he said: "It is true that I killed his father, but that was due to the fight between two armies, we were fighting for our respective masters. Since Brother Chang thinks that Ma Ying Jie cares most about his tribe, I will believe this judgement. In that case, if we use this as the premise and assume that Wolf King is the biggest obstacle to Ma Ying Jie when he wants to restore his tribe, wouldn't that be the best?"

Once he said that, Chang Biao was stunned this time.

He gave Pan Ping a look, thinking: "Wise people might have a moment of folly, while foolish people might have a moment of brilliance, to think that this Pan Ping would have a smart rebuttal for once."

Immediately, his mind worked quickly as he assessed: "Indeed, there is a possibility of that. Ma Ying Jie's weakness is Ma tribe! But how can we plan this so that Ma Ying Jie would willingly join the Wolf Killing Alliance?"

Chang Biao thought of this and had an idea, remembering a small detail that he had heard of earlier.

His gaze turned to the left defensive line.

There was a young rank two Gu Master there.

"He is Ma Hong Yun, he was originally Ma Ying Jie's servant earlier, but now he is one of Ma Ying Jie's most trusted aides. Not long ago, Wolf King hunted the earth chief beast group and Ma Hong Yun managed to escape with his life, he obtained not a small amount of battle gains and contributed it to Ma tribe, causing Ma Ying Jie to reward him with three green copper relic Gu, for his loyalty. He even returned all the Gu worms that were contributed, allowing Ma Hong Yun to keep them.

"This lad's luck is not bad! He managed to leave before Chang tribe and Ge tribe Gu Masters entered the battlefield, the green copper relic Gu is of considerable value too, after Ma tribe became weak, their morale was low and Ma Ying Jie used the green copper relic Gu that he could not use to demonstrate how his men could be rewarded by the act of a good role model."

"Ma Hong Yun obtained the green copper relic Gu that he needed most, getting to rank two realm in one night, that speed is something not even I could compete with."

Chang Biao thought of this and sighed at the mysteries of fate.

Compared to Ma Hong Yun, Chang Biao had a much higher starting point, he had huge amounts of resources provided to him, but even so, Chang Biao took about ten times as long to advance to rank two.

After all, green copper relic Gu were natural Gu, they were rare and produced at random places, it was thanks to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building that Ma Ying Jie obtained them as a reward.

"This lad Ma Hong Yun had prospered due to Chang Shan Yin, earlier, Chang Shan Yin had ordered Chang tribe and Ge tribe to capture some of the Gu Masters who tried to take advantage of the situation, what will happen if I release this information?"

Chang Biao pondered.

"No... just Ma Hong Yun, who is a rank two Gu Master, would be an ant in Chang Shan Yin's eyes. He is still too weak, there is no point in reporting him. Furthermore, Ma Ying Jie will not deal with Chang Shan Yin just because of this tiny Ma Hong Yun. We should continuing planning and waiting for this..."

Forty-five minutes later, the sand dune erupted into cheers.

"Victory, victory!"

"It was not easy, we finally got through."

"I wonder what the reward for this round is?"

Many curious gazes landed on Chang Biao, Pan Ping, Ma Ying Jie and others.

After passing this round, Chang Biao and the others' apertures suddenly had many new Gu worms.

Among them was an east window Gu, storing information.

"Six arm heavenly zombie king?" Chang Biao, Pan Ping, and Ma Ying Jie checked this information and looked at each other.

They had differing expressions.

To think that the reward would be a strength path killer move, according to the description, this killer move's power was phenomenal!

Chapter 577: Young Master, save me...

Bam!

A silhouette flew out like lightning, six arms were like heavy cannons crushing a huge helmet crab to death.

At once, fresh blood spewed in this secret room as limbs flew everywhere.

"Hahaha." Pan Ping combed his messy hair, laughing loudly as he ignored the blood and carcasses on the ground.

"Awesome, amazing! This six arm heavenly zombie king killer move is really amazing! Using the zombie body to avoid requiring my insufficient background in strength path, thus even with my mild cultivation in strength path, I can still use it."

Pan Ping's eyes shone brilliantly as he talked to himself, pondering about the killer move.

He was born from the demonic path, he lacked resources and did not have enough creativity, thus he had never owned a killer move. But one did not need to know how to cook in order to eat, after roaming in northern plains for so many years, Pan Ping's vision had expanded and he knew that this killer move 'six arm heavenly zombie king' really had what was in the description — unparalleled strength!

"As long as I have this, my chances of dealing with Wolf King will be higher by ten percent! Wolf King has a strength path killer move, but so do I! Wolf King, don't be arrogant, one day, I will return all the humiliation that you inflicted onto me by tenfold!" Pan Ping gritted his teeth, his eyes shining with hatred.

At the same time, Chang Biao was also testing this killer move.

"As expected of a reward from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, this killer move is too strong!"

The power of the killer move was very shocking to Chang Biao as well.

"If I have to mention a flaw, it would be that the appearance is too ugly and evil..." Chang Biao looked at the mirror with a dark gaze.

The Chang Biao in the mirror had green-grey skin, fangs were growing out of his mouth and his eyes were yellow. He has green-red messy hair, looking very horrifying. Especially the six monstrous arms on his back, they were of different shapes and sizes, each were ruthless looking and made people feel a chill when they saw them.

Pan Ping originated from the demonic path, he often lacked resources and lived in terrible conditions, with survival as his main goal, he did not care about appearance or image.

But Chang Biao was different.

He was born in Chang tribe, he was like a noble, a reputable figure in the righteous path, he loved his appearance and placed emphasis on his reputation, if he were to show this appearance to people, he would feel very uncomfortable in his heart.

"However, although this form is ugly, I can only resort to this when dealing with Chang Shan Yin!" Thinking of Fang Yuan, Chang Biao made up his mind.

"To speak the truth, this move is quite similar to his strength path killer move. His killer move creates four arms on his back, together with his actual arms, he would have six in total. Meanwhile, my killer move creates six arms, I would have eight in total. This is a difference in appearance, but also shows that my killer move is stronger than his by a level."

Chang Biao was assessing in his heart, his impression of Fang Yuan's killer move was still the one in the Imperial Court contest.

Suddenly, Chang Biao had an inspiration, he had a guess: "This is quite the coincidence, the two killer moves are so alike... maybe, my version is the original, and what Chang Shan Yin got by chance was only a remnant version that was passed on outside."

The more he thought about it, the more he confirmed his guess.

"Chang Shan Yin is already an enslavement master, with his talent in enslavement path, how can he also have such talent in strength path? Hehehe, in the future when I get rid of him, I wonder what expression he will make when he sees my killer move? I am looking forward to it."

Thinking so, Chang Biao's lips curled into a smile.

Right at this moment, a servant came and told him Pan Ping had arrived.

Chang Biao's mind clicked and he knew what Pan Ping's intention was, he instructed: "Bring him to my study room, attend to him with good tea, I will be there shortly."

Because he was testing the killer move, Chang Biao's clothes were tattered.

After changing his clothes, he came to the study and saw that Pan Ping was gulping the tea that was served to him.

"What a waste of my good tea." Chang Biao sneered in his heart, before cupping his fists and calling out: "Brother Pan, you look especially happy today, there has been progress in the testing of the killer move?"

"Hahaha, Brother Chang is right, that is exactly so. This killer move is simply outstanding." Pan Ping laughed loudly before changing the topic: "However, there are some problems with this killer move, I tested it for three times, and every time after I end the transformation, I would feel a great pain in my stomach area. In fact, the pain gets worse the more I use it. Is this the backlash of the killer move?"

"Oh?" Chang Biao heard this and his gaze concentrated: "My symptoms are different from you, you have a stomach ache while I feel dizziness, even temporary deafness and blindness. I was going to find you to discuss this problem."

The two talked about the issue, but they did not gain any insights.

They were neither expert strength path cultivators nor refinement masters, their so-called discussion was only based on their own experiments, they could not get to the root of the issue.

Pan Ping suggested: "There are three other people who cleared the round along with us. Why don't we invite them over as well to discuss this matter. Relationships are built by interaction, once our relationship improves, we can invite them to join the Wolf Killing Alliance!"

Pan Ping was adamant on recruiting more members into their alliance, Chang Biao laughed as he said vaguely: "I have plans for this already, it will take effect in the next few days."

　　...

Imperial Court blessed land. A thousand li away from the sacred palace.

In the lush and green forest, a group of Gu Masters were carefully moving ahead.

Crack.

With a light, crisp sound, Ma Hong Yun accidentally stepped on a twig.

Everyone's movements stopped, they sent their angry and frightened gazes towards him.

"You idiot! How many times have we told you to notice what you step on, look down!" The group leader suppressed his volume as he chided with his eyes wide open.

"Sorry, sorry, I did not mean to do that!" Ma Hong Yun quickly apologised.

"Shut up, shut up!"

"Shush, quiet, you idiot!"

The Gu Masters nearby were anxious, the people near Ma Hong Yun even covered his mouth quickly in fear.

The leader's expression was solemn, he was anxious and some killing intent leaked: "All of you shut up. If you alert the iron beak bird group, we will be finished. We are only here to steal the eggs this time, we are retreating once we do that, I will personally kill whoever ruins this!"

The leader was the only rank three Gu Master here, he had the greatest strength and naturally, authority.

Hearing his words, everyone nodded quickly, including Ma Hong Yun.

The leader looked around, his gaze paused at Ma Hong Yun for a second as he gave him a fierce stare, deciding in his heart: "Once we go back, I am kicking this idiot from the group. So what if he has rank two strength? I must be blind, looking at how complementary his Gu worms were, I agreed to let him into the group. If a Gu Master is stupid to this degree, so what if he has good Gu worms?"

Swoosh!

Right at this moment, there was a sound that resembled waves in the forest.

Largest numbers of iron beak birds flapped their wings as they soared into the sky from the tree branches.

The Gu Masters who saw this felt that they had sunk into an icy abyss.

"What's going on?"

"Oh no, the birds were alerted! Quickly run!"

"Ma Hong Yun, it is all your fault, if I survive this, I will definitely settle the score with you!!"

Everyone were frightened and anxious, some were furious.

"No, the birds are flying south, it was not us who alerted them, it seems that there were others who accepted Chang tribe's mission!" The leader saw the situation and was overjoyed, screaming uncontrollably.

Everyone heard this and looked over, seeing this was the case, their moods changed.

"Save, save us!" A group of Gu Masters were flying quickly, towards them.

Looking at the densely packed bird group that were attracted over, the Gu Master's eyes were almost popping out.

"Don't, don't come over!" The leader shouted: "I will kill you first if you come closer!"

"Leader, looking at their clothes, they are Chang tribesmen." Ma Hong Yun said hesitantly.

The leader's eyes were wide open as he wanted to bash this guy up, shouting: "You idiot, do you still want your life? Go save them if you want to die!"

Ma Hong Yun thought of the time when they faced the earth chief beast group.

He only wanted to remind Jiang Dong, but he was nearly killed as a result.

"If not for my good luck..." Ma Hong Yun thought of this and shuddered, asking the leader: "What should we do?"

The leader gritted his teeth, seeing that the Chang tribe Gu Masters were not listening, rushing over intentionally, he stomped his foot: "What can we do? Split up and run!"

Everyone split up at once, as Ma Hong Yun was in a daze, quickly choosing a direction and running for his life when he realized what was going on.

"Lord, that is Ma Hong Yun, Ma Ying Jie's confidant." The Chang tribe Gu Masters who were running away might look pathetic, but they were all cool headed and had no fear.

Chang tribe group's leader was Chang Biao's confidant, he looked at Ma Hong Yun's figure as he was shocked: "Is this guy a fool? He is not using his movement Gu?"

Chang tribe was scheming, they naturally got all the details of Ma Hong Yun, they knew that he had a complete set of high quality rank two Gu worms.

"I, I am going to be caught, damn it, why are they so fast? They used a movement Gu, ah! Right, right, I have a movement Gu too!" As he ran, Ma Hong Yun patted his forehead as he quickly used his movement Gu, his speed rising drastically.

"He finally remembered, eh? Why is he still running towards the left?" The leader was shocked.

He did not know that Ma Hong Yun had a terrible sense of direction, back when Fei tribe was in turmoil, his father sacrificed himself to give him time to run, but he ran in a circle and turned back to the same spot.

Because of Ma Hong Yun's actions, the situation became more serious.

The leader quickly instructed: "You, you, you, quickly catch up with Ma Hong Yun and protect him. In addition, ask Lady Chang Li to go ahead and prepare!"

"Yes, lord."

Even though the Chang tribe Gu Masters were elites, Ma Hong Yun's random movement often got himself into dangerous situations, the Gu Masters had to attract the bird group while protecting him, they also had to avoid getting detected by him, it was a difficult position. Their plan which was guaranteed to succeed ended up with them sacrificing several elites!

"Sa... save me..." Chang Li was lying on the ground, she was weak and feeble, looking very vulnerable. Her clothes were torn, revealing her alluring shoulder. Her hair was messy and she looked very pitiful, like a fearful rabbit.

Ma Hong Yun ran over quickly, he was looking ahead as he desperately ran, he did not discover Chang Li at all!

Chang Li was stunned, at the last moment, she reacted and stretched out her leg when Ma Hong Yun was about to pass her.

Plop!

Ma Hong Yun fell face flat, he turned around and was shocked.

"What a beautiful lady..."

He was a dummy normally, but he was also at the age of being attracted to girls.

"Young master, please save me." Chang Li's beautiful voice made Ma Hong Yun's heart flutter.

"Oh, oh." Ma Hong Yun quickly replied, after some fumbling, he carried Chang Li and ran.

Chapter 578: Connection by Marriage

A day later.

During an evening banquet.

"A tribesman of your esteemed tribe saved my daughter, I, Chang Biao, am extremely grateful. This first cup is a toast to Ma tribe leader!" Chang Biao raised a wine cup.

Ma Ying Jie quickly lifted his cup and modestly replied: "That was only a chance encounter. I had not expected her to be Lord Chang Biao's beloved daughter, this is Hong Yun's honor."

"Hahaha." Chang Biao laughed heartily and drank the wine.

Ma Ying Jie also followed suit and downed the wine.

Ma Hong Yun who was sitting beside him had become the main character of the whole banquet at this moment and dozens of gazes gathered on him.

Feeling these probing, curious and doubtful gazes, Ma Hong Yun felt a little uncomfortable.

Chang Biao lightly placed down his wine cup and hinted Pan Ping who was beside him, with his eyes.

As they had already discussed properly, Pan Ping understood the signal, and looked at Ma Hong Yun: "Virtuous junior, if I speak so, aren't you like a hero saving the beauty?"

"I.. I..." Ma Hong Yun hesitated, speechless.

In truth, he also did not know how he had saved Chang Li. He had only been concerned about escaping from the endless iron beak birds chasing after him; the situation was so urgent, even if he had saved Chang Li, he did not think much.

Pan Ping stared with his eyes wide open at Ma Hong Yun who looked like he would not start speaking even till the cows came home.

Fortunately, Chang Biao had already calculated Ma Hong Yun's nature in his plan and at this moment, his gaze moved towards a certain person in the banquet.

This person immediately stood up and came to the center, cupping his fist towards Chang Biao: "Elder Chang Biao and all lords, I was one of the people involved in this matter and I was able to fortunately see the whole situation. Lord Ma Hong Yun is generous and modest, not claiming the credit and becoming arrogant, but I cannot endure a heroic deed being buried like this, so I summoned my courage by drinking to narrate the event to all lords."

Hearing these words, everyone knew this person was someone who was good at speaking.

Chang Biao nodded: "You can speak."

This person spoke with confidence, adding plentiful emotions and speaking in a way that echoed and added to their effects; he narrated in such a vivid way that it portrayed Ma Hong Yun as an aloof hero with an unwavering mind, with brains and brawn, not afraid of dangers.

As they listened to the narration, the crowd cheered and praised from time to time.

Their gazes towards Ma Hong Yun also started to change, becoming respectful, warm or appreciative.

Ma Hong Yun's eyes were wide open as he listened to this seemingly heavenly tale. He was feeling incredulous: "Is this person talking about me? When did I become so amazing? Did he mistake me for somebody else?"

There was one other person who did not dare to believe this - Ma Ying Jie.

Ma Ying Jie was Ma tribe leader, an outstanding hero of this generation. He was familiar with Ma Hong Yun's nature and character, how could he be deceived by these flowery words?

He had a faint smile on his face, and also nodded at the appropriate timings, looking at Ma Hong Yun approvingly; his mind, however, was in a state of deep thought: 'If say, Ma Hong Yun saved Chang Li by luck, there is nothing strange about it. But why would elder Chang Biao send a phony to explain things for Ma Hong Yun? What is he planning? In this banquet, although there are tens of distinguished guests, but the true main characters are only two in number, Chang Biao and Pan Ping.'

Ma Ying Jie was inwardly on guard.

Ma tribe had lost in the Imperial Court contest, falling down from their peak. Ma Ying Jie's master and father died in the battlefield, all these difficulties and setbacks caused Ma Ying Jie to quickly mature into an outstanding person.

He was secretly guessing Chang Biao's plan, but on the surface, he did not even bat an eyelid.

The current Ma tribe was declining, while Chang tribe was like the sun in the noon sky because of Fang Yuan! Pan Ping left demonic path and turned to Hei tribe, and was now an external elder of Hei tribe.

No matter which, they were both not people the current Ma tribe, the current Ma Ying Jie, could offend.

"Good, good, good." After that person finished narrating Ma Hong Yun's heroic deeds, Chang Biao repeatedly praised him.

"Heroes indeed arise from young people." Chang Biao looked at Ma Hong Yun, not stinting on his praise.

He paused, then continued: "Since ancient times, heroes love beauties and beauties are matched with heroes. I won't conceal it from everyone, ever since my daughter was saved, she has been silent, taciturn and her mind seems to be drifting off. I inquired her of the reason and only then learned her heart was somewhere else, worrying about the young hero who had saved her during the time of danger. I held this banquet to express my gratitude and also because of this."

The hall was in an uproar.

Countless gazes, mixed with admiration, envy, shock or unconvinced feelings, turned towards Ma Hong Yun.

"What bullshit luck does this kid have? He actually received Chang tribe's young miss' favor?"

"Chang Li is beautiful and pleasant, who could have thought she would prefer such a foolish kid. Sigh, if I had known this earlier, I would have also gone to the forest of iron beak birds."

"Chang Li might not be Chang Biao's own daughter, but he had taken her in and cared for her since she was young, she has always received Chang Biao's love and is a beloved daughter of elder Chang Biao. If this kid, Ma Hong Yun, marries Chang Li, his father-in-law would be Chang Biao!"

Instantly, everyone's mood surged.

Ma Ying Jie quickly reacted from his shocked state and rapidly thought with some suspicions: 'Is this the reason for Chang Biao entertaining us with such great fanfare? Although there is the tale of the Night Elopement of Su Xian, but isn't this going too well?"

There were even better things to come.

In front of everyone, Chang Biao took out two red steel relic Gu: "The new constantly replaces the old, Virtuous junior is a young hero of our northern plains, we cannot have him be unrewarded. These two red steel relic Gu are a little expression of my thanks to the benefactor, please accept them."

The commotion in the hall increased even more.

"Huh?" Ma Hong Yun quickly looked at Ma Ying Jie.

Ma Ying Jie nodded and pointed out with a smile: "We cannot dare to reject senior's gifts, Hong Yun, why are you not kowtowing and expressing your thanks?"

Ma Hong Yun immediately walked forward and kowtowed: "Many thanks for Lord Chang Biao's gift."

Chang Biao laughed heartily and also walked forward, personally putting the two red steel relic Gu in Ma Hong Yun's hand.

Under everyone's gazes, he amiably patted Ma Hong Yun's hand and asked: "I wonder how virtuous junior feels about my daughter?"

"Eh?" Ma Hong Yun raised his head with a flushed face, not knowing how to reply for a moment. After a while, he finally squeezed out a few words, "MIss Chang Li is beautiful, very beautiful."

"Hahaha." Chang Biao threw his head back and laughed, "This is good, this is good. Virtuous junior, please return to your seat."

They returned to their seats, and continued to enjoy the banquet.

The banquet continued from evening to late at night; only then the hosts and the guests had enjoyed to their fill and started taking their leave.

As the crowd dispersed, the matter of Chang tribe marrying off its daughter to the lucky kid Ma Hong Yun, also spread everywhere.

On the second day, Chang Biao again invited Ma Ying Jie and Ma Hong Yun to a banquet. The scale of the banquet would be smaller this time and only a few people were invited.

Ma Ying Jie gazed at the invitation card in his hand with a grave look.

After returning back, he had not slept the whole night and was pondering over this matter.

The small invitation card felt exceptionally heavy to him.

He placed the invitation card on the table and called his servant: "Go, call Ma Hong Yun to see me."

The servant immediately accepted the order and when he was arriving at Ma Hong Yun's residence, Zhao Lian Yun was in the process of instructing Ma Hong Yun: "You fool, what kind of bullshit luck do you have? But this matter is so good that it instead makes it feel hollow. I think tribe leader Ma Ying Jie will definitely call you to ask about this. At that time, explain everything clearly in full detail, don't hide even the smallest details!"

"Okay." Ma Hong Yun immediately agreed.

"Also." Zhao Lian Yun's large eyes turned, "Didn't Chang Biao reward you with two red steel relic Gu? When you meet the tribe leader, offer these two Gu to him."

"What?" Ma Hong Yun's eyes opened wide as he shouted, "This is something I risked my life for and obtained with great difficulty! And they were gifted to me by Lord Chang Biao, I will immediately advance to rank two upper stage after I use them. These are such good things."

"You fool!" Zhao Lian Yun kicked Ma Hong Yun's leg in anger.

Ma Hong Yun immediately held his leg in pain: "Why did you kick me?"

Zhao Lian Yun rolled her eyes and unhappily rebuked: "What do you understand? Even if you become rank two upper stage, what use would it be with your skill? What is the basis for us being able to stand up? It is not your rank two cultivation, but the friendship with tribe leader Ma Ying Jie. How did you advance to rank two? It is because tribe leader Ma Ying Jie gifted you with three green copper relic Gu. Offering the red steel relic Gu is an expression of loyalty, do you think the tribe leader will embezzle your red steel relic Gu? Hmph, he can't use it for himself, so he will definitely accept them then return them to you again."

"Eh, since he will accept them, why would he return them to me again?" Ma Hong Yun asked with doubt.

"Idiot!" Zhao Lian Yun again rolled her eyes, "Ma tribe has declined, there are very few tribesmen while there are many things to do. The whole tribe only has one rank three elder, Ma You Liang, and he is handicapped now. Ma Ying Jie has recently taken the tribe leader position and doesn't have any usable subordinates. He wants to revitalize the tribe and will be looking for talents to nurture into trusted aides. Although you were once surnamed Fei, now you are surnamed Ma, and you were once Ma Ying Jie's head servant. Ma Ying Jie knows everything about you and will be at ease in using you compared to other people. You will be showing your loyalty by offering the Gu worms, he will definitely be happy and accept your Gu worms; this is because he recognizes your loyalty."

"But Ma Ying Jie is not a petty and miserly master, accepting your Gu worms will only be as a gesture and he will definitely return them to you. Why? Because he wants to establish an example, from which the tribesmen can study and be encouraged to imitate your loyalty. I am certain, he will not only return your red steel relic Gu, he will even add in more rewards. Although you are insufficient in ability, you have loyalty. This is called buying horse bones with a thousand gold[1]."

Ma Hong Yun was confused: "What is buying horse bones with a thousand gold?"

"Sigh, you won't understand it even if I explain. Just do what I say and it will definitely be to your benefit."

"Ah." Ma Hong Yun agreed while scratching his head.

The two had just reached an agreement when Ma Ying Jie's servant came running over to summon Ma Hong Yun.

Ma Hong Yun followed Zhao Lian Yun's words and offered the two red steel relic Gu. But different from Zhao Lian Yun's estimation, Ma Ying Jie accepted them but did not return them back to Ma Hong Yun.

After Ma Hong Yun returned, he started complaining endlessly to Zhao Lian Yun.

"Could it be my estimation was wrong?" Zhao Lian Yun also felt some doubts.

[1] Read the TL note. Back

Chapter 579: Deputy Elder

In the evening, Ma Ying Jie took Ma Hong Yun to Chang tribe's banquet.

When the banquet ended, Chang Biao urged Ma Ying Jie to stay and have a talk in the study while letting Chang Li entertain Ma Hong Yun.

"I wonder what insights might Ma tribe leader have in six arm heavenly zombie king?" After some discussion, Chang Biao changed the subject to the killer move.

Ma Ying Jie, however, had not tested the killer move, speaking frankly: "I am an enslavement path master and have no affiliation to strength path. I was quite disappointed for the reward in passing the eighty-ninth round to be this killer move. I plan to sell this killer move, thus haven't tested it. What happened?"

Chang Biao was stupefied, glancing at Pan Ping next to him.

The two had not expected this situation, but it was actually reasonable.

Ma Ying Jie was different from them, he had a concrete and comprehensive enslavement path inheritance. His master Ma Zun relied on this inheritance to make a name and be a ruler of a region.

This inheritance contained a killer move as well. And besides it, Ma Ying Jie still had the powerful killer move from Snowy Mountain's Gu Immortal — Dragon Horse Spirit.

He had yet to master these killer moves, why would he go cultivate a killer move of another path?

He had been cultivating enslavement path since his youth, and as long as he cultivated it properly, he could become a ruler of a region and revitalize his tribe. Cultivating side paths would instead divide his energy.

Since ancient times, Gu Masters prioritized one path, and very few cultivated two paths. Dividing energy and continually moving back and forth will only result in achieving nothing on both ends.

Fang Yuan could dually cultivate paths because of the accumulation of his previous life's experiences.

Ma Ying Jie also had to manage the tribe's affairs and had no extra energy to cultivate some strength path killer move.

"I won't conceal it from you, I and brother Pan Ping have been testing this killer move. Its might is astonishing and overwhelming. We might as well speak the truth to Ma tribe leader." As he said this, Chang Biao paused, considering his words while somewhat hesitating.

He looked at Ma Ying Jie with a sincere gaze and shockingly said: "I would like to request Ma tribe leader to keep this killer move a secret and not spread it to others. Spreading it outside means the reward for clearing the round will be received by others."

Chang Biao intentionally spoke evasively, Ma Ying Jie was smart as he suddenly understood everything.

"So it was like this! Chang Biao was once Chang tribe's leader, now he is only a great elder and the tribe leader is his adopted son Chang Ji You, and the true decision maker is Wolf King Chang Shan Yin. Chang Biao obtained this killer move and wants to keep it a secret. This is a normal practice of Gu Masters. But there is a problem, if Chang Shan Yin learns of this and asks him for it, he will definitely have to hand it over."

Ma Ying Jie observed Pan and Chang's expressions and intonations, and knew six arm heavenly zombie king was absolutely an extraordinary killer move.

Humans were selfish, who would be willing to hand such a valuable treasure for no purpose? Ma Ying Jie understood this point.

Seeing Ma Ying Jie's gaze flicker, Chang Biao continued: "I have already talked with the others, Ma tribe leader can rest at ease. We still need Ma tribe leader's strength for the coming round. Hehehe."

Ma Ying Jie's expression turned solemn: "Lord Chang Biao exaggerates, my ability is limited, it is my fortune to be able to cooperate with all the experts, making it a win-win situation. I am okay with this matter being done like Lord Chang Biao says."

Hearing Ma Ying Jie's answer, Chang Biao and Pan Ping both smiled.

"Sigh, what lord, Ma tribe leader can just call me by my name." Pan Ping saw the chance, and immediately tried to pull their relation closer.

Pan and Chang wanted to pull Ma Ying Jie to their faction while Ma Ying Jie also wanted to rely on Chang tribe and Hei tribe's help to grow his tribe. The three went out of their way to curry favor with each other, addressing each other as brothers.

The three discussed in the study till late at night, getting along with each other.

It was near midnight, the three separated after setting Ma Hong Yun and Chang Li's engagement.

"Brother Chang's plan is excellent. With this connection by marriage, Ma Ying Jie will be tied with brother Chang, and when we deal with the Wolf King later on, he would have to help out." After closing the door, Pan Ping laughed heartily.

Chang Biao, however, slightly shook his head: "Ma Ying Jie is not someone easy to fool, he knows when to bow and submit, and at the the time of danger, he will definitely make a quick decision. It is still not the time to recruit him now, but as long as we continue to be on good terms with him and let people know of our close relation, and put in some resources to support that Ma Hong Yun, we will be able to increase our control over Ma tribe. And when we declare war against Chang Shan Yin in the future, as long as Chang Shan Yin recognizes Ma tribe as an enemy, Ma Ying Jie will have no choice but to get on our boat to protect his tribe!"

At night in Imperial Court blessed land, the bright and warm silver light shone on the ground.

In a carriage, Ma Ying Jie and Ma Hong Yun were sitting opposite each other.

"Hong Yun, you truly are a lucky guy, actually getting the interest of miss Chang Li. Hehehe, I have already come to a decision with lord Chang Biao; the first day of the next month will be a day of celebration for you and Chang Li." Ma Ying Jie said with a smile on his face.

"Ah?" Ma Hong Yun had not expected this news at all, and was not able to react for a while.

"I have seen your loyalty, good, this is your reward." Ma Ying Jie patted Ma Hong Yun's shoulder while sighing with emotion as he took out three red steel relic Gu from his aperture.

"This..." Ma Hong Yun was astonished, and dazedly received the three red steel relic Gu.

"You will be getting married with lady Chang Li, if you don't have power and status, wouldn't it weaken my Ma tribe's name? You can advance to rank two peak stage with these three red steel relic Gu; it should not be a problem for you to advance to rank three with your aptitude. I will now appoint you as a deputy elder and your duty will be to handle the miscellaneous affairs of the tribe." Ma Ying Jie proclaimed.

"Ah?" Ma Hong Yun's eyes opened wide, looking at Ma tribe leader with a stupefied expression.

To him, this surprise was really too heavy and too sudden.

Ma Ying Jie intentionally looked solemn: "You are still not kneeling and thanking me?"

Ma Hong Yun's mind was in a mess, but his body subconsciously kneeled down on the ground: "Thank you lord for promoting me!"

"Yes, work well." Ma Ying Jie encouraged with a few sentences, his thoughts, however were on a different matter, "Six arm heavenly zombie king, this killer move seems to be really powerful. Since it is regarded with such importance by Pan and Chang, and also does not need too much attainment in strength path cultivation, how about I give it a try as well?"

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, central control room.

"Ink transformation!" Fang Yuan's gaze flashed with a sharp light as he softly shouted and pressed down his hands.

Immediately, all kinds of Gu worms sprinkled down like rain from air, rapidly mixing with each other as they fell down.

When they landed on the sand table, they had already turned into drops of inky liquid.

The inky liquid quickly accumulated and covered the surface of the whole sand table once again before soon finding a flaw; the liquid then turned into a whirlpool and converged together.

Mo Yao's will in Fang Yuan's mind satisfiedly commented at this sight: "Good, you have now become skilled at the refinement technique I taught you - shower. With this method, you can quicken Gu refinement process by at least thirty percent and raise the quality by twenty percent. There is nothing more I can teach you about this method now. You only need to remember the essence of shower lies in speed. But you cannot just go fast, you need to pour all your concentration during the whole process. Thus, this method cannot be used too often. If you use it over the limit, you will feel dazed and dizzy in the minor case, causing the Gu refinement to fail, and in the serious case, your soul can be injured, you can suffer memory loss and you might become demented."

Gu refinement had dangers and was not any safer than an intense battle.

Fang Yuan already knew this; he listened to Mo Yao's guidance while methodically throwing the owner token into the ink whirlpool.

In a flash, the ink liquid was depleted completely and the owner token slowly flew up before landing on Fang Yuan's palm.

Fang Yuan observed the owner token which now already possessed five edges.

This meant ink transformation had already been carried out five times.

Strange, Fang Yuan was scarce on immortal essence stones and should have only been able to use ink transformation once more, how could he use it for three extra times beyond that?

After Fang Yuan got the one-edge owner token, his authority was raised and he could learn the contents of rewards for every round of a single floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building through the one-edge owner token.

Fang Yuan did not hesitate and choose one floor on the spot.

This floor was the seventh floor.

One-edge owner token could allow the Gu Master to control one floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The seventh floor had already been broken through to the eighty-ninth round by the collective efforts of Gu Masters. So why did Fang Yuan choose this floor instead of others?

It was because the reward for this eighty-ninth round was five immortal essence stones!

Fang Yuan secretly used the owner token to take control of this floor. Chang Biao, Pan Ping, Ma Ying Jie and others passed the round, and Fang Yuan was able to secretly take the five immortal essence stones, sending a downgraded version of six arm heavenly zombie king into everyone's aperture as the reward.

The genuine six arm heavenly zombie king used borrow strength Gu as its core, the six great flying zombie Gu as the backbone and many other Gu worms as support. Through modification by Fang Yuan and Mo Yao's will, the downgraded killer move used overlord Gu as its core, which greatly reduced its strength.

Although the other flying zombie Gu were not changed, the old earth chief zombie Gu was used instead of Mo Yao's modified Gu.

More importantly, the support Gu worms were also modified and some Gu worms like intention Gu were added to secretly gather the information on the use of six arm heavenly zombie king by Chang Biao, Pan Ping and others.

With this, it not only gave others no reason to doubt the reward being tampered with, it also made them test the killer move in place of Fang Yuan to find any insufficient areas.

"Half a month has gone by since the reward of the killer move was distributed. It is time to catch the fish in a net. What do you think?" Fang Yuan used a consulting tone to ask Mo Yao's will.

Mo Yao mumbled: "It has neither been too long nor too short, we can first take away two sets and see the results."

Fang Yuan grasped the five-edges owner token, and with a shift of his mind, he found two familiar figures in the ninetieth round of the seventh floor.

They were none other than Chang Biao and Pan Ping.

The two were currently running quickly.

Pan Ping shouted to Chang Biao while running: "It has already been seven days since we came here. Even if the time flow here is faster than Imperial Court blessed land, according to our speed, we should have already travelled an immeasurable distance but we have not been able to see anything other than walls."

The running Chang Biao nodded, his clothes fluttering in the wind: "In this place, we cannot fly to the sky nor can we escape under the ground, we can only move in these passageways along the walls. The passageways here spread in all directions, we have travelled so long but haven't encountered a single monster. Clearly, this round tests the Gu Master's scouting and movement ability. This round should be an extremely large maze."

The two guessed correctly, this ninetieth round was precisely a maze.

And just as Chang Biao guessed, it tested the Gu Master's scouting and movement ability.

But Fang Yuan had taken control of this seventh floor now and after he discovered these two, everything was going to be different.

Chapter 580: Perfecting the Killer Move

Howl—!

Wolf howls suddenly echoed out, a large group of turtleback wolves appeared ahead.

"Wolves, how could there be a wolf group here?" Pan Ping's movement slowed down, shouting in surprise.

Chang Biao's expression sank. Because of the connection with Fang Yuan, the animal he hated the most now was the wolf.

But he had never even thought that Fang Yuan would be controlling this round, and said in a gloomy voice: "Our priority this time was to probe, now that there has been a new change, we should see what happens after killing these wolves."

"Okay!" Pan Ping nodded in agreement.

The two cooperated and started killing the wolves.

At first, the two were occupying the upper hand even to the extent that it could be called a slaughter; how could ordinary turtleback wolves be their match?

But soon, other species of wolf started appearing continuously in front of them - vermillion wolves, water wolves, wind wolves and so on. Even mutated wolf groups like frenzy wolves and white-eyes wolves started appearing.

The two were gradually becoming unable to endure this.

"How could there be so many wolf groups?"

"Could it be this round also tests the Gu Master's ability to fight?"

Large numbers of thousand wolf kings entered the battle along with myriad wolf kings; Pan Ping and Chang Biao's expressions gradually turned unsightly.

"This round is so difficult!" Pan Ping sighed woefully.

"In Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the difficulty keeps on increasing as one passes the rounds, with the ninetieth to hundredth rounds being the most difficult." Chang Biao responded.

After a while more, the two could not continue fighting much longer.

"We have already probed the situation, the ninetieth round not only has a maze, but also wolf groups!" Chang Biao summarized in a heavy voice.

"We have walls on both sides, the terrain is narrow, we already are restricting the large crowds attacking us, what else can we do? Pan Ping frowned.

"Let's talk after retreating." Chang Biao sighed.

He and Pan Ping did not have Giant Sun bloodline, and had used guest tokens to enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Guest tokens were precious, thus they had to spend a lot of resources every time they entered.

"Alright!" Pan Ping already had the thought of retreating, he glanced at the wolf groups with hate, "These damned wolf beasts, there will be a day when I will step on your Wolf King and humiliate him! Hahaha...."

He cursed and vowed, the 'Wolf King' he was speaking of naturally referred to Fang Yuan.

"Eh!" The next moment, Pan Ping's laughter suddenly came to a stop, shock and fear replacing it.

"What's going on? We can't go out?" Chang Biao who was at the side also discovered this serious problem.

The two had used guest tokens to enter the tower and could leave with just a thought. They had already entered and exited many times, and were very familiar with this.

But now, this floor was under Fang Yuan's control, the five-edge owner token was many times more powerful than a guest token. These two were like birds within a cage, trapped in a predicament.

"Damn it, what should we do? I only have thirty percent primeval essence remaining!" Pan Ping shouted in panic.

Chang Biao's expression was grim as he shouted: "Calm down!"

His condition was a little better than Pan Ping with fifty percent primeval essence remaining in his aperture. But even if their primeval essence was full, it would be exhausted sooner or later in front of these endless wolf groups.

"This situation is very rare, how could we not get out of this tower? This round is strange, what it might be testing is the Gu Master's courage! We cannot act cowardly!" Chang Biao thought for a while and shouted.

Pan Ping heard his words, and slightly calmed down his panicked mind. He remembered that there were indeed strange rounds recorded in the past history, testing none other than the Gu Master's mind. Often in these rounds, the more cowardly the Gu master becomes, the stronger the monster they would have to face.

Pan and Chang forcibly calmed down, and then tried to break through the wolf groups' encirclement.

But Fang Yuan was in control of this round and was clear of every corner of the maze.

He mobilized the wolf groups with extreme smoothness; no matter how Pan and Chang tried to break through, there would always be wolf groups encircling and cutting off their path.

"No, I cannot die here! Damned wolf beasts, take my killer move!" With no alternative, Pan Ping used up almost all his primeval essence to activate the killer move 'six arm heavenly zombie king'.

He turned into an eight armed zombie; his battle strength rose explosively, creating surging waves wherever he moved. The wolves suffered severe losses with none being able to resist his attacks.

Chang Biao took the valuable chance to preserve his primeval essence by following behind Pan Ping, and was able to save quite a bit of strength.

The good situation did not last long and soon, Pan Ping's primeval essence was thoroughly exhausted.

Chang Biao quickly moved to save him: "In this time of danger, we need to work as one to have the hope of escaping alive. Take a rest and use primeval stones to recover your primeval essence, I will protect you!"

Chang Biao also used six arm heavenly zombie king and firmly protected Pan Ping.

With this kind of assistance between the two, they were able to stabilize the situation.

Seven-eight days went by like this, Chang Biao and Pan Ping's primeval essence were completely exhausted, no longer able to carry on.

"Am I going to die here?" Pan Ping roared at the sky.

"Damn it, there is definitely a way out, definitely!" Chang Biao had lost his earlier demeanour as he started shouting and roaring.

Just at this time of despair, the two suddenly saw a large pile of primeval stones in the corner ahead.

"Primeval stones!"

"Such a mountain of primeval stones, I am not hallucinating, right?"

Finding a way out of death's door, the two were elated and summoned all their bravery to kill their way through. The situation was stabilized once again as they used the primeval stones to recover their primeval essence.

"I understand, I understand now, this round tests the Gu Master's endurance!" Chang Biao shouted with wild joy.

"So it was like that." Pan Ping also came to a realization.

The two were so happy they did not realize the strange changes on their bodies.

As they started using 'six arm heavenly zombie king' more often, their bodies were now growing some irrecoverable zombie speckles.

"This hill of primeval stones is sufficient to last us two-three months." Pan Ping pounced on the primeval stone hill, crying tears of joy.

"Quickly use this time to recover primeval essence. We can't just keep sitting idly, there should be other primeval stone hills. When thirsty, we can drink wolf blood, and when hungry, we can eat wolf meat, maybe we can pass this round if we persevere like this." Chang Biao's eyes shone brightly.

"Brother Chang, you are right!" Pan Ping stood up quickly, his face flushed red as he imagined the scene Chang Biao portrayed, "This round is so difficult, it is almost an absolute death ground. There should definitely be a great reward for passing it!"

Chang Biao resisted the wolf groups' offense, sighing: "I finally know why we can enter but not exit this round. If we could easily leave, how could this round test the Gu Master?"

It was truly a pity these two still did not know this primeval stone hill was intentionally arranged here by their great enemy Fang Yuan. His goal was to make them use the killer move more, and continue the experiment.

The situation was fully within Fang Yuan's control. Even if these two had not been willing to use the killer move and only used their own moves, Fang Yuan would have controlled the wolf groups to continue attacking them, creating a dangerous set of circumstances where these two would have no choice but to use the killer move.

Fang Yuan's worry was unnecessary in this aspect.

As these two used the killer move, they started gradually becoming dependent on it, using it more and more. And in the following battles, they rarely used their own methods.

When their zombie speckles became denser and seriously affected them, they came to their senses.

But it was already too late.

"I don't accept this, I don't accept this, dying right here! Wolf King, I won't let you go even as a ghost!"

Pan Ping was the first to die.

Before he died, he cursed Fang Yuan.

Several days later, Chang Biao also died with exhaustion in the battle.

He died with grievance, mumbling to himself as he neared death: "Exit, where the hell is the exit?"

He had a lot of worries, too many things he could not let go.

Wolf Killing Alliance was only just being set up, the scheme of forcing Ma Ying Jie to join it had only just started, but even more than these, what made him the most unreconciled was his own son - Chang Ji You.

Truthfully speaking, Chang Biao was a pitiful person.

For his reputation, he dared not admit his own biological son and was only able to hear Chang Ji You call him 'godfather', 'godfather'...

Even so, he did not feel secure and to cover it further up, he adopted several orphans as his adopted sons and daughters. Among them was Chang Li.

He had made such painstaking efforts, laid low his whole life, planned so much, but now as he faced death, nothing had come to fruition.

He was unreconciled, full of regrets and annoyance, but what could he do?

"I really... really wanted to hear him call me father..." At this moment of death, his intense thoughts burst out as a sorrowful and regretful voice, passing away with the light of his life.

"The killer move was activated two thousand three hundred and eleven times, although he was exhausted in death, the main reason for fatality is the accumulation of zombie energy in his body." Fang Yuan appeared beside Chang Biao's corpse out of thin air.

He slightly smiled, the experiment had attained the expected purpose, but he found a problem —

Even if the killer move was used every time, it could not surpass a certain time limit, but instead the more it was used, the zombie energy in the body would accumulate till it led to the Gu Master's death.

Whether it was Pan Ping or Chang Biao, they both died because of this.

Fang Yuan took out the Gu worms from the two's corpses and stored them in his storage pouch.

This round was under his control, making it impossible for Pan and Chang to detonate their Gu worms even if they wanted to.

Chang Biao possessed a set of wind path Gu worms, all of them of excellent quality. Pan Ping's Gu worms were also not ordinary, but with Fang Yuan's current scope and capital, they were only considered better than nothing.

Only that sole blade Gu had some collection value, making Fang Yuan look at it for a moment.

Several days later.

In a study, Fang Yuan was thinking with his eyes closed while grasping an east window Gu.

"Hostile intent Gu can condense hostile intent. The hostile intent is strong and fiercely encroaching as fire, but it somewhat lacks flexibility and does not have the power to persist for long."

"Sharp intent Gu can condense sharp intent. The sharp intent is very sharp like swords and spears, however it can be subdued through soft tactics and is very difficult to restore."

"Reckless intent can condense reckless intent. Nothing is a taboo for the reckless intent and it can easily spread unchecked, but it is difficult to control and can easily injure the Gu Master."

This east window Gu, which Fang Yuan had purchased from treasure yellow heaven, recorded a fairly intact wisdom path inheritance. He paid all his small savings of immortal essence stones for it.

But it was worth it, Fang Yuan made some gains after reading it.

Fang Yuan pondered: "This inheritance records fourteen wisdom path Gu worms with six that touch upon the aspect of intent - hostile intent Gu, sharp intent Gu, reckless intent Gu, changing intent Gu, cold intent Gu and chaotic intent Gu. The first three are used to condense will, with each having their own pros and cons."

Wisdom path was the most mysterious among Gu Master paths, extremely broad and profound. It originated from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and had existed from Remote Antiquity Era. The Gu Masters who cultivated it were extremely few in numbers, but it still remained and passed down till today, never declining.

"Then what is Mo Yao's will classified as - hostile intent, sharp intent or reckless intent?"

Fang Yuan was researching these wills to guard against and deal with the enormous hidden danger in his mind.

"Hostile intent is fierce like fire, sharp intent is sharp like a spear, reckless intent is flamboyant and difficult to control, but Mo Yao's will is mysterious like the sea, hidden and indistinct. From the confrontations I had with her, it felt like I was not able to display my strength, like punching cotton."

Fang Yuan carefully analyzed and perceived Mo Yao's will was not any one among this list.

This inheritance he had gathered was only a corner of wisdom path; there were definitely many other wisdom path Gu worms.

"It seems I still need to continue gathering information on wisdom path..." Fang Yuan inwardly sighed.

Fang Yuan was not able to easily use his methods against Mo Yao's will because he was not familiar with wisdom path, and did not know her trump cards.

"As the proverb goes, know yourself and know your enemy, and you will go unscathed through a hundred battles. I need to bear with this for the moment, make her think continuously and wear herself down, while also using her to help in exploring True Yang Building."

Right as he was thinking, Mo Yao's will appeared with her indistinct figure in Fang Yuan's mind.

"It is done, the six arm heavenly zombie king this time is truly perfected, there are no more unsuitable factors." Mo Yao said with a weak tone and exhausted expression.

'Looks like she had been worn down a lot from all the thinking over these days." Fang Yuan was inwardly happy, and as he looked at the modified killer move, this hidden happiness gradually turned into exultation!

Chapter 581: Advance to six-edge, difficulty finding a Gu tester

Fang Yuan was a vigilant person, he had always felt that everyone else in this world was unreliable, the only dependable person was himself. Thus, he researched the six arm heavenly zombie king killer move the moment he obtained it.

This killer move was originally created based on the foundation he provided, furthermore during these few days, with Mo Yao's guidance, his refinement path attainment was deepening, and his perspective had widened greatly.

Right now, he had a great understanding of the concept of six arm heavenly zombie king, it was clear as water to him.

At this moment, he looked at the completed killer move, without any experiments, he knew that this killer move was close to perfection.

Mo Yao had reduced many supplementary Gu worms from the original base, while keeping the core and the six zombie Gu unchanged, only adding several supplementary Gu worms in.

Sensing the ingenuity of this, Fang Yuan praised endlessly.

In his mind, Mo Yao's will explained: "This is all thanks to the intention Gu on Pan and Chang. With their experience and insight, I could refine this move to such an extent, we have reached an extreme level of perfection. As long as the time does not exceed thirty minutes, no matter how many times you activate the killer move, it will not accumulate zombie energy in your body and cause zombie speckles to grow."

Fang Yuan nodded, knowing that Mo Yao's words were true.

This killer move was truly refined to its limits, according to this line of thinking, it had already reached its strongest potential. Unless he added Immortal Gu in the future, or changed the core Gu.

But if he added Immortal Gu in, this would destroy the original coordination of the Gu, he would need to reassemble it and the move would become completely different, it would truly be a situation of 'pull one hair and the whole body moves'.

If he changed the core Gu, that would be going into another line of thought. The new killer move would be completely different, rather than calling it 'six arm heavenly zombie king', he might as well give it another name.

In all, the killer move six arm heavenly zombie king, be it the core Gu, the zombie Gu or the supplementary Gu, they were being used to their fullest potential, there was no way to refine this further.

Even though there were still backlashes from using it, if one exceeded thirty minutes, the zombie energy would cause great damage to the Gu Master's body, if the time was too long, the Gu Master might even turn into a zombie.

But this was a problem caused by inappropriate usage by the Gu Master, it could be avoided. The reason was that even if this move was used many times, it would not accumulate the zombie speckles. If the Gu Master activated the move multiple times in a period of time, they could potentially sustain the killer move for a long duration.

Except, Fang Yuan was still not satisfied with this huge result.

"If you have any other ideas to refine this killer move, this grandmaster here is willing to listen." Mo Yao laughed eerily.

"At this point, six arm heavenly zombie king is at its limit, there is nothing to improve. But there is still one part that I am not satisfied with, that is the backlash of the killer move." Fang Yuan said.

"After the improvement, the current six arm heavenly zombie king's power has doubled, and the duration has reached thirty minutes, it is sufficient for you to handle anything in this mortal realm. What are you dissatisfied with? You must know, any killer move represents the combination usage of Gu worms, since it is the use of Gu worms, there has to be weaknesses. A killer move's backlash cannot be avoided, they are only different in terms of severity. This strength path killer move's power is at the top five of killer moves in my memory. Don't be too greedy." Mo Yao lectured.

Fang Yuan snorted.

His potential enemies were Gu Immortals, beings who surpassed mortals!

With six arm heavenly zombie king, even if Fang Yuan abandoned his enslavement path, he could still dominate the mortal realm, but it was far from sufficient to deal with Gu Immortals.

Battling an immortal as a mortal, this aim was too arrogant, it was too much for people to believe. Fang Yuan had no intentions of informing Mo Yao about this.

Immediately after, he said: "Preparedness ensures success, and unpreparedness spells failure. If one day, because of a peculiar situation, I overuse the killer move and become

a zombie, what happens? I am also clear that the killer move six arm heavenly zombie king cannot be improved further, but now, my goal is to resolve this weakness."

Mo Yao finally understood Fang Yuan's intention, she sunk into silence.

Fang Yuan was young and arrogant, Mo Yao did not expect that he had such a cautious side. To speak the truth, Mo Yao was looking at him in a different light now —

"This lad, he has talent, resources, and opportunities. He has great perseverance and is able to lower his head when needed. On one hand, he advances bravely, while on the other hand, he is cautious and vigilant, always considering all sides of the matter. This lad, one day, he will definitely shake the world."

She was silent for a short time, soon, Mo Yao said: "It is very troublesome to resolve this backlash. Six arm heavenly zombie king is not an ordinary zombie, the zombie energy is extremely thick, once the Gu Master transforms, they cannot even use Yin-Yang rotation Gu!"

"As a refinement grandmaster, is there nothing you can do?" Fang Yuan did not believe her.

Mo Yao did not fall for his taunting, she spoke in a calm manner: "I need a rank five Gu Master to fully transform into the six arm heavenly zombie king, after which I will experiment on their body. I need this test subject to cooperate with me fully, and I need to have full control over their condition, in terms of body, mind, and personal experience... These are all important information that I need to consider."

Mo Yao did not want to ponder about this deeply as it would expend too many of her thoughts, she used the same method again, planning to use people as experimental fodder. They would replace her thinking and undergo the most crucial steps for her.

Fang Yuan frowned: "Rank five Gu Master? And a fully cooperative one?"

"That's right, it would be best if they are willingly doing it. Because if slavery Gu is used to control them, their emotions would be affected, their experience and feelings when turning into a zombie would be ruined."

This was troublesome!

If Fang Yuan wanted to resolve the problem of six arm heavenly zombie king, he would need to find a rank five Gu Master, and they would need to be cooperative and listen to Fang Yuan, risking their lives to undergo this experiment.

Where was Fang Yuan going to find such a person?!

Three days later.

Central control room.

From the ink whirlpool, the owner token rose up and flew into Fang Yuan's hands.

Activating the refinement path killer move ink transformation once again, five-edge owner token had transformed into six-edge.

Fang Yuan was both happy and worried.

Happy because he had the six-edge owner token, once Hei Lou Lan's owner token becomes four-edge, he would be able to snatch it and form the ten-edge owner token.

With a ten-edge owner token, he could obtain one of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's true inheritances!

An Immortal Venerable inheritance had a huge attraction to almost anybody.

Worry was because Fang Yuan had expended almost all his resources to undergo this sixth ink transformation. In order to accumulate funds, he had sold the Immortal Gu remnant recipes again and caused these remnant recipes to have no value left.

At the same time, he sold large numbers of rockmen, fox groups, wolf groups, Gu worms, and even the precious hairy men and some air bubble fish.

Like the rank four emotion poetry Gu, golden dragon Gu, golden breeze Gu, as well as rank five Gu including multiple spring egg Gu, vajra stare Gu, turn gold Gu, soft bones Gu, pitch black Gu, and hints and clues Gu.

"Right now, I only have the enslavement and strength path Gu worms left in my aperture. In Hu Immortal blessed land, I have Blood Sea Ancestor's true inheritance, rank four blood skull Gu, as well as rank three bone flesh unity Gu and the yang Gu left after using yin Gu of the yin-yang rotation Gu. Other than that, I still have some stargate Gu, hole earth Gu, connecting heaven Gu, divine sense Gu, burial soul toad, and some supplementary Gu."

These Gu were all of utmost importance, they could not be sold. Some were absolutely necessary, he needed them in the future.

"Hu Immortal blessed land was almost squeezed dry by me, it needs to recover. But now that I have the six-edge owner token, I can control six floors in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building as I wish. All of the rewards in these six floors can be taken by me. These rewards are extremely valuable, if I take them all, my wealth would grow by at least sixty times that of my current foundation!"

Fang Yuan had his plans.

But currently, he could not touch these rewards.

Hei Lou Lan had gathered some experts, and was at the final round of the fifth floor.

Soon, he was going to obtain a one-edge owner token.

With this token, he could check any floor's round rewards in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

If Fang Yuan took the rewards, wouldn't he reveal himself?

"At the final moment, when Imperial Court blessed land is about to close and everyone gets sent out, I will take the rewards then, by that point, nobody would know a thing."

　　...

Bam!

The bear paw smacked and the earth quaked, rocks were sent flying like shrapnel.

As the smoke dispersed, a huge bear paw the size of five to six horse carriages was lifted, showing a huge crater.

The rank four Gu Master who was unfortunately hit by the bear paw had turned into a pile of mushy flesh, mixed with some bone shards and brain matter.

"Too fast! We cannot react to it."

"The final round is truly harder than ascending to heaven..."

"This is only the phantom image of a flying bear, it only has half the strength of the true body. If this was really the desolate beast flying bear, we would not even be able to escape!"

The Gu Masters on the battlefield were all injured, they were in a pathetic state and felt great lingering fear.

It was the phantom image of the desolate beast flying bear that was guarding the fifth floor's hundredth round.

It had a huge body, like that of a mountain, it had white, snowy fur, and a full set of Gu worms in it, each were elite Gu worms. It attacked fiercely, but moved just as agilely, it could dart around like lightning, which was ironic due to its huge bulky figure. After fighting for only thirty minutes, the Gu Masters had already suffered huge losses.

"Lord tribe leader, we should retreat. Our motive this time is to probe it, now that we have understood most of the Gu worms on the flying bear, we have actually achieved our goal already." Sun Shi Han stood beside Hei Lou Lan, advising.

Hei Lou Lan frowned, looking around the battlefield.

He was an expert in leading men to wars and battles, he knew that his troops had low morale now.

"Since I started challenging the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, this flying bear phantom is the strongest opponent I've met. To defeat it, our strength is not enough, we need even more helpers."

Hei Lou Lan assessed in his heart before snorting and saying one word: "Retreat."

Sun Shi Han felt relieved in his heart, and not just him, the other Gu Masters already had the intention to retreat, but because of the Black Tyrant's fierce reputation, no one dared to suggest it.

Chapter 582: Fighting flying bear, Wolf King gets fifty percent

Everyone retreated from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, as Hei Lou Lan gave an order to recruit experts that night.

He was the alliance leader that won this contest, according to the rules, the entire army was his to mobilize. Everyone knew about the Black Tyrant's fierce reputation, together with him opening Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to everyone without any cost, they were deeply grateful to him.

With both authority and gratitude, Hei Lou Lan's influence reached its peak.

With this order, it created a huge commotion as everyone who was called showed up without fail.

Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu, Twin Demons Gao Yang and Zhu Zai, Little Ma Zun Ma Ying Jie, Fox Commander Tang Miao Ming, White Fairy Xi Xue, Shadow Sword Expert Bian Si Xuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Lu Shuang, Tao You, Gu Guo Long, Dou E, Nie Ya Qing, Ye Lui Sang...

On the day of the alliance meeting, the hall was filled with shining stars as heroes and conquerors whipped up a huge storm.

"Old sir, with you here, it is like having a giant pillar of support, we do not have to fear about low morale, hahaha!" Hei Lou Lan sat grandly at the main seat, looking around and laughing with great ambitions.

Among those who were present, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had the greatest reputation, he healed people all over the land, countless people were indebted to him, even Hei Lou Lan or Chang Shan Yin could not compare to him.

But the person who sat next to Hei Lou Lan was not Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but Wolf King Chang Shan Yin.

Reputation was something, but battle strength was another aspect.

After the Imperial Court contest, everyone agreed that Fang Yuan's battle strength was the greatest. Dual path cultivator, flying master, enslavement master, all these auras gathered into one person, it was dazzling and overwhelming, thus no one had any disagreements regarding Fang Yuan's position.

Thus, after Hei Lou Lan talked to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he turned around to Fang Yuan: "Brother Shan Yin, we will need to count on you for this battle! If we get through, you will earn half of the rewards."

He understood Fang Yuan's nature, he would not act without benefits, thus he gave such a tempting offer.

The final round's rewards were nothing ordinary. Once Hei Lou Lan spoke, he gave half the benefits to Fang Yuan, this meant that he, along with the others, would have to share the remaining half of the rewards.

As their interests were concerned, some discussions could be heard in the hall.

Many people were indignant regarding this allocation, but no one had the guts to openly oppose Black Tyrant's arrangements and offend the grand Wolf King in this hall.

"Very well, we will go with that." Fang Yuan nodded, his arrogant gaze swept the hall, as the voices came to a stop.

"Why has elder Pan Ping not arrived yet?" Hei Lou Lan asked around.

Pan Ping was born in the demonic path, nowadays he had entered Hei tribe and become an external elder. As the current Hei tribe leader, Hei Lou Lan's orders did not summon Pan Ping, Hei Lou Lan was extremely displeased by this.

Actually, not just Pan Ping, Chang tribe's first elder Chang Biao was not present either.

But Chang Biao was a Chang tribesman, Hei Lou Lan had to ignore it because of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not react.

The information regarding the deaths of Pan and Chang had not been spread yet.

Challenging Eighty-Eight True Yang Building normally took several days or even half a month, the tougher the rounds, the longer it would take. Especially someone like Pan Ping, as a person without Giant Sun bloodline, he would incur huge expenses when he entered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building using the guest token. Precisely because of this, these outsiders treasured their opportunity in entering the building, if possible, they would not leave it unless they had no other choice.

Hei Lou Lan's words had just been spoken, when his attendant Hei Shu stood up and reported: "Reporting to lord tribe leader, elder Pan Ping and Lord Chang Biao had gone into the seventh floor not long ago, I have sent people to inform them, but the seventh floor's layout is very confusing, it is like a huge maze. The maze prohibits the use of letter Gu, and there are even wild wolf groups deep inside. The servants have tried to find them for many days, but they only found some battle traces, they could not find the two lords."

Hei Lou Lan snorted as he waved his hand: "Then forget it, we will not wait for them, the guest tokens are ready, we will depart tomorrow morning!"

By the second day, everyone grandly charged into the fifth floor.

This was the largest force that had gathered to enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building since it was formed, it attracted countless gazes in the sacred palace.

The final round of the fifth floor was a barren and desolate mountain.

Brown soil, hard as steel rocks, with no grass or plants.

The moment everyone entered, the flying bear phantom was alerted and growled, tearing through the air, and causing a thunderous noise.

Swoosh!

They saw in the dark yellow sky, a white whirlwind come crashing down.

The experts retreated at once.

The flying bear phantom crashed on the ground, with a loud bang, the earth shook as intense winds blew, causing many to lose their balance.

"Ferocious indeed!" Pei Yan Fei's expression was solemn, if he had been hit directly, he would be heavily injured if not dead.

"It was thanks to tribe leader Hei Lou Lan's reminder, if not, the moment we came in we would've been attacked by this bear." Gu Guo Long looked at the howling flying bear inside the crater and said with lingering fear.

"This is called learning from past experiences, the last time we came here, we were sneak attacked by the flying bear, five experts died on the spot!" Hei Xiu Yi gritted his teeth, saying with deep hatred.

"Brother Shan Yin, the rest is up to you guys." Hei Lou Lan urged.

According to their battle plan earlier, the first wave of attack should be unleashed by the enslavement path Gu Masters, in order to wear down the flying bear phantom's battle strength.

Without any words from him, large numbers of wolves came from all directions, from the sky and land, charging and attacking the flying bear phantom.

In the sky, there was the azure wolf group, on the ground, there were the white-eyes wolves, frenzy wolves, blood forest wolves and others.

Ordinary wolves numbered to over four hundred thousand.

At once, the wolves engulfed the area, charging like the huge waves of the great sea, submerging the island-like flying bear phantom.

Roar!

The flying boar roared, shaking heaven and earth.

Howl!!!!

The wolf groups were not to be outdone, howling in a similar fashion.

The battle ensued, whipping up a bloody storm.

The flying bear phantom's four paws slammed, killing at least dozens of wild wolves with one strike. The ordinary wolves could only be a disturbance to it, only the mutated beast groups could pose a threat and cause injuries to the flying bear phantom.

But the essence of enslavement path had always been to overwhelm quality with quantity, expending the enemy's energy to their greatest limit.

Fang Yuan manipulated the wolf group, attacking as freely as the wind, or as crushing as the snow, the flying bear phantom seemed to have sunk into a deep swamp, even with its frenzied attacks, it could not break through the encirclement.

"Now this is a master level attainment."

"Wild beasts are beasts, without a human's intelligence, they are being toyed around by Chang Shan Yin."

"The beast groups are like a work of art under Wolf King's control!"

Everyone was in a daze, the enslavement Gu Masters Tang Miao Ming and Hei Qi Sheng could see the brilliance of his actions, feeling a strong sense of admiration and adoration towards Fang Yuan.

But the good situation did not last, the flying bear phantom suddenly stopped its actions, opening its mouth and exhaling.

With this, the world changed colors, as starlight shone brilliantly to form into a river.

Rank five — star river Gu!

The star river poured down, like a dragon or python, it engulfed the places it went, be it frenzy wolf or blood forest wolf, they were swept away by the star river, some were holding their ground desperately with their defensive Gu, but those that did not have defensive Gu were turned into stardust.

At once, the wolf group suffered huge losses.

Fang Yuan's gaze was unmoved, it was as if the losses did not affect him, and he did not stop for now.

Only until half the wolves were left, did he order them to retreat.

Tang Miao Ming and Hei Qi Sheng quickly ordered their beast groups to replace the wolves.

These two, one was called Little Fox Commander with quasi-master attainment, in terms of enslavement attainment, she was second to Fang Yuan alone in the sacred palace.

The latter was an enslavement path Gu Master nurtured by the super force Hei tribe, although he had not attained master level skill, he had deep foundations and great strength.

Tang Miao Ming controlled the fox groups, while Hei Qi Sheng controlled the eagle groups, one dominated the sky while the other was on the ground.

But the flying bear phantom was getting more ferocious, after the star river had fully looped around in a ring, it clapped its paws together, roaring again as an intense wind blew, and clouds formed from nothing.

In an instant, the intense wind turned into tiger-shaped wind tigers, while the clouds turned into dragon-shaped cloud dragons.

Rank five — wind tiger cloud dragon Gu!

Thousands of wind tigers and cloud dragons charged forward, facing the foxes and eagles head on.

At once, the battlefield was in chaos as blood rained and the pungent smell spread.

"Oh no, at this rate..." Tang Miao Ming's forehead was full of sweat, her head was hurting as she was gritting her teeth desperately.

The battle was too intense, she wanted to preserve her fox group, thus she manipulated them very meticulously, it caused her soul to be greatly worn out, and she was reaching her limit.

As for Hei Qi Sheng, his situation was even worse than hers.

The fox group could still resist the enemy, but a large proportion of Hei Qi Sheng's eagle group had already been killed by the wind tigers and cloud dragons, they were in disorder and he could not attend to one aspect without neglecting another.

The other Gu Masters retreated time and time again, but they did not show any surprise.

Star river Gu and wind tiger cloud dragon Gu were exposed in their previous probing, everyone was prepared for them.

"Have you finished the investigation?" Hei Lou Lan asked an investigative Gu Master beside him.

The investigative Gu Master was very nervous, he sat on the ground as he activated his Gu worm wholeheartedly. His forehead was folded into a frown as he replied with a trembling voice: "Star river Gu's location has been found, it is in the flying bear's mouth, on the largest tooth on the left side. As for the other Gu worms, we have to continue searching."

It was different to deal with beasts compared to Gu Masters.

All the Gu worms on the wild beast are wild, they can be captured. Gu worms on Gu Masters were usually refined already.

Hei Lou Lan ordered his men to search for the location of the wild Gu because of this.

As long as they can capture the wild Gu on the flying bear's body, it would be much easier for them to destroy the flying bear phantom.

Even if they could not capture it, it would suffice if they destroyed the Gu.

Gu worms were very fragile on their own, even for Spring Autumn Cicada which was rank six, Fang Yuan just needed to squeeze lightly to squish it.

Wild beasts did not have apertures, the wild Gu resided in their bodies, this was a huge weakness.

Hei Lou Lan snorted, shouting: "Continue searching!"

He was not pleased with this result, the star river Gu was inside the flying bear's mouth, the difficulty to capture it was too high.

During their conversation, the battlefield's situation was getting worse.

"Tang Miao Ming and Hei Qi Sheng are slowly becoming unable to resist!" Pei Yan Fei said with a heavy expression.

"The flying bear's attacks are too ferocious, luckily the wild beasts are attracting its attention. But even if the foxes and eagles die, we can replenish them, our motive of weakening the enemy has been achieved." Sun Shi Han stroked his beard as he evaluated.

Chapter 583: Killing flying bear, Accident at the final moment

Although wild Gu absorbed energy from the air directly, being able to use their abilities freely without any limits on primeval essence.

But during an intense battle, towards the end, the wild Gu would become more and more passive, if they sensed that the battle was going south, they would leave their host and escape on the spot using their instinct of sensing danger.

Thus, when attacking a wild beast, especially beast kings or desolate beasts, during the first half of the battle, it would usually contain the most firepower, after a while, the attacks would slowly become weaker and less oppressive.

"Even so, we cannot allow the fox group and eagle group to suffer such losses, we should invite Lord Chang Shan Yin to step in." At the side, Hei Xiu Yi said.

"Step in... to what end?" Fang Yuan folded his arms, scoffing arrogantly as he heard this: "According to our battle arrangement, I will strike first while the two of them take over after me, with such intervals, we have to each hold on for fifteen minutes. Right now, they have not even been there for half the allocated time, it is not time for me to step in yet."

If they entered the battlefield now, the wolf group would only face the cruel slaughter of the flying bear phantom, although it would weaken the flying bear phantom as intended, if he could reduce his losses, Fang Yuan was very willing to watch on the fence.

As for the others' losses, was that Fang Yuan's problem?

Hei Xiu Yi was furious upon hearing this, but because of Fang Yuan's status, he could only hold in his anger: "Lord Wolf King, everyone is putting in their full effort for this battle, right now Tang Miao Ming and Hei Qi Sheng are fighting with their life, but lord is watching by the side, isn't this too much?"

"Hmm? You dare to lecture me?" Fang Yuan frowned as his killing intent surged.

Although he was folding his arms, a monstrous arm grew out from his back.

The monstrous arm was extremely powerful and strong, but it also moved extremely fast, directly assaulting Hei Xiu Yi.

Never in Hei Xiu Yi's dreams did he think that Fang Yuan would dare to publicly, and especially during such an important battle, try to kill him?!

Before the fist hit, he felt the intense winds blowing towards him, causing his face to feel pain already.

An incomparable feeling of fear and danger instantly filled his heart.

At the crucial moment, his battle senses from many years of fighting saved his life successfully.

He reacted before even thinking, activating his defense Gu and putting up three lines of defense.

He was a defensive Gu Master originally, and because his specialty was defense, Hei Lou Lan had once sent him to Fang Yuan as a form of protection.

But during the battle, Hei Xiu Yi cherished his own safety and forgot about his mission, abandoning Fang Yuan on the battlefield.

The monstrous arm was unstoppable, it smashed the three defenses quickly and hit his chest.

Crack.

A crisp sound could be heard.

Hei Xiu Yi's rib bones were all crushed, the monstrous strength sent him flying like a cannonball.

He vomited blood while flying in the air.

Then with a rumble, he crashed on a small mound several hundred steps away.

When the sound of the impact was heard and the dust settled, he was half embedded into the mound, falling unconscious and losing his battle strength.

"Lord Wolf King?!"

"What happened? What happened! Why did they fight?"

"Hei Xiu Yi urged Lord Wolf King to battle, the two could not get along and Wolf King suddenly burst into anger, sending Hei Xiu Yi flying!"

Seeing such a shocking event, everyone was gasping.

Internal conflicts were always so sudden, so severe.

Hei Xiu Yi's identity was not simple, he was one of the three commanders of the black banner army, an important person within the Hei tribe higher-ups. Fang Yuan attacking him with such intensity was no different than openly taunting Hei Lou Lan.

Once Hei Lou Lan and Chang Shan Yin stood on opposing sides, this battle would not only end up in failure, the entire sacred palace would also fall into political turmoil!

"Wolf King, what happened? I would like to hear your explanation." Hei Lou Lan's expression was like still water as he came over to question Fang Yuan.

He usually called Fang Yuan "Brother Shan Yin" to show their close relationship, but now that he called him "Wolf King", it showed his anger.

But no matter how angry he was, would Fang Yuan be afraid?

Immediately, Fang Yuan stared back at him with no fear, his killing intent dispersed as he snickered: "Tribe leader Hei Lou Lan, you came at a good time, your subordinate was truly stepping out of line, he dared to lecture me? Such a lack of respect with a complete disregard for seniority, I punished him for you, no need to thank me, don't forget about our friendship after all."

Using "disrespect" and "seniority", he sent two reasons over just like that.

His final sentence mentioning "our friendship" had even deeper meaning.

It was like he was trying to say that they had a great friendship, but it could also mean that they had no friendship at all!

Hei Lou Lan stared furiously!

"This Chang Shan Yin is too arrogant! He dared to hit my man! Looking at his lawless manner, does he really think I cannot do anything to him just because of his great battle strength?" Black Tyrant roared in his heart.

He was cultivating dark path on the surface, but in truth, because of the Great Strength True Martial physique, his real cultivation was in the strength path.

His battle strength was superb, but he could not use his strength path methods because that would accelerate the disaster of one of the ten extreme physiques.

"I'll endure it! Right now, we are at the crucial moment of attacking the flying bear phantom, if we get into an argument now, it would all go to waste! What is most important now is to find my strength path Immortal Gu and ascend to become a Gu Immortal!"

As long as they killed the flying bear phantom this time, Hei Lou Lan would be able to get through this floor and his owner token would immediately become a one-edge owner token.

With the one-edge owner token, he would be able to inspect the reward of any round of any floor, the one with a strength path Immortal Gu would be his focus and target.

Precisely so, it was extremely important to kill the flying bear phantom, even with Hei Lou Lan's temper and cruelty, he had to endure it.

"I'll let you be arrogant for once! One day, I will make you kneel down at my feet and lick my toes, if I tell you to shut up, you will keep quiet. If I ask you to bark, you will wag your tail!"

Hei Lou Lan was extremely furious, veins were popping on his forehead, but his eyes were fixed on Fang Yuan intensely.

Just as everyone was feeling a heavy atmosphere from this silence, and were feeling uneasy, Hei Lou Lan suddenly raised his head and laughed loudly: "Good, brother Shan Yin did a good job, such a disrespectful person should be taught a lesson indeed."

This was akin to Hei Lou Lan taking a step back, those who knew his poor temper were all shocked.

"His tribesman was beaten till he was unconscious in public, Hei Lou Lan actually agreed with him?"

"Wolf King is too strong, he did not care about the super force Hei tribe, now even Hei Lou Lan need to take a step back."

"Bullshit, this is tribe leader Hei Lou Lan caring about the big picture! He did not want to stoop to the level of Chang Shan Yin! Chang Shan Yin beat us Hei tribesmen, one day, he will pay the price."

Everyone had their comments as they conversed in secret.

Roar!

The flying bear's roaring attracted everyone's attention again.

The eagle and fox groups were facing great losses.

"I have let down all the lords." Hei Qi Sheng's nose was bleeding, his face was full of shame.

Tang Miao Ming's expression was pale, as her slim body was swaying with weakness.

"Protect the two of them." Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted.

"Both of you have had a huge contribution to this, I can see your sincerity. After this battle, you will be greatly rewarded." Hei Lou Lan had an amicable expression as he came forward to console them.

The flying bear lost its obstacles and charged forward towards everyone.

By right, the wolf group should be charging up to continue weakening the bear.

But Hei Lou Lan looked at Fang Yuan who was folding his arms arrogantly, not saying a word, in fact his wolves were retreating faster than anyone on the battlefield.

"I'll endure! One day, I will make you pay a huge price!" Hei Lou Lan gritted his teeth, knowing that he could not make Fang Yuan do anything, if he forced Fang Yuan and got rejected in public, he would take a huge hit to his reputation and be deeply humiliated.

Thus, Hei Lou Lan shouted loudly: "Strike, initiate the second step of the plan!"

"Go!"

Immediately, two people flew out like lightning.

One was a slim and elegant person wearing a fluttering blue dress, it was White Fairy Xi Xue.

The other was muscular and stable, wearing a yellow robe, it was Gu tribe leader Gu Guo Long.

White Fairy Xi Xue flew into the air, her sleeves were waving as she shouted in an alluring manner, causing snow to descend immediately.

It was her signature rank five Gu worm — flying snow Gu.

Gu Guo Long ran on the ground, his legs were moving like turbines, everywhere he went, smoke rose as rocks were sent flying.

It was also a rank five Gu, called flying sand moving rock.

At once, white snow was floating in the air, while sand and rocks were rolling on the ground.

The giant mountain-like flying bear phantom was stuck between the snow and sand, its speed reduced drastically as its vision was also obscured.

It roared loudly, waving its paws in the snow and sand, but the air currents generated from its attacks made the sand and snow even more intense, blurring its sight.

Seeing this, Hei Lou Lan laughed cruelly, ordering: "Third step!"

This time, almost ten people charged into the battlefield.

Every one of them was an expert, there was Bian Si Xuan, Hao Ji Liu, Pei Yan Fei, Gao Yang, Shu Zai, Dou E, Nie Ya Qing, Tao You, Lu Shuang...

These Gu Masters were either rank four peak stage or rank five experts.

Adding in Gu Guo Long and Xi Xue, they were truly a powerful formation.

They drilled into the snow and sand, attacking furiously towards the flying bear phantom.

The flying bear phantom roared continuously, it was very agitated and attacked randomly, but had little effect.

On the other hand, the Gu Masters had used their investigative Gu worms from the start, their vision was clear as they constantly avoided the bear while unleashing strong attacks.

Pei Yan Fei grew wings as his swallow wings were like scissors tearing through the sky.

Swallow wings Gu.

Golden coat Gu.

Rainbow transformation Gu.

Killer move — Golden Rainbow Strike!

He turned into a golden flash of lightning as he charged down with fierce crackling.

The flying bear roared in pain, blood was spewing as a huge injury appeared on its chest, from the left shoulder to its right waist.

Nie Ya Qing followed closely after.

He was a rank five Gu Master, using the iron hook silver slash Gu.

His palm formed into an eagle claw shape as he aimed at the flying bear phantom, slashing with his fingers.

Immediately, several flashes appeared in the air, some were as dark as steel while some were shining like silver.

His claws continued to tear at the sky, as countless flashes attacked the flying bear phantom's eyes, nose, and mouth.

Nie Ya Qing attacked its weak points, causing the flying bear to take the hit passively.

"Overlapping shadow." Bian Si Xuan shouted lightly, as the shadow sword in her hand waved.

A dark sword shadow flew several hundred steps and attacked the flying bear's right leg noiselessly, leaving a ten meter long wound.

"Protect me." Ye Lui Sang shouted, raising both his palms as a fireball appeared above him, growing and expanding at a rapid speed.

The fireball became larger and larger, as the battlefield was dyed red, the light from the fireball could not be concealed by the snow and sand.

The flying bear felt the danger too and struggled, charging towards Ye Lui Sang who was in the air.

But the next moment, it was attacked by Dou E, Gu Guo Long, and Tao You.

Dou E was a transformation path Gu master, turning into a giant crocodile as he battled and retreated.

He opened his mouth, shooting out his teeth one by one.

The teeth hit the flying bear's body and were embedded into it, in a few breath's time, they exploded, causing the flying bear's body to be covered in flesh and blood.

Gu Guo Long waved his sleeve and dozens of Gu worms flew out.

These Gu worms landed on the ground, causing the earth to grow into a mound.

The mound broke and rockmen-like giant statues appeared, standing up and attacking the flying bear phantom.

Tao You was an earth path Gu Master.

But he and Gu Guo Long had different methods, he continued to absorb the earth energy as he gathered it into himself.

Next, he punched consecutively, with each punch shooting out earth energy. Flying in the air, they transformed into meteors and crashed onto the flying bear's body.

Bam bam bam...

As the intense meteors collided, the flying bear's attacks towards Ye Lui Sang slowed.

Finally, Ye Lui Sang was finished with his charging and he pressed his palms down, as a giant fireball was sent down like a descending mountain, hitting the huge flying bear phantom without regard for its welfare.

Bam——!

With an intense explosion, ears were deafened.

The intense wind stirred, spreading everywhere, blowing the snow and sand away to the edge of the battlefield.

The Gu Masters who were there were blown by the intense winds, getting shocked as their clothes and hair were pulled along by the wind.

When the dust settled, a huge crater formed on the battlefield.

All around the deep crater, a sand-like surface could be seen due to the strong heat from the fire.

The flying bear phantom was curled up into a ball, making no sounds. Its body was covered in five lights that were interchanging, black, white, red, yellow, and azure.

Rank five — five element bear skin Gu.

This Gu could greatly reduce the damage from metal, wood, water, fire, and earth path Gu worms, but under the attacks of so many experts, the flying bear's body was covered in injuries as blood spewed everywhere, and some injuries were so deep bones could be seen.

Gu Masters were standing at the edge of the crater, watching the flying bear.

Although the flying bear was strong, after two rounds of battle, such results had been obtained.

"Be careful, do not forget that it still has the grand chaotic dance Gu." Sun Shi Han reminded.

The Gu Masters had a serious expression as some nodded lightly.

Grand chaotic dance Gu was a rank five Gu, it could cause the flying bear to go into a frenzied state, increasing its strength and speed greatly, at the same time its four limbs could be twisted at will.

Once this wild Gu was activated, the flying bear's danger level would surge, if one was not careful and got caught, they might be turned into meat paste in no more than a few breath's time.

"What's there to be afraid of, don't forget we have Old Sir Tai Bai here, whoever charges first will be heavily rewarded by me!" Hei Lou Lan shouted, his promise of rewards made the Gu Master's eyes shine brightly.

When great rewards are offered, brave people emerge.

"I'll do it!" Hao Ji Liu shouted, whipping up a wave as he charged towards the flying bear.

Under everyone's gazes, he advanced towards the flying bear quickly.

A thousand steps, five hundred steps, three hundred steps!

The flying bear suddenly raised its head, its eyes were blood red as it growled loudly, shooting out an invisible air bubble.

The bubble expanded at lightning speed, covering both Hao Ji Liu and the flying bear, as it contracted quickly and vanished completely.

In an instant, the flying bear and Hao Ji Liu both vanished!

Chapter 584: Demise of Water Demon, Fang Yuan’s enlightening words

With such a sudden event, everyone's expressions changed.

"What happened? Where did they go?"

"He vanished!"

"Don't tell me this round has some secret behind it?"

Everyone was guessing as they discussed among themselves.

Hei Lou Lan was frowning, feeling very perplexed.

Sun Shi Han's expression was grim and uncertain, he seemed to have thought of something as he spoke in a hesitant manner: "Is it the battle space Gu?"

"Battle space Gu?" At once, everyone's attention was focused on Sun Shi Han.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes shone with brilliance as he said deeply: "This is indeed a space path Gu worm, but if it is the battle space Gu, then elder Hao Ji Liu is in trouble."

"Battle space Gu vanished for so many years, to think it would reappear here today." Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed, it seemed he had confirmed it.

He had obtained an Immortal inheritance from the old beggar, he naturally had great knowledge.

"What is the battle space Gu?" Everyone asked.

Ye Lui Sang's gaze was grave, he was the current tribe leader of Ye Lui tribe, a super tribe, but because they lost, he had to join Hei tribe.

He owned a mysterious fire path Immortal Gu, he was well-learnt and had a wealth of knowledge, at this point, he started explaining: "The battle space Gu is a rank five space path Gu worm. Once activated, it can send both the enemy and the user into a unique space. In there, they will fight to the death, so only when the winner is decided, or when the time runs out, would they be released from that space."

"Sigh, to think that the flying bear had such a Gu worm hidden!" Hei Lou Lan sighed as he looked at the sky, speaking with a hateful tone.

Everyone's expression was grim as ever, expressing their worry towards Hao Ji Liu's safety.

The flying bear phantom was so strong, even with everyone's combined strength, they could not kill it, how could Hao Ji Liu face it all on his own?

The result of this match could be easily predicted by anyone — the flying bear wins and Hao Ji Liu loses.

Although Hao Ji Liu had first rate escaping methods like water image Gu, Ye Lui Sang had already said that the space created by battle space Gu would only close when one side has a clear victory, decided by life and death.

Even if Hao Ji Liu used all his escaping methods, he would be captured and killed by the flying bear phantom eventually.

Unless he had an opposing space path Gu.

But Hao Ji Liu was a water path Gu Master, everyone knew that.

Even among all the experts present, none of them were in the space path, thus there was nothing they could do to the battle space Gu.

"Maybe there is still some hope, tribe leader Ye Lui Sang said earlier that 'only when the winner is decided, or when the time runs out', this 'time runs out' means?" Tang Miao Ming asked.

Ye Lui Sang sighed deeply: "Sigh, this time restriction is for Gu Masters. To maintain the battle space Gu, primeval essence will be expended constantly. If a Gu Master uses it, the battle space would vanish when their primeval essence is completely used up."

At this point, everyone lost their hope.

The flying bear phantom's battle space Gu was a wild Gu.

Wild Gu absorbed the primeval energy in the air, and as the primeval energy in the air was continuously supplied, there was no way for the 'time limit' to end.

"If we can absorb all the primeval energy in the air, would that work?" Bian Si Xuan gave a very good suggestion, everyone's eyes were shining.

But it was no use.

After discussing for a while, everyone found that to deal with the invisible and formless primeval energy, qi path methods were required.

But qi path was an ancient path, it had once flourished but had been replaced later by the rising strength path.

By now, strength path had declined, not to mention qi path.

Qi path had been near extinction for a long time.

It was extremely rare to see a qi path Gu Master.

Even though Tai Bai Yun Sheng had roamed northern plains for so many years, he had only see three qi path cultivators. The most recent one, who was also the strongest, was Liu Wen Wu's sworn brother — the variant human Mo Shi Kuang.

But this person had followed Liu Wen Wu since long ago, he was part of Liu tribe, why would he serve under Hei Lou Lan?

Even if he could help, he was an attack type Gu Master, he might not have the ability to deal with the primeval energy. In any case, no one could enter Imperial Court blessed land anymore at this point.

"Qi path is not the most important. The most crucial thing is to break the connection between the primeval energy and battle space Gu, we do not need to get rid of the primeval energy in this area." Tai Bai Yun Sheng said as he stroked his beard.

But this was something no one could do.

Breaking the connection between the primeval energy and wild Gu was the signature ability of restriction path.

Restriction path was also a rare path, there were very few restriction path Gu Masters.

Among everyone present, no one was a restriction path Gu Master.

"Sigh, earlier when I obtained a high grade evaluation and entered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's treasure room, I found the restriction path primeval break Gu, it could be used in this scenario. But who could I have predicted this, I ended up exchanging something else." Lui Shuang patted his thigh, expressing his regret.

Fang Yuan was folding his arms, expression and not speaking as he stood at one side.

"Think harder, there has to be a way." Hei Lou Lan had just spoken, when the space shook, the huge body of the flying bear phantom appearing before them.

It opened its mouth and roared, showing its frenzy nature.

Everyone's heart sank, quickly looking for Hao Ji Liu's traces.

If he is alive they must see him, if he is dead they must at least see the corpse, but they could not find it anywhere.

"Quick, look at the flying bear's mouth!" Sun Shi Han was an investigative Gu Master, he was the first to find the trace.

Everyone looked over and saw that the flying bear's mouth had traces of blood, and there were some cloth stuck in between its teeth.

This cloth was very familiar to them, everyone pondered about it and quickly realized, wasn't this Hao Ji Liu's clothing?

They understood at once.

Hao Ji Liu was eaten by the flying bear!

What a pity for Hao Ji Liu, the great demonic path expert, known as the "Water Demon", displaying great brilliance in the Imperial Court contest, yet he died at this very place.

Fate was full of uncertainty, the cruelty of reality made everyone feel a strong sense of pity and dread.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng could do nothing either.

Although he had man as before Gu, but it needed a target to use it on, right now Hao Ji Liu's corpse was chewed up by the flying bear, and swallowed into its stomach.

How could he be saved?

The Gu Masters' morale fell.

"The flying bear phantom is too ferocious, how can we fight it?"

"It is so cramped inside the battle space, the flying bear has the five element bear skin Gu, wind tiger cloud dragon Gu, star river Gu, and grand chaotic dance Gu, if we fought it alone, who could be its match?"

"We could never have expected this final round to be difficult to this degree!"

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's rounds got harder towards the later stages, and the final, hundredth round was the hardest.

Right now Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had already created more than ten floors, the Gu Masters were working hard to clear all the rounds for rewards, but most of them were stuck at the ninetieth or so round.

This final round was the first one everyone had arrived at.

"Damn it, morale is so low, it is hard to fight anymore, do we return empty handed this time?" Hei Lou Lan's expression was grim.

This time, they created a huge party for this challenge, yet they lost an expert without gaining anything. This was a huge blow to his reputation and prestige.

Disregarding that, what Hei Lou Lan wanted was a strength path Immortal Gu, meaning he needed a one-edge owner token.

If he could not clear this floor, he would only have an ordinary edgeless owner token.

If he gave up on this floor and chose other floors to challenge, he would need to expend a lot of time.

Time waits for no man, and this too went for him, Hei Lou Lan!

Just as the troop's morale was sinking, Fang Yuan slowly said with a calm expression: "What difficulty is there in killing the flying bear?"

Once he said so, dozens of gazes turned around to look at him.

But soon, they lowered their gazes.

Wolf King was no longer the Wolf King in the rumors.

In the past, Wolf King Chang Shan Yin was a great heroic character in northern plains, a legend who exterminated Ha Tu Gu and his band of bandits.

The current Wolf King was a flying and enslavement master, the number one fierce general publicly recognised in this current Imperial Court contest. During the final battle, he took down the enemy's commander easily from amidst the army, showing his great strength!

He had become even more arrogant and aloof, even becoming cruel and ruthless, striking as a means of persuasion. Hei Xiu Yi who was nearly killed by him was a prime example.

Looking back in time, there was another example, Sun Shi Han.

He had once been attacked by Chang Shan Yin in public, his entire face was trampled on the ground under everyone's watchful eye, he had lost all his pride and face.

Only Hei Lou Lan's gaze approached him, only the 'Black Tyrant' had no fear towards the unrestrained and arrogant Chang Shan Yin.

"Brother Shan Yin, I would like to hear your brilliant plan!" Hei Lou Lan cupped his fists.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly: "It is not a brilliant plan, there is no harm in saying it."

He paused before saying: "This battle space Gu is quite special, but it is only rank five, there has to be restrictions on it, particularly in range. In my opinion, as long as we fight it from afar and avoid the range of battle space Gu's effect, we will be fine."

Hei Lou Lan was shocked, these words truly made him feel as though he was waking up from a dream!

Everyone's eyes were shining, some patted their head as they said excitedly: "I was too frightened by battle space Gu's reputation."

Indeed, any Gu worm had its range of effect.

The battle space Gu's range should not be wide, otherwise, it would not have waited for Hao Ji Liu to get close before activating it.

Of course, battle space Gu was a wild Gu, so the range had to be assessed more carefully.

"Next, I will manipulate the wolf group and encircle the flying bear, you guys will attack from afar using long range methods." Fang Yuan commanded.

Hei Lou Lan was overjoyed, he could not command Fang Yuan to move, now that Fang Yuan was voluntarily entering battle, he quickly said: "We will do as Wolf King says!"

Battle ensued again.

The wolf group was inside trapping the flying bear. The Gu Masters were outside unleashing a rain of attacks from afar.

Like this, the scene of a group of ants eating an elephant was formed.

Flying bear roared continuously, using star river Gu, wind tiger cloud dragon Gu, grand chaotic dance Gu and others, causing great casualties to the wolf group.

In contrast, the Gu Masters were all safe and sound, no more deaths occurred.

Hei Lou Lan was initially afraid of Fang Yuan withdrawing due to huge casualties in the wolf group.

But Fang Yuan showed a strong attitude, he did not retreat even though he was having losses, he even disregarded the wolf corpses.

Hei Lou Lan was perplexed, but after thinking about it, he attributed Fang Yuan's reason for not retreating no matter what to his earlier promise — once they cleared this, Wolf King would get fifty percent of the reward!

What he did not know was, Fang Yuan's true motive was his owner token.

Hei Lou Lan wanted to elevate his owner token, that suited Fang Yuan's interests, after his owner token becomes four-edge, Fang Yuan would snatch it away and form the ten-edge owner token, obtaining a Giant Sun true inheritance.

Because of Fang Yuan's intervention, the scales of victory tilted towards the Gu Masters.

Flying bear's injuries became heavier, as blood flowed down the mound like a waterfall.

Roar!

Suddenly, the flying bear roared again, shooting out another invisible bubble.

The rank five battle space Gu was activated once again.

The Gu Masters were prepared for this, retreating quickly, but the bubble was targeted at a blood forest wolf.

Swoosh.

With a light sound, the flying bear and the blood forest wolf vanished.

"Using the same move again, what's the use?" Someone saw this and laughed.

"As long as we do not get closer, why would we be afraid of the battle space Gu? Hahaha!"

"All of you shut up!" Hei Lou Lan screamed furiously, showing a very annoyed and irritated expression.

Not just him, Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the others also had a grim expression.

Chapter 585: Finally getting through, Fang Yuan requests for an Immortal Gu

This time, the battle space lasted much longer than before, lasting half a day before it dispersed. The hill-sized giant flying bear phantom appeared once again before everyone.

"Damn it, just like we thought!" Sun Shi Han cried out involuntarily.

"Hmph!" Hei Lou Lan was also not looking well.

There were no injuries on the flying bear phantom's body, a dazzling halo flowing through its snow-white fur. Its eyes were bright and its battle intent soared high; it had seemingly made a complete recovery

Flying bear had a rank five healing Gu which had already been investigated clearly.

As for its opponent - the blood forest wolf - which had been pulled into the battle space, only a pile of white bones remained.

"Can we still fight it?" Even Pei Yan Fei with his raging battle intent, felt indecisive at this moment.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng stroked his beard and muttered: "No matter how serious the flying bear phantom's injuries are, as long as it uses battle space Gu to enter the battle space, it can recover back to its prime state in half a day. And during this time, we can do nothing but to just look on."

"Right, battle space Gu might only be a wild Gu and not under the flying bear's control, but a wild Gu's sense of danger is very sharp, and when it senses danger, it will casually choose a target to pull into the battle space to protect its host."

"Doesn't this mean the wolf groups also cannot be used? Wolf groups have to engage in close combat, surrounding the flying bear, aren't they just the best targets to pull into the battle space?"

"Looks like only us Gu Masters should attack now!"

When someone said this, the scene suddenly quietened.

Throwing out the wolf groups and making Gu Masters assault the flying bear phantom was also not feasible!

The flying bear could quickly pull a Gu Master into the battle space. The Gu Master was sure to struggle bitterly to their last breath, using every method they had to keep on living.

There was a very simple way to break the battle space and not give the flying bear enough time to heal: the Gu Master that was pulled in to the battle space needed to immediately suicide.

But no one would want to kill themselves, survival instinct was human nature.

Even Tai Bai Yun Sheng would not be able to save them; Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's bloody tragedy was a clear example of it.

"The final round is really too difficult. We have gathered so many people with many heroes, but we are actually helpless against this flying bear phantom with our combined strength!"

Flying bear quietly lied down on the ground, vigilantly looking at the crowd. It did not attack and only let out low roars.

"It should not be like this, the crucial thing is we have no way to restrain battle space Gu. We don't have methods of restriction path and qi path."

"Hei tribe leader, I suggest we change the strategy." Ye Lui Sang was also a tribe leader of a super force, others might not dare to speak up, but he could talk bluntly.

Hei Lou Lan gave a snort but did not reply.

His thoughts moved like lightning: 'Looking at this situation, it is almost impossible to resolve the problem of battle space Gu. It seems like there is only one way, that is for me to go into battle and make the flying bear pull me into the battle space. In the battle space, I can use my strength path killer move and kill the flying bear!"

His strength path killer move was extremely powerful, it was a secret technique of Hei tribe.

Hei Lou Lan could not take care of the flying bear with just the dark path cultivation which he showed on the surface. But if he used his strength path abilities, with the amplification from his Great Strength True Martial Physique, it would not be difficult for him to kill the flying bear.

But if he did so, he would be breaking the sealing effect of Immortal Gu Dark Limit, which would quicken the appearance of the disaster of one of the ten extreme physiques.

"The time I have is already not enough, now if I use my strength path killer move to kill the flying bear, this time will shorten even more. And in this short period of time, I still need to attack another floor, clear a hundred rounds and obtain a strength path Immortal Gu, this difficulty is too large!"

"But if I don't cross this round, I won't have a one-edge owner token, so how could I know about the position of the strength path Immortal Gu? Whether I change the strategy or ask for support from the tribe, they both require time!"

"The worst situation will be if I use the strength path killer move, kill this flying bear, obtain a one-edge owner token, but there is no strength path Immortal Gu in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building..."

Hei Lou Lan was hesitating.

This matter concerned his life and death while the path ahead was filled with darkness, even he could not avoid being indecisive and helpless.

"It is not difficult to break the battle space."

One astonishing sentence resounded in the place.

Everyone followed the voice towards its source; it was none other than Wolf King once again.

"Brother Shan Yin, you have another method?" Hei Lou Lan immediately asked.

Fang Yuan smiled: "I should also be making an all-out effort for the fifty-percent reward, right? My plan is divided into three steps. First, we will use long-range methods to exhaust the flying bear's energy as much as possible. Second, we will send a death warrior to engage in close combat; he will have to immediately suicide if he is pulled into the battle space. Third, the flying bear will have no time to take a breather, and we continue with long-range battle; we will definitely be able to kill this beast once we maintain this plan!"

"Good plan!"

"How could I have not thought of it?"

Some people cheered; some people slapped their thighs loudly in pleasant surprise; while some people inwardly muttered of this plan's cruelty.

But no matter what they commented, everyone knew this method could solve the problem.

In northern plains where battles occurred frequently, every single tribe possessed death warriors; it was only a matter of whether they had many or few, whether they were elites or ordinary.

Hei tribe was a super force, the death warriors they cultivated were not only many in number, but were also elites.

"This way..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng slightly frowned, disturbed by this plan.

Sun Shi Han's eyes flashed with brilliance as he looked at Hei Lou Lan without speaking.

Dying in battle and taking the initiative to throw away one's life were two completely different concepts.

The former was the honor of the brave, while the latter was those in power bringing disaster to other's lives for their benefits.

If this plan was really to be carried out, Hei Lou Lan, this Hei tribe leader's reputation would be completely destroyed.

This was against the values of the righteous path.

Being in the righteous path, their biggest concern was reputation.

Those with bad reputation would have a limited achievement in the righteous path. Demonic path was different, no matter what the reputation was, its main value was strength! Thus, within the demonic path, there was the plague-like Hao Ji Liu, as opposed to the life-savior Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Because of this, Sun Shi Han did not attempt to advise this matter.

He was a smart man and knew no matter how he said it or persuaded, it would not be appropriate.

He had even thought of this method earlier, but did not suggest it.

He did not dare.

The current Sun Shi Han was already an external elder of Hei tribe. Once he suggested this, it would be asking to soil his reputation, would he still be able to stay with Hei tribe then?

"Probably only this sinister and cruel Wolf King can say it without any misgivings." Sun Shi Han secretly glanced at Fang Yuan with hatred and fear, his cheeks seemingly twitching in pain.

But what Sun Shi Han did not know was — to Hei Lou Lan, what use would reputation be when his own life was about to be over?!

When Hei Lou Lan heard Fang Yuan's plan, he immediately decided to use it.

But he still frowned and thought for a long while, hesitating, pitifully sighing and showing a profound 'merciful' expression. Finally, he heaved a long sigh and spoke a pile of erudite words.

The main idea was: They were forced to use this plan. The tribesmen who die will be given grand burial by him as a brother, and he will personally take care of their family, give compensation, and so on.

Everyone knew it, but they could not point it out, this was the game rule of the righteous path.

After going through this process, Hei Lou Lan immediately summoned Hei tribe's death warriors to enter the battle.

These death warriors from Hei tribe were all of rank two cultivation and had been brought up by Hei tribe since youth, imbued day and night with the ideology of loyalty to the tribe.

As for rank three death warriors, it was not that there were none of them. But once they reach rank three, they would become a precious resource and almost every one of them would be free from the status of a death warrior.

Only super forces would have a number of death warriors of rank three and even rank four cultivation, but they would not use them so lightly.

Hei Lou Lan was this generation's Hei tribe leader and if he sent these death warriors to their deaths, they could not refuse him.

If the emperor wants his subjects dead, the subjects need to die no matter what, regardless of their will!

This was the system.

The following battle went without any accidents.

The battle persisted till more than ten death warriors were sacrificed, and the flying bear phantom finally collapsed on the ground, breathing its last.

But when everyone wanted to deliver the final strike, they suddenly discovered they could not even budge.

"What is happening?!"

"It is Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's power making us not able to move!"

"This, isn't this too shameless. Only a move more and we could kill this flying bear!"

Everyone shouted and raged at this stupefying situation.

Only Fang Yuan's expression was tranquil, he had a six-edge owner token and knew that this round was over.

Hei Lou Lan also felt this and immediately took out his owner token, fixing his gaze at it and saw an edge gradually emerging from the originally round owner token.

At the same time, a strong sense of fortune entered the depths of his heart, letting him know that he was in full control of this floor.

'So we had no need to kill the flying bear in this final round and only needed to beat it to near death!' Hei Lou Lan was exulted inwardly, but showed a mournful expression on his face, sighing, "Everyone, do not fret, the battle has ended, we were successful, this round is crossed. Sigh... what happened to my Hei tribe's children was truly a pity. If not for the battle space isolating the connection between the inside and outside, I would have definitely used puppets or wild Gu to replace them."

"Passed... we passed?" Everyone was shocked and excited.

"Tribe leader Hei Lou Lan, I wonder what the rewards for this round are? Is it possible to let this old man broaden his horizons." Tai Bai Yun Sheng inquired. The motive for him entering Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was lifespan Gu. However, lifespan Gu was rare and precious and could only appear as the rewards for ninetieth or above rounds.

Hei Lou Lan revealed a peculiar expression at the inquiry and pointed at the dying flying bear phantom: "That is this round's reward."

"What?"

"This flying bear phantom?"

"How could it be?"

Everyone was shocked once again, only Fang Yuan knew clearly.

He possessed a six-edge owner token, and knew the rewards for any round of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's current floors like the back of his palm. Before even tackling this round, he knew of this round's reward - it was a rank six phantom path Immortal Gu with a simple to understand name - flying bear phantom Gu.

Sure enough, at the next moment, under everyone's astonished gazes, the dying giant flying bear gradually turned into an enormous ball of white light.

The white light shrunk rapidly, finally turning into a speck of light that flew towards Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan quickly received it and carefully observed it.

He was the master of the owner token, the reward for passing this round was his. He had just come into contact with this flying bear phantom Gu, but easily refined it because of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's power.

Fang Yuan's six-edge owner token was different. It was created from exploitation and could only receive the floor's rewards after taking control of the floor. Naturally, it was not like it could not contest against Hei Lou Lan's owner token, but once they contested, Giant Sun's will would awaken which would cause a great loss to him, or even face a tragic end.

This risk was better not taken if possible.

Flying bear phantom Gu was looking very dim, its aura was weak like it was near death, its condition was extremely poor.

But Hei Lou Lan was unable to take his eyes off it. What was this?

'This is an Immortal Gu!'

He had just sighed with emotions inwardly when a voice sounded in his ears: "This Immortal Gu, give it to me."

The tone of the voice was flat, but it could not suppress the determination within.

Hei Lou Lan immediately frowned, he did not need to look around to know who the speaker was.

Who else had guts to mention such a request besides Wolf King Chang Shan Yin?

Chapter 586: Using flying bear, Mo Yao speaks of phantom path

When Fang Yuan publicly requested the flying bear phantom Gu, Hei Lou Lan's immediate reaction was to object immediately.

This was an Immortal Gu!

Even an ordinary Gu Immortal would not obtain one easily. No matter how amazing Wolf King was, he was only a mortal, he dared to make such an absurd request?!

Moreover, this flying bear phantom Gu was extremely easy to use.

With just a single thought, and a toss of the Gu, one could make the Gu worm transform into the flying bear phantom and engage in combat.

Although the flying bear phantom's battle strength was not as terrifying as the desolate beast flying bear, it definitely had half-immortal battle strength, with this Gu, one could easily dominate the mortal realm.

If during the Immortal Court contest, Hei Lou Lan had such an Immortal Gu...

There would be no place for Fang Yuan to display his abilities!

Fang Yuan opened asked for it, it was very rude. However, even though Hei Lou Lan was furious, he felt that this was only natural.

After all, only a person like Chang Shan Yin would have the guts to make such a request in public.

Looking at the flying bear phantom Gu in his hand, Hei Lou Lan slowly calmed down.

"Not good, the flying bear phantom was half beaten to death by us, this Immortal Gu's condition is extremely poor, it cannot be used now, it has to recover for some time."

"An injured Immortal Gu needs an Immortal Gu to heal it. Other than that, it can only self recover, but during that period it would need to consume lots of food, unceasingly."

"If I did not remember wrongly, this flying bear phantom Gu's food is the desolate beast flying bear's flesh and blood. This is problematic! How can I have such a thing? I have to seek help from the tribe's immortals."

The more Hei Lou Lan thought about it, the more his anger subsided.

He was of the ten extreme physique's Great Strength True Martial Physique, he needed a strength path Immortal Gu to ascend to Gu Immortal realm and escape the threat of death.

The flying bear phantom Gu was not something he needed, what he desperately wanted now was a strength path Immortal Gu.

"My most important priority at the moment is to find a strength path Immortal Gu. Immortal Gu are often only given at the final round of a floor, during the process of completing this, I will need everyone's strength."

Although Hei Lou Lan was not afraid of Chang Shan Yin, if he forcefully kept the flying bear phantom Gu, then the Wolf King would definitely become enemies with him. With that gap between them, there was no way he could utilize the Wolf King's strength again.

He might as well give this Immortal Gu to him, to exchange for his strength, and truly help and benefit Hei Lou Lan himself.

This way, Hei Lou Lan's reputation could be preserved as well, no one would say that he went back on his words.

Hei Lou Lan made many considerations, but this was only a moment in real time.

"Hmph hmph," Sun Shi Han snickered, " Lord Wolf King, this is an Immortal Gu, you want to take it just like that? My tribe leader promised you half the rewards earlier, but that does not mean we need to give you the Immortal Gu."

"It seems the lesson I gave you earlier was not enough." Fang Yuan heard this and frowned lightly, his gaze turned ice cold as his killing intent was released fully, towards Sun Shi Han.

Sun Shi Han's expression changed instantly, and he could not help but move closer to Hei Lou Lan.

No one questioned if Fang Yuan would have the guts to directly execute the killing blow.

The ferocity of Wolf King was ingrained in everyone's hearts.

"Hahaha." Hei Lou Lan laughed loudly, walking towards Fang Yuan as he patted his chest: "A true gentleman never goes back on his words! Earlier, I promised the Wolf King half the rewards, then it shall be fifty percent. It was all due to brother Shan Yin's brilliant plan that allowed us to get through this round, I will add another ten percent of reward, but the Immortal Gu is unique, its value is immeasurable, even with your sixty percent reward, in what way are you going to compensate the remaining forty percent to us?"

"That's right, we put in much effort too!"

"I have heavy injuries now, I did not retreat amidst the fierce combat, everyone can be my witness. Even Lord Water Demon Hao Ji Liu died because of this!"

"I believe Lord Wolf King will give us a good solution."

Everyone said in agreement, it was all targeted at Fang Yuan.

Even though Fang Yuan had great strength, but wealth moved people's hearts, everyone was filled with envy, jealousy and hatred upon seeing that an Immortal Gu was going to fall into his hands. Thus, they pushed all of their unhappiness towards Fang Yuan.

Under everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan frowned deeper and deeper.

Hei Lou Lan laughed secretly: "Wolf King, oh Wolf King, even with your ferocious reputation and outstanding strength, you will still eventually be captured by me."

Seven days later.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's seventh layer, the ninetieth round.

In the maze, the flying bear phantom was roaring at the sky.

Its body was covered in wounds, blood was oozing at its mouth, and several of its sharp teeth had broken. Its right eye was blinded, hanging outside its socket like a grape, it was in bad shape.

But it only had one enemy.

He was floating in the air, with six arms on his back, compared to the hill-like flying bear phantom which had a massive body, he was very small.

But the flying bear phantom was serious and vigilant like it was facing a strong enemy. After they had battled for fifteen minutes, it could deeply feel how powerful this 'tiny' enemy was.

"Flying bear phantom Gu, it is deservedly an Immortal Gu! Even after turning into the flying bear phantom, it retains much wisdom, and is quite shrewd, in the future when I face strong foes, I can use it to restrain them and that can help me save a lot of energy."

Fang Yuan looked at the flying bear phantom below him as he evaluated in his heart.

Seven days ago, Hei Lou Lan gathered the band of experts and broke through the final round of the fifth floor, obtaining the flying bear phantom Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan was blunt and unrestrained, as he immediately asked for it.

Even though the other Gu Masters were jealous and envious, trying to come up with endless excuses against this, Fang Yuan announced that he was willing to compensate the remaining half of the Gu's worth, while giving an unrelenting attitude. Eventually, Hei Lou Lan gave this Gu to Fang Yuan.

With this Gu, Fang Yuan went to Hei Lou Lan that night and borrowed resources, establishing a contract with him in secret.

After returning, he used Hu Immortal blessed land to connect to treasure yellow heaven, exchanging for the relevant Gu worms and food, and during the sixth day, the flying bear phantom Gu was restored to its healthy state.

By the seventh day, Fang Yuan secretly entered the seventh floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, personally testing the flying bear phantom Gu and the finalized killer move six arm heavenly zombie king.

Fang Yuan ordered the flying bear phantom Gu to attack him without holding back, while he himself used the six arm heavenly zombie king to fight back.

Flying bear phantom Gu was an Immortal Gu, it had half the battle strength of the flying bear, but it was not Fang Yuan's match when he was in six arm heavenly zombie king mode.

Fang Yuan was very satisfied with this result.

He thought about it in his mind: "The killer move six arm heavenly zombie king is indeed formidable! It uses borrow strength Gu as the core to borrow the natural strength of heaven, earth, fire, water and others, sustaining itself by allowing a steady and endless torrent of strength to be supplied."

"Most amazingly, it can transform my body into a zombie's body temporarily, this way, my body will be in a half-dead state, my recovery speed will increase greatly and my sense of pain will reduce, I would be in the state of near unlimited energy and strength, I can do anything!"

If it was an ordinary living body, constantly using strength would tire it out. But by becoming a heavenly zombie, Fang Yuan could avoid such a weakness.

This kind of strength and feeling was intoxicating for Fang Yuan, but it also made him more alert.

"I can only maintain this form for a short period of time, during intense battle, I will have to commit to the battle fully and I would not recognise the flow of time. Although this killer move is great and gives me a good feeling, it is easy to get addicted and lost when using it. I must never forget the time limit of this killer move, otherwise the consequences would be severe!"

The killer move six arm heavenly zombie king was powerful, but had a time limit. Once the time limit was exceeded, the Gu Master might turn into a real zombie from over usage.

The severity of this surpassed even the ten extreme physique's disaster, even if he used the yin-yang rotation Gu, he could not recover.

Fang Yuan wanted to get rid of this weakness, but Mo Yao's requirements were too strict, Fang Yuan could not find a suitable person to test the Gu.

"Actually, you have not fully unleashed the true power of this flying bear phantom Gu." At this time, Mo Yao's will in Fang Yuan's mind spoke.

"Oh, what do you mean?"

Mo Yao had some understanding regarding phantom path: "Phantom path, it focuses on the forms of phantom and solid, during the initial stage from rank one to five, phantom is the foundation, using phantom form to avoid attacks. Thus, phantom path Gu masters often lack attacking power, but have ample defensive measures. But at rank six and above, phantom path Gu Immortals have both offense and defense, by turning into phantom and solid form at will, they can go into the defensive phantom mode, nullifying all forms of attacks, and also turn phantom into solid, attacking people when they least expect it."

"The flying bear phantom Gu is a phantom path Immortal Gu, it was created by killing the desolate beast flying bear and using all of its skin, bones, flesh, blood, and soul to refine it. Just the flying bear phantom Gu alone has half the strength of the real flying bear. But if it was given accompanying Gu worms, like the battle space Gu, grand chaotic dance Gu, five element bear skin Gu and others, its battle strength would surge greatly."

Mo Yao's words made Fang Yuan nod repeatedly.

He recalled the fight when they were at the final round, precisely because of the flying bear phantom's Gu worms could it have a huge boost in battle strength, even causing the band of experts to be helpless.

But after the battle, battle space Gu was taken by Hei Lou Lan, and the remaining Gu worms were also taken by other people.

Fang Yuan was fighting the flying bear phantom alone in secret, the flying bear phantom had no Gu worms left, thus, Fang Yuan could have the upper hand when fighting.

He had some degree of comprehension in this: "Looking at it from another angle, complementing the flying bear phantom Gu with other Gu worms is exactly like using multiple Gu worms at once. Isn't this a killer move?"

Killer moves are a Gu Master's unique creation, using many Gu worms at the same time together to create an effect greater than when used individually, unleashing great strength.

Mo Yao nodded in agreement: "Your comprehension is completely right, that is so. However, what truly complements the flying bear phantom Gu are only phantom path Gu worms. Forget the rest, just a single turn phantom Gu would allow the flying bear phantom Gu to turn from solid to phantom form, evading all sorts of attacks."

"Turn phantom Gu?" Fang Yuan's heart shook uncontrollably.

He could completely imagine that when the turn phantom Gu is used with the flying bear phantom Gu, it would become an extremely troublesome enemy.

This could transform the usage of flying bear phantom Gu completely, achieving a true qualitative change to a degree.

Mo Yao laughed lightly, saying: "Lad, as long as you return Water Pavilion to Spirit Affinity House properly, I will tell you the details of three phantom path inheritances, among them, one is likely to be a phantom path Gu Immortal inheritance."

"We'll talk about that later." Fang Yuan calmed down, replying in a plain tone.

He had never removed his alertness towards Mo Yao.

Although Mo Yao did not displayed any hostile intentions, Fang Yuan had always felt a sense of danger in his heart.

Chapter 587: The vast difference between immortal and mortal

Time passed by rapidly and a month had passed.

Northern plains.

The wind raged and snow fluttered around.

The world was a scene of white as the white snow covered the large grassland. Bone chilling wind blew everywhere; occasionally, it would form into a tornado and occasionally, it would lift the deep snow on the ground.

Every ten years, the blizzard disaster devastated the whole of northern plains. Living beings lamented and all things turned destitute. At a few limited places, the surviving humans and animals were struggling for their lives.

They not only had to overcome the frigid climate, but also needed to engage in fierce combat against snow monsters and other battles.

However, in such a cruel environment, snowmen were like fish in water, moving very frequently and becoming extremely lively.

The ice cold blizzard was merely a warm spring wind to snowmen.

They hunted in this blizzard, and large numbers of wild snow path, ice path and water path Gu worms started to live one after another on their body.

The snowmen tribes who were hunted by the Gu Masters, beaten down and sold during normal times, were now experiencing enormous growth. Their forces expanded rapidly.

In the raging blizzard, two dark figures appeared.

The dark figures stood on a cliff, overflowing with immortal aura; they were Hei tribe's two Gu Immortals — Hei Bai and Hei Cheng.

They looked down towards the valley under them.

The blizzard was still wild, but it was not even able to sway the two's clothes. The snow fluttered madly, but was not able to obstruct the two's probing gazes.

In the valley, many ice houses were built, packed together with the numbers reaching several tens of thousands.

A group of heroic snowmen warriors had just returned from their hunt. They had returned with great harvests once again.

Rank six wood path Gu Immortal Hei Bai frowned: "Hmph, this group of snowmen is taking advantage of this time period to grow so rapidly! In these three days, this is already the seventh tribe we have seen of such a scale."

Those who are not my race have different motives, although snowmen had men in their name, they were still variant humans.

When the blizzard ends, northern plains' tribes would actively start developing which was bound to result in many large battles with these snowmen.

To human tribes, such a large number of snowmen meant their enemy was more in number and stronger.

Hei Cheng patted Hei Bai's shoulder, smiling: "Virtuous brother should be happy. Looking at it from another angle, these snowmen are our wealth! We can take these snowmen as captives and not only exchange them for immortal essence stones with other Gu Immortals, we can also give Xue Song Zi something to cry about."

The corners of Hei Bai's lips raised to an arc: "Elder brother thinks in a comprehensive way. If not for Xue Song Zi, the wooden chicken Gu would have already been in my hands. And he even meddled in the last Imperial Court contest. These days, we have been hunting snowmen everywhere and selling them in treasure yellow heaven. Hehehe, I really want to see how Xue Song Zi's expression is like now."

But the moment he finished saying this, his smile disappeared and his gaze revealed a trace of anxiety: "Elder brother, Hei Lou Lan has already been in Imperial Court for so long, and according to the time, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building should have already formed over twenty floors. Why is there still no trace of wooden chicken Gu?"

Hei Cheng laughed: "Do not fret, do not fret. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has altogether eighty-eight floors, this is not much. Hei Lou Lan, this kid might have a irascible temper, but he is meticulous when it comes to the big picture. He hasn't broken off the contact with us since he entered Imperial Court, isn't that right? Moreover, he now already has one-edge owner token, as long as wooden chicken Gu is involved in the creation of a new floor, Hei Lou Lan can sense it, and we will receive the news."

Hei tribe was a super force, although they did not have ability in exploiting the flaws that could match the level of Fairy Mo Yao, they had their own ways to use Gu worms to transfer messages inside and out.

Hei Bai sighed: "Imperial Court blessed land and northern plains' outside world have differing time flow. A day here in the outside world is equal to over twenty days in Imperial Court blessed land. I am somewhat worried Hei Lou Lan's notice will be late, and if so, the help we can provide will be small."

Hei Cheng comforted with a smile: "Virtuous brother, the more you worry, the more frantic you will get. Relax, according to Hei Lou Lan's strength, getting through three or four floors would not be a problem. Before this, we'd better take care of this group of snowmen."

"Okay." Hei Bai's worry was slightly relieved, as he nodded.

The two shot down like lightning, directly charging into the snowman tribe within the valley.

Hei Cheng chuckled.

Instantly, an unrestrained laughter shook the world, stopping even the moving clouds! The whole valley buzzed from the tremor and the majestic snowfall also slowed.

Crash crash crash....

The soundwave swept through the valley, crushing countless ice buildings into fine powder.

The snowman tribe instantly suffered serious losses!

"Enemy attack! Enemy attack!"

"A strong enemy has appeared. Warriors, it is time to protect our homeland!!"

"Protect our homeland. Remember, we cannot fall down, behind us are our wives, children and parents!"

Snowmen were in an uproar, and after a short moment of panic, they prepared to resist.

"Hmph, overestimating your strength." Hei Bai looked at the snowmen flocking together while floating in midair, his gaze apathetic like he was looking at a group of ants.

He lightly waves his sleeve - buzzz buzzz buzzz.....

A black mass of Gu groups flew out. First the number was in hundreds, then thousands, then it reached tens of thousands.

Finally, the several hundreds of thousands of Gu hovered over the valley like dark clouds pressing down on a city.

The snowmen looked at the sky, their expression filled with terror and lifelessness. The fighting spirit and heroic feelings they raised up just a moment ago, froze completely in front of a Gu Immortal's might.

At this moment, they were truly able to feel the bone-piercing chill of the blizzard.

Gu Immortals possessed immortal essence, a bead of immortal essence could be regarded as unlimited primeval essence. This meant every single Gu Immortal could control large numbers of mortal Gu, and would never be lacking in primeval essence.

The snowman tribes might be flourishing, but in front of a Gu Immortal's battle strength, they were like lambs waiting for slaughter and could only let themselves be trampled upon.

Next moment, Hei Bai lightly pointed and the Gu groups pounced down loudly.

Mournful sounds started resounding and echoing endlessly in the valley.

A dozen or so days later...

Imperial Court blessed land.

Hei Lou Lan slowly put down the letter Gu in his hand, sneering.

The letter Gu came from Hei tribe' Gu Immortal, its content was the same as before, still urging Hei Lou Lan to speed up the search for wooden chicken Gu.

There was originally no way to send messages from or to Imperial Court blessed land, but after so many years had gone by, even if it was an arrangement by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, it could not stand the erosion of the river of time, and a few flaws appeared.

Although they did not have capability in exploiting this on Fairy Mo Yao's level, the super forces like Hei tribe and Liu tribe had polished the methods to send the message.

"Once a Gu Master advances to an immortal, their physique would thoroughly raise to a higher level and would possess immortal essence. Mortals simply cannot be an immortal's opponent, to deal with Gu Immortal requires a Gu Immortal!"

"Strength path Immortal Gu..."

Hei Lou Lan softly muttered then slowly stood up from his seat and walked towards the window.

He looked up at the gorgeous aurora moving at the summit of the sacred palace. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's newest floor had condensed at this moment.

"Thirty-eighth floor." Hei Lou Lan sighed. Having seen this scene so many times, he no longer had the excitement like before when he saw it for the first time. But his esteem towards Old Ancestor Giant Sun, had now reached the level of prostrating himself in admiration before the old ancestor's heavenly methods every time he saw the scene of True Yang Building condensing a floor.

"Only with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and Old Ancestor Giant Sun's power, I can take my revenge!" Hei Lou Lan took out his owner token.

So much time had passed by but his owner token was still one-edge owner token.

Hei Lou Lan knew of history and also knew his own strength.

The current forces, compared to the past winners of the Imperial Court contest, were not bad but also could not be considered too good. Taking everything into account, it was only enough to cross three-four floors.

Hei Lou Lan wanted to acquire his strength path Immortal Gu, but also had the tribe responsibility of getting wooden chicken Immortal Gu. This meant the quota for two clearances was already filled.

Hence, these days, he restrained himself from taking action, making recuperation his priority, and at the same time, he still opened up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, letting Gu Masters increase their strength as much as possible.

Naturally, he did this to make the Gu Masters, outside of Hei tribe, thankful and admire him. And naturally, many among Hei tribe were dissatisfied and puzzled by it, but mindful of Black Tyrant's fierce reputation, none dared to speak up.

"Messenger." Hei Lou Lan softly called.

His trusted aide Hei Shu immediately appeared before him and quietly kneeled down, speaking with a lowered head: "Lord tribe leader, please instruct."

"How is the recent situation?" Hei Lou Lan rubbed the owner token, his gaze still at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"The situation looks to be steady recently, but undercurrents are starting to surge. Chang tribe's Gu Masters have repeatedly been killed, many Gu Masters have mysteriously disappeared when going out. Chang tribe leader Chang Ji You has personally moved out, searching everywhere to capture the killers, but no gains have been made. Instead, the attacks on Chang tribe's Gu Masters have become even more serious." Hei Shu reported.

"Eh, who has such guts?"

Hei Shu revealed an ashamed expression: "Subordinate is still investigating."

Hei Lou Lan slightly nodded, his tone revealing some slight joy in another's calamity: "No need to hurry, hehe, we shouldn't hurry in this matter. Chang Shan Yin's actions are too sinister and cruel, losing favour with people, and now he is tasting the bitter consequences. A few months ago, he wiped out the earth chief beast group and assigned Chang tribe's Gu Masters to capture many Gu Masters, and he actually killed all of them! Hmph, this had already aroused public anger, but fearing Wolf King's reputation, no one dared to take actions though they had the heart for revenge."

Hei Lou Lan remembered this clearly.

Because, among these unlucky Gu Masters Fang Yuan captured to do experiments on, were some people who had some relations to Hei Lou Lan.

Wolf King actually did not give him face and killed these people; Hei Lou Lan had secretly been bearing this grudge all this time.

"Tribe leader is wise, subordinate and others also think this is the case." Hei Shu flattered and said in agreement, "Chang tribe leader might be Chang Ji You, but he is Wolf King's son and was appointed as the tribe leader with one sentence from Wolf King. He is too young and cannot appease the tribesmen. The whole of Chang tribe's affairs actually lie with Chang Ji You's godfather Chang Biao."

"But not long ago, the death of the two lords Chang Biao and Pan Ping while roaming seventh floor's ninetieth round, had spread. There was an indistinct commotion within Chang tribe and Chang Ji You has been finding it hard to maintain Chang tribe's situation. The avenger saw this great opportunity, and maybe because they had received a great increase in strength from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's rewards, they have been killing Chang tribe's Gu Masters everywhere."

"Hmm." Hei Lou Lan nodded, Hei Shu's analysis was similar to his own thoughts.

　　

"Quickly investigate this person. Taking revenge wholeheartedly in spite of Wolf King's fierceness, this is bravery. Killing Chang tribe's Gu Masters and not being found even after so many days, this is scheming. This person is brave and can scheme, they should be taken into my Hei tribe. And also, only my Hei tribe can protect their life." Hei Lou Lan instructed.

"Yes, lord."

"Are there any movements from Chang Shan Yin?"

"Ever since Chang Biao's corpse was found and delivered to Chang tribe, maybe Wolf King found some clues from the corpse, he entered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building that very day and has yet to come out now. Subordinate had sent people to inquire, Wolf King should have gone to seventh floor's ninetieth maze round. Ever since he entered, people have often reported hearing the howls of wolf groups." Hei Shu reported.

Hei Lou Lan frowned.

Chang Biao, Pan Ping and Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's deaths were something he had not wanted to see.

But since they were already dead, Hei Lou Lan could only accept this fact.

He could complete forecast once Wolf King exited the tower and knew of Chang tribe's misfortunes, he would fly up in rage, searching for the killer. At that time, the whole sacred palace might be turned upside down.

Hei Lou Lan was looking forward to Wolf King attracting every more public anger, but he worried Wolf King would even implicate the innocents and start massacring everywhere which would greatly weaken the forces to mobilize in passing the rounds.

Hei Lou Lan must prevent this from happening. But how to prevent it?

Hei Lou Lan fell into silence as he started thinking.

Hei Shu was calmly kneeling down, patiently waiting for Hei Lou Lan's next command.

Hei Lou Lan did not think for long before an amazed expression appeared on his face.

His gaze instantly turned sharp as he once again looked at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building on the summit of the sacred palace.

There, the thirty-ninth floor was slowly condensing into shape.

Although it had yet to form, Hei Lou Lan was able to know the Gu worms in this floor through his one-edge owner token.

'Wooden chicken Gu! Wooden chicken Gu has finally appeared!'

Hei Lou Lan's mind was shaken, but soon he calmed down and his gaze quickly moved towards Hei Shu.

"Go, summon Ma Ying Jie to see me. Immediately!"

Chapter 588: Each with their schemes

Ma Ying Jie heard the summons and quickly hurried to pay a visit.

As Hei tribe's greatest opponent — Ma tribe had suffered disastrous losses in the decisive battle. Ma tribe's experts were almost completely annihilated, but the young tribe leader Ma Ying Jie was luckily rescued and bravely rose to take the great responsibility of a tribe leader.

His original plan had been to hole up in warm pond valley and recover as much as possible. But Hei Lou Lan brought his army to the valley and forcibly annexed Ma tribe.

Thus, Ma tribe had not alternative but to follow Hei tribe to Imperial Court blessed land.

Ma Ying Jie had thought Hei Lou Lan wanted to get rid of Ma tribe's name and completely swallow Ma tribe. For this reason, he expended great effort and even accepted outsiders, giving them the surname 'Ma'.

But the situation he had anticipated never happened. Not only this, Ma tribe did not receive any severe duties from Hei Lou Lan's side even after arriving at Imperial Court blessed land, instead they were treated without discrimination. Hei Lou Lan selflessly opened up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to the public from where Ma tribe had obtained many gains. Right now, the whole of Ma tribe was able to recover favorably and the tribe's forces were prospering day by day.

However, there was no free lunch in the world, Ma Ying Jie had been on tenterhooks because of this.

With Hei Lou Lan's sudden summons, the unease in his heart immediately increased several times, reaching the extreme limit.

Hei Lou Lan smiled when he looked at Ma Ying Jie: "Ma tribe leader, has Ma tribe been well these days?"

Ma Ying Jie was on guard inwardly and immediately replied: "It is good. We must thank you, lord tribe leader, for disregarding previous enmity and being magnanimous. Ma tribe was on its last breath, but now has recovered some vitality."

"If I am not wrong, Ma tribe received help from Snowy Mountain blessed land's demonic path immortal Xue Song Zi in this contest, right?" Hei Lou Lan asked amiably.

Ma Ying Jie was tongue-tied, cold sweat started flowing down from his body, and he was not able to speak a word.

Ma tribe, who possessed Huang Jin bloodline, privately joined hands with a demonic path Gu Immortal, this undoubtedly broke the rules Ancestor Giant Sun had set.

'Is Hei Lou Lan looking to settle the score at this time? Damn it, right now, he holds the knife while I am the fish, he only needs to casually say a sentence and Ma tribe would be finished!" Ma Ying Jie was very nervous, revitalizing Ma tribe was his wish, Ma tribe was what he cherished most in his life.

"Hahaha." Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily, his laughter resounding in the study, "Ma tribe leader, no need to worry, as long as you cooperate obediently, glory and riches will come gushing forth."

"Tribe leader, please explain." Ma Ying Jie gnashed his teeth.

A wise man submits to circumstances; with such a pressing situation, he had no choice but to lower his head.

"What?"

However, Hei Lou Lan's next words shocked Ma Ying Jie, his dumbstruck expression frozen like a statue.

　　...

Snowy Mountain blessed land.

The lofty Snowy Mountain peaked through the clouds. The clear blue sky shone with dazzling brilliance.

On the fifth branch peak of the mountain range.

Within the Ice Lake Palace, a negotiation was reaching its end.

Xue Song Zi's expression was worried as he looked at Demon Lord Long Dan, saying impatiently: "Demon Lord, don't forget who it was that lent you immortal essence stones and settled your debt during your emergency. It was me! Now I have some small troubles and am asking you for help, but you are using all sorts of excuses, isn't this too disappointing? Is the grand Demon Lord Long Dan such a petty person?"

Demon Lord Long Dan sipped his tea with a smile, his tone calm: "Lord Song Zi, please speak cautiously. The friendship from before, I still remember and have not forgotten even a little. But this time, Lord Song Zi, your troubles are not small. If I helped you, it would be offending Hei tribe's Gu Immortals. My business at treasure yellow heaven has just recently taken somewhat of a turn for the better, it cannot endure such an attack."

Xue Song Zi made a living out of selling snowmen and had made a lot of wealth. But in these recent months, his business at treasure yellow heaven was intensely impacted by Hei tribe.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals wantonly hunted snowmen and sold them at low prices, destroying the established standards and benefits of selling snowmen slaves.

This was an unconventional confrontation and would implicate extensively on him. Xue Song Zi could only take up the challenge to protect his source of revenue, and was barely able to draw a stalemate against Hei tribe's Gu Immortals.

Although he had riches, but he was after all only a lone force.

To a super force like Hei tribe which had been engaging in business over thousands of years, he paled by comparison.

Thus, he was gradually unable to bear it and began to request help from the surrounding Gu Immortals.

Demon Lord Long Dan's calm appearance made Xue Song Zi angry and anxious: "Demon Lord, don't beat around the bush, speak up, how can I make you take action?"

Demon Lord Long Dan laughed heartily, his bright eyes stared at Xue Song Zi: "Lord Song Zi, I know you have a hundred year lifespan Gu in your possession. As long as you give it to me, I will definitely use all my strength to help you!"

Xue Song Zi immediately stood up from the seat and pointed at Demon Lord Long Dan: "Do you feel no shame in making such a request?"

Demon Lord Long Dan raised his brows and said with a gloomy voice: "Why would I feel shame? Who would make a move without good cause? Xue Song Zi, I persuade you to not be impulsive, if you point your finger at me again, I will start to get angry."

"Hmph." Xue Song Zi knew he was not Demon Lord Long Dan's match and lowered his finger with a snort, then he flicked his sleeve and left.

Demon Lord Long Dan also did not make him stay, looking darkly at his receding figure before letting out a snort. He had already disliked Xue Song Zi for his ordinarily arrogant attitude whilst holding plenty of spare wealth.

Back then, when he asked for immortal essence stones from Xue Song Zi, Xue Song Zi actually dared to lend at an exorbitant rate of interest.

Demon Lord Long Dan had suffered a big loss and had always been keeping it in his mind.

Xue Song Zi returned to his seventh branch peak with an ashen expression.

He sat on a mat, and with no others present, his tight expression finally relaxed as he heaved a deep sigh.

"If I had known this before, I would not have meddled in the Imperial Court contest." He regretted it deeply.

Winner takes all.

Previously, he had invested a lot in the Imperial Court contest, but received no gains. Now, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were making it difficult for him, and he was not even able to guard his own financial source which was the basis of his status.

"In the end, it is still the righteous path who are united while demonic path has separated minds. Snowy Mountain blessed land has so many demonic path Gu Immortals, but I cannot obtain the help from even one. In contrast, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals involve the assistance of many forces and are suppressing me together."

"Sigh, in this battle, my many years of accumulation have all been used up, resulting in serious losses to me. The water in the Imperial Court contest runs too deep, it is not something I can tread upon. So many demonic path Gu Immortals had involved themselves in Imperial Court contest before, but how many obtained a good ending? Sigh, I got greedy because of wooden chicken Gu and thought that since I had already offended Hei tribe's Gu Immortals, I might as well directly go further and meddle. But I did not know how many demonic path Gu Immortals were mocking me behind my back. Sigh, it is time to reflect upon myself!"

Xue Song Zi kept on sighing and just when he was going to finish pondering his painful experience in attempting to learn from it, a letter Gu travelled through space and appeared in front of him.

"Eh, isn't this the letter Gu I gave to Ma tribe to contact me?"

Xue Song Zi was baffled. He held the letter Gu and searched it with his mind before immediately revealing an astonished expression: "What, what does this mean? Hei Lou Lan actually wants to cooperate with me?"

Xue Song Zi scoffed in disdain: "Using wooden chicken Gu as the bait, do you think I will be fooled? Maybe this is another scheme of Hei tribe! Huh, wait a moment, this actually....does Hei Lou Lan really want to work with me? Interesting, hahahaha, interesting!!"

After over half a month....

"Mother! Mother!!" Hei Lou Lan suddenly woke up on the bed.

He was panting and his body was soaked with cold sweat.

A good while later, his eyes gradually recovered their focus.

The nightmare once again.

Since long ago, this nightmare had been tormenting him.

This nightmare was like a pile of firewood that ignited the fire of revenge in his heart, every time it occured.

Recovering his breath, Hei Lou Lan got up from the bed.

His body was obese like a black bear. His triangular eyes began flickering with terrifying sharp light. Only his face had the expression of heavy exhaustion.

But by the time he pushed open the window, this exhaustion was already concealed by him, replaced by a savage and tyrannical aura.

He gazed up at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building while pondering over the cooperation with Xue Song Zi.

In the letter, he had taken great risk, speaking his greatest secret, and delivering crucial Gu worms as a pledge, before he was able to obtain Xue Song Zi's trust.

Now, the thirty-ninth floor had already been formed for quite some time. The cooperation between him and Xue Song Zi was progressing very well. Benefitting from this demonic path Gu Immortal's help, Hei Lou Lan was able to smoothly break through the rounds in the thirty-ninth floor.

His action was betraying Hei tribe.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals would absolutely not let him go.

Hei Lou Lan did not even have the confidence of being able to conceal this matter for long.

But he knew clearly, he was safe as long as he was within Imperial Court blessed land. Imperial Court blessed land prohibited the entry of Gu Immortals.

At this stage, he was no longer able to turn back and could only move forward until his death. But the most crucial thing in Hei Lou Lan's plan, the strength path Immortal Gu which could change the whole situation, was yet to appear.

He could only continue to wait.

　　...

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, seventh floor.

Ninetieth round.

"Chang Ji You pays respects to Lord Supreme Elder." Chang Ji You kneeled down with an ashamed expression.

"Do you know why I called you?" Fang Yuan stood in front of him, and said in an indifferent tone.

"I am ashamed, I failed to live up to Lord Supreme Elder's trust. I am extremely incompetent, letting the killer get away with it to this day, I request Lord Supreme Elder to bestow punishment!" Chang Ji You kowtowed again and again, muffled thuds sounded out as his forehead smashed on the ground..

Soon, blood could be seen on his forehead.

Fang Yuan snorted: "You know yourself and know your incompetence. Don't kowtow anymore, stand up and answer."

"Subordinate, subordinate does not dare."

"Get up." Fang Yuan emphasized once again, his tone was calm but it was filled with a will that could not be disobeyed.

Chang Ji You stood up with his head lowered, blood slowly flowed down his cheeks, making him look very miserable.

"Sigh." Fang Yuan sighed softly before touching the wound on Chang Ji You's forehead.

White light appeared, and under the power of a healing gu, Chang Ji You's wound rapidly healed without even leaving a scar.

Chang Ji You's body trembled, his eyes couldn't help but release two flowing lines of warm tears.

Ever since the "father and son" had met, this was the first time Chang Shan Yin had done such an intimate action to his son Chang Ji You.

Chapter 589: The bond between father and son, real and fake affection

Fang Yuan wiped Chang Ji You's tears and said with a mild tone like a spring wind: "What are you crying for, I am Wolf King and you are my son, you can only shed blood and not tears."

Chang Ji You's mind shook fiercely like he had been struck by lightning, when he heard the word 'son'.

An enormous joy engulfed Chang Ji You's mind like a tsunami: 'Father finally recognizes me as his son, he called me son with his own mouth!!!"

The grievances that had accumulated in his heart, the pressure he felt, the anger and shame he had put aside, the sorrow at his adoptive father's death, everything was dispelled at this moment.

He involuntarily was about to cry tears of joy but Fang Yuan's words lingered in his ears and he endured painfully, his expression twisted and he even bit his lips, but the tears still flowed out with no end.

He opened his mouth, wanting to call out 'father', but did not dare, and could only keep on apologizing as he sobbed: "Sorry, I am sorry..."

Fang Yuan lightly patted his shoulder and warmly said: "Do you know what your greatest deficiency is?"

Chang Ji You was slightly shocked.

Fang Yuan continued with a decisive tone: "Your greatest deficiency is that you are not strong enough."

"Not strong enough?" Chang Ji You stopped sobbing, his eyes that were hazy with tears looked at the imposing figure in front.

"This is a yellow gold relic Gu, enough for you to advance to rank four peak stage. Also a purple crystal relic Gu which will help you advance rapidly in rank five." Fang Yuan took out two relic Gu and handed them to Chang Ji You.

Chang Ji You dazedly accepted it, soon a surging grateful feeling filled his wild heart.

"This, isn't this paternal love!? So many poets praised paternal love to be as heavy as a mountain and as deep as the sea.....I can finally enjoy it today!"

"Father..." Chang Ji You was choked with emotions, he gazed at Fang Yuan before kneeling down again.

"An eagle chick cannot grow firm, iron-like wings without going through the tempering of wind and frost. A horse foal cannot run like the wind without experiencing falling down. I have already heard of Chang tribe's misfortunes, but I will not concern myself with it. Become strong, go through such temperings, take control of the tribe, use this pretext to establish your might, this is something you need to do. I will be watching you from behind."

"Lord father, son, son is ashamed..." Being given such earnest attention by his 'blood related father', this made Chang Ji You excited and also brought a fearful feeling in him.

Fang Yuan waved his hand: "I know your misgivings. You are worried your aptitude is not enough and you cannot break through to rank five, right? No problem, I will now raise your aptitude and also impart you a strength path killer move set which will increase your strength to an unimaginable level! This is father's special skill and even at the decisive battle of Imperial Court, I only used thirty percent of its power."

"Ah?" Chang Ji You involuntarily opened up his mouth, shocked and happy.

Father actually had ways to raise aptitude, moreover was also imparting a strength path killer move!

Even during the decisive battle with Ma tribe, father only used thirty percent of this killer move's power!

'My father is after all my father. Godfather Chang Biao might have treated me very well, but that is nothing compared to my father. This is the deepest bond between blood. Lord father is nurturing me with all his efforts!' After the shock, Chang Ji You felt a surge of happiness.

"Now I am going to raise your aptitude. Relax your mind, pacify your heart. Sleep, sleep, take a good sleep first." Fang Yuan spoke gently while secretly using hypnosis Gu.

Chang Ji You's mood was not stable and he had already been exhausted, and with his extreme trust in Fang Yuan, he soon fell asleep under the effect of Gu worm.

Fang Yuan lightly smiled as he took out blood skull Gu.

This Gu had a crystal like texture, the size of an infant's skull and could be held by a palm.

But right now, it was full from drinking blood and shone with a demonic blood light.

This blood was absorbed from the Chang tribesmen Fang Yuan had secretly killed over these days.

The sound asleep Chang Ji You had a slight smile on his face, a happy smile. He had never even expected the killer who had assassinated Chang tribesmen in these days was his most loved and respected 'blood related father'.

Even Hei Lou Lan and other outsiders were also in the dark, not having the least bit of doubt towards Fang Yuan.

"Go." Fang Yuan willed and the blood skull Gu slowly flew out of his palm and circled around Chang Ji You.

The blood skull Gu then stopped over Chang Ji You's head; it opened its mouth and puffed out blood with a thick stench.

The blood directly sunk in through Chang Ji You's head, skin and hairs, followed his veins and finally converged in his aperture.

Chang Ji You's aperture began to slowly but steadily advance.

By the time Chang Ji You woke up, Fang Yuan had already gone away.

The previous encounter was like a dream, making Chang Ji You feel doubts.

But the Gu worms on the ground and plentiful food left behind, were the best proof that everything was true..

"Heavens, my aptitude really advanced, now it is at ninety-six percent!!" Chang Ji You shouted out with joy after he checked his aperture.

"Stay here for few days and cultivate properly. Use all the relic Gu father left behind, your cultivation will reach rank five upper stage with these. I am temporarily lending the other Gu worms on the ground to you. Among them is an east window Gu which records the contents of the killer move, read it and practice it."

A message echoed into Chang Ji You's ears.

Chang Ji You was extremely excited: "Ahh, this is father's voice. Lord father, son will not disappoint you. Son will definitely become a rank five Gu Master and master this killer move!"

Chang Ji You felt extremely bold and was filled with fighting spirit. He sat down cross-legged on the spot and took a yellow gold relic Gu into his aperture.

Fang Yuan was secretly observing this.

"This is the Gu tester you chose? He is truly a good choice." In his mind, Mo Yao's will let out a cold sneer, "It is only that you clearly indicated the flaws of six arm heavenly zombie king in the east window Gu. And you have also not tampered with the Gu worms you lent him, are you not afraid he will worry about the flaws and be careful, not completely transforming into a heavenly zombie?"

"Hehe, Mo Yao, you don't need to worry. I still have the ability to grasp people's hearts. You haven't used six arm heavenly zombie king, so you don't know how intoxicating the feeling of endless strength you get when transforming to the heavenly zombie state can be. Even I was intoxicated. Chang Ji You is young and does not have enough control over his heart. When he practices the killer move, he will naturally search for wolf groups to battle with. This here is my territory, I will just lead more wolves towards him when the time comes, no need to be afraid he won't change into a heavenly zombie!" Fang Yuan spoke with confidence.

"Hmph, you humans are so sinister and crafty. This blood skull Gu you used, we inkmen would absolutely never refine such an evil Gu worm which is used to harm our own people." Mo Yao sneered.

Fang Yuan was not angry, instead smiling: "Eh, aren't you Spirit Affinity House's fairy, a representative of the righteous path? Why didn't you stop me?"

"That is possible only if I had the ability to stop it. Moreover, why would I stop the internal conflicts between you humans? Hmph, I would rather the whole of your human race died. Then, us variant humans can have space to survive." Mo Yao rolled her eyes.

Her identity was special, she was a past generation's fairy of Spirit Affinity House with an extraordinary relationship with Bo Qing. However, she was also an inkman and was not a purebred human.

The feeling with which she looked at humans fighting each other was the same feeling humans had when they watched internal strife between snowmen or beast groups.

'Just that, you truly don't have the ability to stop me?...' Fang Yuan suppressed this doubt within his heart.

Three days later, Chang Ji You finished using all the relic Gu and succeeded in advancing to rank five upper stage.

Immediately afterwards, he began to practice the killer move six arm heavenly zombie king.

Just like Fang Yuan expected, he was addicted to the vast power of the killer move and gradually began to forget its flaws.

Under Fang Yuan's intentional manipulation, he fought an intense and prolonged battle.

Chang Ji You rampaged around to his heart's content in the battle, forgetting the time.

Only when the battle ended, did he make a frightening discovery; he had already completely transformed into a heavenly zombie.

Two days later, Fang Yuan appeared before him again.

"Father, save me!" The monstrous Chang Ji You kneeled on the ground and begged with terrified expression.

"Son, how did you become like this?!" Fang Yuan asked in great shock and rage, "I clearly warned you to never use this killer move over the limit. You, you, how could you forget such a crucial thing!"

"Father, son is ashamed, I was muddled for a while and forgot time. By the time I discovered it, it was too late for regret!" Chang Ji You was extremely ashamed as he looked at Fang Yuan with tear filled eyes while kneeling.

Right now, he had transformed into this monstrosity, his only hope rested in Fang Yuan.

"Sigh... this is difficult. Your appearance, even if we use yin-yang rotation Gu, it won't be able to treat it. This killer move has extreme power, but also because of this, the after-effects are very severe. Even father does not have a way." Fang Yuan held out his hands, showing an expression filled with sadness and anger.

"Ah?! Even father does not have a solution?" Chang Ji You walked towards Fang Yuan on his knees with despair and fear on his face.

Fang Yuan lamented again and again: "This killer move's origin is not simple. Father took extreme risk and charged through a Gu Immortal's inheritance alone, risking a fatal danger before I was able to luckily obtain this immortal killer move."

"This is an immortal killer move? No wonder, no wonder it is so powerful!" Chang Ji You was stupefied, Fang Yuan might have a lofty figure in his heart, but there was no doubt he paled in comparison to a Gu Immortal.

Chang Ji You had been Chang tribe's young tribe leader, he had not been familiar with Gu Immortals, but was also not completely unfamiliar.

"I was wrong, I made a big mistake, how could I seek instant gains!" Chang Ji You wailed, his wail was sharp and unpleasant like a night owl's.

Suddenly, he started kowtowing to Fang Yuan and sobbed: "Father, son failed to live up to your hope. Son made a mistake, son has disappointed you!"

"No, it is this, I needed you to transform into this.' Fang Yuan was laughing inwardly while on the surface, he supported Chang Ji You.

"My son, I told you so many times, don't cry! You cannot cry! Although you made a mistake, the fault lies within me as well. I have only been exploring this maze round over these days and did not look after you. Father believes there is always a way out, we will research together and find a way to turn you back into a human! There is definitely a way, believe in father and believe in yourself!" Fang Yuan said with emotions, with tears in his eyes.

"Father!!!" Chang Ji You wailed again.

He was thoroughly and completely moved.

He had become a monster and he, himself, did not not dare to see his face. But his father, Chang Shan Yin, did not loath him. It was clearly the son's fault, but he took the blame upon himself.

Now that his son had changed to such an appearance, he still did not give up on him.

"This is the most profound bond between father and son!"

"This is my father, my dad!"

Chang Ji You was extremely moved, a spark ignited in his despair filled heart, giving him the confidence to continue living.

"Son, stay here and let father think properly on how to change you back. As for Chang tribe, father will personally manage it. You don't need to worry, just recuperate here, with us father and son working hand in hand, what is there to fear about a measly killer move's zombie transformation?"

Fang Yuan's words made Chang Ji You feel a source of assurance in his heart.

"Yes, son will listen to father!"

Chapter 590: Endurance, Shatter, Death

Ah——!

The pitiful scream was so shrill that it could pierce eardrums.

Chang Ji You was in so much pain that he was shivering from head to toe, his muscles were exploding, as the six arms behind his back were dancing around chaotically, making loud sounds like that of stirring wind and rolling thunder.

But Fang Yuan only needed one hand to hold him tightly in the air.

At this moment, his eyes were like lightning as he manipulated his Gu worms, shouting loudly: "My son, endure it! Now is the time!"

Chang Ji You was about to lose his sense of reasoning due to the pain, this was an inhuman pain.

Even though he transformed into a heavenly zombie and almost lost his sense of pain, he could still feel every single piece of his skin and every muscle tearing and breaking ruthlessly.

But Fang Yuan's words were like cold spring water that were sprinkling on Chang Ji You's heart.

Chang Ji You was forcing himself to his limit, just as he was about to faint, the intense pain dissipated like a subsiding tide.

"Su… success?!" Chang Ji You breathed roughly, his head was hurting intensely and he barely managed to open his eyes, seeing that the skin on his arm had already turned back into living flesh and blood.

In fact, the six arms on his back were also slowly shrinking.

There was nothing more attractive to Chang Ji You than turning back into a human.

This moment, he was almost going to cry of joy.

"Oh no!" Suddenly, Fang Yuan spoke, his tone extremely solemn.

Chang Ji You's newly recovered arm turned back into the heavenly zombie state in an instant, like that of a rotting log.

The six arms on his back grew back as well, becoming tougher and stronger.

"No, no! Why did I change back?! Father…" Chang Ji You was screaming in fear, subconsciously turning towards Fang Yuan for help.

But when he saw the intense fatigue that Fang Yuan was pretending to show on his face, Chang Ji You could not say a word.

"Father is tired! That's right, these days, he had been helping me, thinking of hundreds of methods to solve this without any rest or sleep. He expended countless Gu worms in the process. I saw at least seventy to eighty rank five Gu! What reason do I have to blame father? This is all because I was too careless, and committed a grave mistake! Father, this son has not lived up to your expectations and nurturing…"

Chang Ji You was heartbroken and ashamed, he had a sensation of bliss from being taken care of by Wolf King as his child, like a small strand of grass being shielded by a tall tree.

"Damn it, this heavenly zombie form is really stubborn. Even this method is not working!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth secretly, he asked in his mind: "Mo Yao, what other ideas do you have, tell me!"

The dozen ideas that Fang Yuan came up with were all proven to be useless one by one.

The current experimental method was all Mo Yao's idea.

This was also one of Fang Yuan's schemes.

On the one hand, he was experimenting on Chang Ji You continuously and attempting to find a way to restore him back to human. On the other hand, he was trying to get Mo Yao's will to think and expend her limited energy.

Mo Yao was silent for a while before saying: "There is still a way, but it is quite dangerous, the person testing the Gu will endure three times the pain as before! Most likely, he would die from the pain alone!"

"He is a heavenly zombie, he is technically dead. How can he feel pain?" Fang Yuan was confused.

"He is only half dead. The body is dead, but his soul still remains in his body. Unless his soul was absorbed into the door of life and death, then he would truly be considered dead." Mo Yao explained.

The door of life and death was a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it was very famous and was recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>.

But the current era was different from the immemorial era.

The life and death door had vanished, and after going through numerous owners, its control over souls of the demised had weakened greatly. This was the reason for the existence of monsters like zombies.

Mo Yao's idea carried huge risks, it could shatter the person's soul due to pain, breaking into irrecoverable pieces.

Once Chang Ji You's soul shatters, he would be truly dead.

Mo Yao urged: "Lad, when there is gain, there is also loss. The killer move has unrivalled attack power, thus the flaws will be extremely hard to get rid of. These few days, you have experimented so many times, and spent a huge fortune, even borrowing extensively from Hei tribe, I'm sure you understand the difficulty of this now."

"This is my final method, I cannot guarantee that it will work. Moreover, this method is extremely dangerous, there is barely a chance of success! You can decide whether or not to do it. Your 'son' has already turned into a heavenly zombie completely, he has good battle strength. He listens to your words obediently, it is too wasteful to sacrifice him like this. I would suggest that you keep him by your side as a helper."

Fang Yuan was silent and did not reply.

"Father, please rest more, I am not anxious…" At one end, Chang Ji You muttered.

Fang Yuan concentrated and looked over, although Chang Ji You had turned into a heavenly zombie, and looked very ugly, his eyes were crystal clear, showing great admiration and love for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "Son, I have thought of a good method. But this method is extremely dangerous, your life will be in danger. The success rate is very high though, thus father cannot decide…"

"Sigh…" In his mind, Mo Yao sighed deeply.

Although Fang Yuan said this, Chang Ji You who hated his current self and wanted to recover would only make one decision.

As expected, once Chang Ji You heard this, he hesitated for a moment before his eyes shone brightly: "Lord father! Please use this method, living in my current form is simply worse than death!"

Fang Yuan stared at Chang Ji You's eyes intensely: "But, you are my only child…"

"Father!" Chang Ji You cried, he kneeled on the floor as he hugged Fang Yuan's leg: "I cannot bear to part with you either, father. But son really cannot live with such an appearance, even if there is some bit of hope, I will work hard and fight for it!"

Fang Yuan was silent for a while, before sighing a long, deep breath: "Alright. Humans should live according to their own wishes. Father is unwilling to see you live in such agony as well! Go rest for a few days, father will go prepare. A few days later, we will go with the final try!"

A few days later.

"Ahhhhh…"

Chang Ji You's screaming voice had already turned hoarse.

"Endure it for a bit more." Fang Yuan's gaze was warm, but his heart was cold as ice, as he encouraged.

But the next moment, Chang Ji You's screams and cries came to a stop.

This was the three hundred and seventh time he had fainted from pain.

"Hmph, completely useless!" Fang Yuan's expression was dim as water, he snorted unhappily as he stopped using the Gu worms.

This experiment had to be undergone when Chang Ji You was conscious and awake, otherwise it would not work.

Chang Ji You fainting meant that his soul was already forming cracks and chips, he was at the brink of collapsing.

Fang Yuan had to stop and use soul path Gu worms to nourish and heal his soul.

"I said before, this method has little hope, it is better to preserve his life." In his mind, Mo Yao spoke in a sad tone.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, squinting as a cold light flashed across his eyes: "One more try, we will try it one last time!"

Chang Ji You slowly woke up, his vision turning from blurry to clear. He looked at Fang Yuan beside him, in his eyes, his 'father' was extremely worn out and exhausted.

This made his heart tighten as tears flowed down his eyes again in shame, he choked as he said: "Father…"

"Let's try again, don't lose hope." Fang Yuan laughed as he encouraged.

"Father, if I still faint this time, then stop trying it. Father, this was all my fault, you really need to take a rest." Chang Ji You said.

"Yes, after trying this, it is really time to rest." Fang Yuan sighed, the precise deeper meanings in his tone were not able to be perceived by Chang Ji You.

First, three rank five Gu worms were activated together.

Next, more Gu worms were added, these Gu worms were all floating around the face of Chang Ji You, some drilled into his skin while others mixed into his blood, flowing towards his heart.

"Ah…" The intense pain assaulted him again, Chang Ji You gritted his teeth in pain but he soon opened his mouth and growled, his expression twisting from the pain.

Fang Yuan's movements were smooth and methodical as he continued adding in Gu worms.

The more Gu worms that were added in, the more intense the pain Chang Ji You felt. He struggled desperately, his eyes rolling as he felt pain to the point of losing reason, almost as if he was becoming deranged.

"Stop, his soul cannot take this." In his mind, Mo Yao urged.

But Fang Yuan acted like he did not hear it, continuing to add Gu worms regardless of what was going on.

"Enough, this amount has exceeded all our previous attempts, he is really going to collapse." Mo Yao could not bear to see this.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, not saying a word.

"This is too much, if you continue messing around like this, he will really die!" In his mind, Mo Yao's will protested.

"What can we achieve if we do not take risks?" Fang Yuan laughed coldly, adding more Gu worms until it was the limit.

His eyes were shining with an excited light: "Just three more Gu worms and we will see the effect. This is the first."

"Alright, this is the second!"

"Fantastic, this is the final one, success or failure will depend on this…. eh!"

Fang Yuan's expression froze, the surrounding Gu worms were breaking apart like the scattering of fireworks.

Chang Ji You no longer struggled, he was floating in the air motionlessly.

He was dead.

His soul had shattered and dissipated from the pain.

His expression however, was very calm.

The surroundings became dead silent.

"You've killed him." In Fang Yuan's mind, Mo Yao's will spoke coldly.

"Yes, I've killed him." Fang Yuan's brows lifted, laughing lightly: "He did not die in vain after all, at least I got to find out how stubborn this killer move's flaw truly was."

Mo Yao did not speak, she did not want to respond to Fang Yuan's cold and unscrupulous nature. She hid her form and vanished from Fang Yuan's mind.

Fang Yuan's smile gradually vanished.

He was progressively discovering how big of a threat this will of Mo Yao in his mind was.

Did she know about the way to resolve the flaw of the six arm heavenly zombie king killer move or not?

Did she know the method, but was unwilling to say it, or was she not thinking so as to preserve herself?

Especially when this killer move's flaw is so severe, if Mo Yao's will attacks Fang Yuan's mind during the crucial moment and cause his thoughts to become chaotic, he would not be able to stop the killer move even if he wanted to.

"What was the Gu used to create this will of Mo Yao's? These days, I have been collecting information on wisdom path, and purchased many wisdom path Gu worms that could create wills. But I have not found any Gu worm which can allow her to hide and completely conceal herself like this, this is such an unfathomable will!"

"Sigh, I don't have much time left. Right now Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has formed about sixty floors already. Hei Lou Lan is attacking the thirty-ninth floor right now at full force. It seems his target is the wooden chicken Gu."

"I have to work faster, I cannot wait anymore!"

Chapter 591: Sacrifice (Double Chapter)

It had been so long since Fang Yuan had come to Imperial Court blessed land, and he had entered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building so many times, but he had never forgotten his original intention in coming to northern plains.

That was to save Dang Hun mountain.

He needed landscape as before Gu to save Dang Hun mountain.

There were many difficulties and challenges to obtain this Gu, the main thing was it was with a person. This person was Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Ever since Tai Bai Yun Sheng joined Hei tribe army, Fang Yuan had been placing his attention on him.

Several months ago, Fang Yuan uncovered some information:

When Hei Lou Lan obtained the one-edge owner token, he was able to explore the rewards of every round; Tai Bai Yun Sheng had gone to visit him and inquired about the existence of lifespan Gu.

But at that time, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building did not yet have lifespan Gu.

When the fifty-fifth floor had condensed, Hei Lou Lan informed Tai Bai Yun Sheng he had discovered a fifteen year lifespan Gu.

After the fifty-fifth floor completely formed into shape, Hei Lou Lan investigated the location of the lifespan Gu and could precisely tell it was the reward for clearing the eighty-fifth round.

From then on, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had put all his energy in the fifty-fifth floor. He called up many Gu Masters, forming an enormous group and forcibly crashed through the rounds. Relying on his might, prestige and enormous rewards, along with repeatedly requesting Hei Lou Lan and other experts, he was actually making fast progress.

Hard work paid off, Tai Bai Yun Sheng spent all his wealth and finally was able to reach the eighty-fifth round.

Fang Yuan naturally did not wish to see Tai Bai Yun Sheng obtaining what he desired.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was old, and did not have much lifespan left; it was natural behavior for him to increase his lifespan with lifespan Gu.

But if he really obtained this lifespan Gu, he was definitely not going to risk advancing into an immortal. If he did not risk advancing to an immortal, there would not be the inspiration from heaven and earth that would form the Immortal Gu Landscape As Before.

If there was no landscape as before Gu, how would Fang Yuan save Dang Hun mountain which was about to completely wither away?

Especially the past few days, he had learned more information: Tai Bai Yun Sheng had attempted many times to pass the round and he had already found hope. He did not stint on borrowing from Hei Lou Lan and even agreed to Hei Lou Lan's condition of becoming an external elder of Hei tribe.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was then able to use Hei tribe's resources to recruit large numbers of experts and form a powerful lineup, charging into the fifty-fifth floor to make the final attack.

Despite Tai Bai Yun Sheng taking the risk to advance to an immortal in the memories of his previous life, Fang Yuan was cautious and did not dare to take the risk, deciding to personally intervene.

Time waits for no man.

Fang Yuan had intended to get rid of Mo Yao's will first, dealing with the internal problem before attacking the external problems. But this matter had not made any progress, so now, he used his owner token to secretly infiltrate into the fifty-fifth floor.

The situation of the fifty-fifth floor had already been probed out by Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

There was a majestic and grand blood river flowing here, and in the depths of the river, there was a legendary and mythical blood palace erected.

The blood palace had three great halls and sixty-nine auxiliary halls.

Every hall contained large numbers of blood path Gu worms as well as blood beast guards.

The large groups of blood path Gu worms were of huge strength, but as long as they were killed one by one over a period of time, there would be a point when they are all slaughtered.

The problem was the blood beasts.

Even after these blood beasts were killed, they would absorb blood and resurrect within a short moment. One could say that they could be killed but not killed, there was no way of reducing their numbers.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's several attempts at passing the round had all been thwarted by these blood beasts.

But at the last attempt, he had unintentionally discovered a pleasant surprise: as long as they keep on charging forward to the depths of the great hall and take out the command token hanging on the main beam, they could make the blood beasts dissipate.

This discovery birthed a strong confidence in Tai Bai Yun Sheng. He was thoroughly poor now, and did not hesitate to sell himself to Hei tribe, borrowing funds and forming a Gu Master group to charge through this round.

When Fang Yuan secretly entered this floor, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's group had already charged through thirty-three side halls and were presently in a fierce battle to reach a towering main hall.

Fang Yuan took out the six-edge owner token, and with a thought, immediately had complete control over this floor.

The six-edge owner token could let Fang Yuan control up to six floors of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Fang Yuan had already used it once to control the seventh floor. Now, he was using it a second time to control this fifty-fifth floor.

Hei Lou Lan had a one-edge owner token and the floor he controlled was the fifth floor.

With a shift of thought, Fang Yuan's figure disappeared on the spot and appeared on the main beam of the great hall.

He leisurely sat on the main beam, and not far from him was that crucial command token.

With a bit of concentration, the battle scene of Tai Bai Yun Sheng and his group appeared in Fang Yuan's mind.

The deeper they went towards the great hall, the more blood beast guards there were, and the battles that occurred were extremely intense. This group of Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not even have fifty people now.

They had been charging forward the whole way, suffering disastrous casualties which left behind a trail of corpses along the way.

Two great rank five Gu Master experts Zhu Zai and Gao Yang took turns as the front vanguard of the group.

Meanwhile Tai Bai Yun Sheng, as the number one healing Gu Master of northern plains of this generation, was protected in the center of the formation. He continually used man as before Gu; rays of light shooting forward and shining upon the corpses, resurrecting the Gu Masters, or shone upon live Gu Masters, healing their injuries and recovering their primeval essence in an instant.

But even Tai Bai Yun Sheng, a rank five peak stage Gu Master, was in a very sorry state.

Gu Masters were falling down time and again, and although he used all his strength, he truly could not save everyone.

The countless blood beasts surged out of every corridor near the great hall and every room, blocking the group's way with very dense numbers.

The closer they got to the main command token, the stronger the blood beasts became.

And blood beasts could absorb blood to quickly recover and resurrect.

By the time Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the group charged to this place, the blood beasts they had killed on their way had once again resurrected and chased them, blocking their way back. The situation was getting very dangerous.

"No wonder Tai Bai Yun Sheng risked advancing to immortal in my previous life. This round's difficulty is rather high, unless a blood path Gu Master works with them." Fang Yuan was in control of this place and could see the actions that Tai Bai Yun Sheng took as easily as reading the lines of his palm.

To a blood path Gu Master, this round was no less than a paradise. With so many blood path wild Gu to subdue and blood beasts to devour, their blood path cultivation would strengthen rapidly.

It was a pity blood path could not be easily revealed. Because of Blood Sea Ancestor, a blood path Gu Master would be hunted persistently by the righteous path the moment they appeared.

And because blood path Gu Masters could quickly increase their battle strength, even demonic Gu Masters widely feared it.

Often, when a blood path Gu Master was discovered, not only would they be hunted down by the righteous path, they would also suffer sneak attacks from demonic path Gu Masters.

There was not even one blood path Gu Master among Hei tribe army. Even if they existed, they were hidden deeply and would not appear for Tai Bai Yun Sheng's use.

Fang Yuan ascertained for a moment and knew clearly that the chance of Tai Bai Yun Sheng succeeding was extremely minute.

The worry in his heart immediately dissipated by more than half.

Fang Yuan laid back on the beam and took out \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, passing the time while paying attention to Tai Bai Yun Sheng's progress.

Death was possible when advancing through Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Fang Yuan was scheming for landscape as before Gu, and could not allow Tai Bai Yun Sheng to die at the moment.

"Kill, we must break through this siege! Otherwise, we are all going to die!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's face was filled with blood stains, roaring loudly to raise the morale.

Waves of blood beasts roared and snarled, before pouncing on the group like a blood colored giant wave.

　　...

The great hall was a scene of tranquility.

Fang Yuan leisurely flipped through the pages while adjusting his posture to make himself more comfortable.

　　...

Grrr!

A blood beast with the head of a tiger and body of a horse madly snarled while rampaging in the group of Gu Masters.

Two Gu Masters met its attack; one died while the other was heavily injured.

"Man As Before!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted and raised his palm; a white light immediately shot out and shone upon that injured Gu Master.

The Gu Master immediately recovered his previous uninjured state. The terrifying injuries from the blood beast's attacks disappeared without a trace.

The Gu Master panted roughly, he was still frightened, retreating back behind the frontlines. The defensive gap he left behind was immediately filled up by another Gu Master.

But that dead Gu Master's corpse was swarmed by the blood beasts and roughly dragged away.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not make a move.

Without advancing to an immortal, even a rank five Gu Master would have limited primeval essence and have to use it cautiously.

Moreover, that dead Gu Master's Gu worms were severely damaged, his defensive Gu worm was even pierced and destroyed. Even if he was resurrected, he would be killed again.

The remaining Gu Masters grieved and cursed, but they could only look as their companion's corpse was madly torn apart by over ten blood beasts.

Blood beasts were extremely sensitive to blood and even a bit of bloody odor could make them go crazy. By swallowing stronger organism's blood, they could strengthen themselves.

Soon, the dead Gu Master's blood was completely absorbed by the blood beasts. The whole corpse became a dried up mummy, creating a wretched spectacle.

The beasts that had absorbed his blood started to grow human like forms. Some grew human like eyes; some grew several human ears; and some grew agile human arms.

But when they were spending time in absorbing the corpse, the pressure on Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the group greatly reduced and they took this valuable opportunity to break through and moved forward tens of steps.

　　...

Fang Yuan flipped through \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> to chapter three, section fourteen.

Northern Dark Ice Soul awakened his elder sister Desolate Ancient Moon, and the two again asked for advice from cognition Gu on how to save their father.

Cognition Gu said: "Humans, Cheng Bai mountain has disappeared, who knows when it will form again. I am also not clear on other ways to bring your father back to life. But no need to be dejected, you can try asking wisdom Gu. I am its mother, wisdom is the crystallization of cognition."

The student surpasses the master; the things cognition Gu did not know, wisdom Gu might not necessarily be unknowing of.

Under cognition Gu's directions, Northern Dark Ice Soul and Desolate Ancient Moon found wisdom Gu.

Wisdom Gu had somewhat of a connection with Ren Zu, back then Ren Zu had used rules and regulations Gu to capture it. But it was able to escape in the end.

At first, wisdom Gu was not willing to help Northern Dark Ice Soul and Desolate Ancient Moon.

But seeing that they were introduced by its mother cognition Gu, it reluctantly said: "Oh humans, I can show you the right path. But I need remuneration, one of you need to hand over your middle age to me."

"I will give my middle age to you." Desolate Ancient Moon immediately replied with no hesitation.

She was awakened by her little brother Northern Dark Ice Soul and had been bestowed with the meaning of her life which was to bring her father, Ren Zu, back to life. Thus, she replied immediately without the intention of passing it to others.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was not able to argue with his sister and could only let her offer her middle age.

This meant, once Desolate Ancient Moon's youth had passed, she would directly skip middle age to reach old age.

But to save her father, she did not have many misgivings.

Wisdom Gu obtained Desolate Ancient Moon's middle age and gave her directions: "In the center of the golden desert in the west, there is a still blue sea with no ripples, as flat as a mirror. That is the source of all living beings, all lives in the world originates from there. And in the depths of the blue sea lie many life Gu shining upon all living beings. You need to infiltrate the sea, catch a human shaped life Gu and bring it to shore. This human shaped life Gu can bestow your father a new life. But remember, you cannot spend over fifteen minutes in the sea, otherwise you will be assimilated by the sea.

Wisdom Gu added another sentence in the end: "It is extremely difficult to find human shaped life Gu. Only a person who has truly comprehended the truth of life can do it. If you are not able to do it, don't blame my solution for not being easy to use."

Desolate Ancient Moon wanted to ask something, but Wisdom Gu quickly flew away and did not give the siblings any chance to make inquiries.

　　...

The clamorous shouts and cries resounded everywhere.

The blood beasts surged forward like sea tides. Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the group were like a reef, resisting the attacks of the blood beasts time and again, while also moving forward step by step with difficulty.

"Almost there, we are only three hundred steps away from the great hall door!" Someone shouted, boosting the morale.

"Careful!" Suddenly, a Gu Master at the side warned.

That Gu Master who had tried to boost morale was dazed and the very next moment, a blood beast with the head of a dragon and body of a bear fiercely smashed into him.

Crack.

The Gu Master's ribs instantly shattered from the crash, and the blood he puffed out contained pieces of internal organs.

His body was sent flying from the smash, the Gu Masters behind tried to stop him with all their strength; in an instant, the formation turned chaotic and there was a crisis of it collapsing apart!

"Hold on, continue to hold on!!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng, his face stained with blood, shouted furiously with extreme anxiety.

In such a battle situation, if the Gu Masters scattered, they would immediately be torn to pieces by the surrounding countless blood beasts. Only with the Gu Masters working in a tight formation, could they have a chance at survival!

But the Gu Masters were retreating step by step, large numbers of blood beasts broke the defense line and fiercely pounced upon them.

Miserable screams started rising continuously.

Many Gu Masters were still recovering their primeval essence as much as possible. Being caught unawares, they were immediately torn to pieces by the blood beasts.

A mantis-like blood beast brandished its sickle arms and charged in the very front.

Swish!

A Gu Master's head was slashed apart; blood started spurting out of the Gu Master's neck and the head flew high, but before it fell down, it was grabbed by a blood beast flying in the air and with a 'gulp, was swallowed down.

But the red hot blood fell down, splashing right at Tai Bai Yun Sheng's face.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly wiped away the blood and was barely able to open his eyes; the dense bloody stench assailed his nose, and agitated a group of blood beasts.

"Finished!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart sank to the bottom, but right at this time, a figure pounced down like a tiger getting off the mountain.

BOOM BOOM BOOM.

After several rounds, the figure killed the mantis blood beast and finally stabilized the formation at this final juncture.

It was Zhu Zai!

A rank five Gu Master, a famous expert of the demonic path!!

Everyone was saved, feeling like they were dragged back from the cliff.

But Zhu Zai also paid a price, there were three new wounds on his body, all of them so deep one could see his bones.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly activated man as before Gu to heal him.

Zhu Zai recovered his previous state and the new injuries completely vanished. At the same time, his intensely depleted primeval essence recovered back.

It was only that the several expendable Gu he had used to gain a burst in his battle strength earlier could not be restored.

Man As Before could only target human bodies and had no effect on Gu worms.

　　...

"This Man As Before has marvellous effect, but unfortunately, it cannot be used on one's own body." Fang Yuan sighed before gazing back to the book in his hand once again.

Desolate Ancient Moon and Northern Dark Ice Soul travelled an arduous journey through the golden desert and arrived at the center of the desert where they saw the blue sea.

The blue sea was so beautiful that nothing more beautiful than it could be imagined.

Just like wisdom Gu said, even strong winds could not cause the slightest of a ripple on the blue sea.

With the soft golden sand surrounding it, it looked like a deep blue gemstone embedded on this golden cloth.

The siblings infiltrated into the depths of the sea and sure enough found large numbers of life Gu packed together in the sea depths.

These life Gu were like blue gems. But they were of different sizes and shapes.

Some looked like a colt; some like a tiger or leopard; some like an eagle or dove; while some like a snake or flood dragon.

The siblings were dazzled from the sight. They saw all kinds of life Gu from flowers, birds, fishes, insects, beasts, snowmen, hairy men and all other shapes, except the human shaped life Gu.

Helplessly, the siblings could only get out of the sea and back to the shore.

The moment they had left the blue sea, a deer shaped life Gu Northern Dark Ice Soul had been holding, let out a soft light before jumping on the sand and turning into a fawn.

This was the birth of a life!

The siblings looked at this sight in wonder, with their eyes wide open.

Only when the fawn had hopped far away, the elder sister Desolate Ancient Moon suddenly comprehended: "No wonder wisdom Gu flew away immediately after speaking and did not let us question it. I have understood the truth of life."

"The truth of life, what exactly is it?" Northern Dark Ice Soul quickly asked.

Desolate Ancient Moon pointed at this blue sea in front of them and asked in return: "Tell me, if we were to really find a life Gu, a human shaped blue gem, and we bring it back, what will it transform into?"

Northern Dark Ice Soul thought for a moment and replied: "It should be like that fawn and turn into a real active life form, right?"

He suddenly looked distracted.

Desolate Ancient Moon looked at him with a smile: "It seems you have also understood. We are these life forms. We were formed from life Gu! We, ourselves, are human shaped blue gems!"

Northern Dark Ice Soul completely understood, where did humans come from?

Wisdom Gu had already made it clear before: This blue sea is the source of all living beings, all lives in the world originate from here.

Humans, naturally also originated from here.

Their father Ren Zu was once a blue gem in the depths of this sea. By some opportunity and coincidence, it was able to come out from the sea and form a zestful life form that roamed the world, surviving with difficulty and reaching this stage.

But humans were the spirit of all living beings, so how many human shaped gems could there be in such a large sea?

It was definitely extremely few, and it was very possible Ren Zu was the only one.

Searching for a small blue gem in such a vast sea, how big of a project was this!

This was innumerable times more difficult than Desolate Ancient Moon looking for the only success Gu in Cheng Bai mountain.

"I know a method which can get us a human shaped life Gu quickly." Desolate Ancient Moon suddenly said.

"What method?" Northern Dark Ice Soul had a bad feeling.

Desolate Ancient Moon smiled: "That is... I will go into the bottom of the sea and assimilate with this blue sea, returning back to a life Gu."

Although Desolate Ancient Moon had transformed into a monster, she was intrinsically a human.

The essence of her life had not changed.

Since she was a human, once she was assimilated, she would form a human shaped blue gem like life Gu.

This speculation was not wrong.

No wonder wisdom Gu said: But remember, you cannot spend over fifteen minutes in the sea, otherwise you will be assimilated by the sea.

Wisdom Gu's words did not have any superfluous words.

Wisdom Gu had also said: If you are not able to do it, don't blame my solution for not being easy to use.

One could analyze from this sentence — it was extremely likely there were no human shaped blue gems in the blue sea. If the siblings were not willing to sacrifice themselves, they would not be able to obtain human shaped life Gu. As such, don't blame me, the wisdom Gu, if you are not able to do it.

"No, you can't sacrifice yourself like this, elder sister." Northern Dark Ice Soul immediately dissuaded.

Although he wanted to bring his father back to life, he did not want to sacrifice his own sister.

"I need to do it, the meaning of my life is to bring father back to life." Desolate Ancient Moon replied tranquilly.

Northern Dark Ice Soul suddenly could not say anything.

It was him who gave this meaning to Desolate Ancient Moon's life, and Desolate Ancient Moon was living for this. In other words, if her father could not be brought back to life, there would be no meaning in her life. Then what would be the use in continuing to live?

As long as she sacrificed herself, she could bring her father back to life; this was the greatest meaning of Desolate Ancient Moon's life!

"Humans originally were gems of the world. It is only that whether the gems are bright or not require us to polish them. Every effort we make, every choice we take, are all polishing each of our gems."

"And humans can only obtain life by sacrificing life."

Desolate Ancient Moon leisurely spoke before sinking into the blue sea.

Northern Dark Ice Soul tried his best to stop her, but he was not able to. Desolate Ancient Moon had become a monster with incomparable strength, and he was not her match.

After fifteen minutes of time, Desolate Ancient Moon was assimilated by the blue sea and turned into a human shaped blue gem.

But this blue gem was not of a healthy human shape but a badly damaged, less than half a proper human shape.

This was because Desolate Ancient Moon had given her 'middle age' to wisdom Gu.

Humans, in the process of understanding what life was, would often have already used up half of their lives.

Northern Dark Ice Soul held this blue gem with tears in his eyes, and left the golden desert.

He did not have any of the happiness of success, but instead sank down into extreme remorse.

From a certain perspective, it was him who had killed his elder sister.

　　...

"There are still fifty steps left!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted with all his strength.

They pushed forward with difficulty with a companion falling down every short moment, the intense and bitter battle had left them with only five people now!

But success was right in front of their eyes!

"Just a little more of a push..."

"I will tear these blood beasts into pieces!!"

Zhu Zai and Gao Yang protected Tai Bai Yun Sheng from left and right; they also shouted to raise the morale.

Thirty steps!

Two more fell down, leaving behind Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Zhu and Gao.

The surrounding blood beasts brandished their claws and fangs, looking extremely malevolent. They advanced wave upon wave in their endless numbers.

Ten steps!

Zhu Zai and Gao Yang used all their strength, suffering disastrous losses to their Gu worms because of excessive use, and their primeval essence was also almost depleted.

"This old man owes both of you a favor, I swear I will definitely reward you heavily sometime in the future!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes shone brightly, his tone extremely earnest and sincere.

"Old sir, what are you saying! We were saved by you back then, without old sir, we would not be alive today!"

"Old sir's life saving favor is as heavy as a mountain! Even if we die today, it can be considered repaying your favor."

Gao Yang and Zhu Zai replied, full of emotions.

There existed two-faced hypocrites in the righteous path, and demonic path likewise was not without true heroes!

Five steps!

"Save me!" Zhu Zai shouted and without caring for defense, pounced on the blood beasts blocking the way forward, perishing together with them.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng stretched out his palm but the white light did not come out.

He shouted out involuntarily: "Not good, my primeval essence is finished!"

This bad news immediately made Gao Yang's expression turn pale white.

All along, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had served as the core of the group. Only with man as before Gu's continuous support, everyone was able to push forward this deep.

"It doesn't matter, no blood beasts will enter the great hall. As long as I can enter the great hall, I can recover my primeval essence quickly and save Zhu Zai!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted.

Gao Yang's spirits rose.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was right, blood beasts might tear apart the corpse, but their main priority was absorbing the blood. As long as most of the corpse was intact, there was hope of saving Zhu Zai.

Snarl!

Next moment, a strong blood beast that looked like a giant python suddenly moved in from behind and swallowed Gao Yang in one bite!

Two steps!

The great hall's door was very close; with a body filled with injuries, Tai Bai Yun Sheng staggered forward through a small gap among the blood beasts.

At the crucial moment, he used up his final precious bit of primeval essence to summon a golden armor which resisted the blood beasts' attacks.

He reached!

"Humans can only obtain life by sacrificing life. Gao Yang, Zhu Zai, I will remember your sacrifices!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng exerted all his remaining strength to push open the door.

He fell down inside the great hall, the blood beasts behind him roared, snarled and brandished their claws, but did not dare to enter the great hall.

It was just like what Tai Bai Yun Sheng had investigated before.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng lay down on the ground with no strength left in his body. The injuries all over his body were continually transmitting intense pain.

He took a few strong gasps of breath, and suddenly started laughing heartily, but his laughter contained a sobbing tone.

Tears were overflowing on his face.

"This round has three great halls and sixty-nine side halls! If one crosses the round completely within a certain time period, they can obtain high grade evaluation. Passing two great halls and forty-six side halls will be considered middle grade evaluation. I surpassed twenty-three side halls and one great hall, I can only obtain low grade evaluation. But regardless, I have obtained lifespan Gu!"

"Fifteen year lifespan Gu can increase my lifespan by fifteen years. A whole fifteen years..."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was exclaiming with deep and boundless emotion, when suddenly, his eyes blacked out and he fainted.

Chapter 592: Deep Dark Shadow

Fang Yuan lowered his head, observing Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had already fainted and lost consciousness.

He was the culprit who caused Tai Bai Yun Sheng to fall unconscious.

At this moment, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's body was bathed in blood, he was lying on the ground and within his deep eye sockets, his eyes were tightly shut.

There were lots of injuries on him, his snow white hair had stuck together because of dried blood, he no longer had the demeanour and appearance of the number one healing Gu Master in northern plains.

Merely a few steps away, outside the main hall's doors, a sea of blood beasts were growling, the messy overlapping noises were sent over with great force.

Fang Yuan raised his head, staring at them as he opened his mouth and said lightly: "Shut up."

Almost immediately, there was silence outside the hall.

The blood beasts all became quiet, lying prostrate on the ground like obedient cats or dogs, staying motionless.

Fang Yuan made use of the six-edge owner token to control this floor, he was the master of this floor, these beasts were all his to control, they listened to his commands and moved according to his will.

Fang Yuan shut his eyes, his mind entering this floor's control system as he let his senses observe the area.

At the moment, in this particular round, there were many Gu Masters remaining.

Among these Gu Masters, some were Gu Masters recruited by Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but during the earlier fighting they had been separated from the main party. Another portion were the information gatherers of all the different forces, they were all investigative Gu Masters. They came from Hei tribe, Ma Tribe, Ye Lui tribe, and all the other large forces, with the intention of observing whether Tai Bai Yun Sheng failed or succeeded.

As for this hall and its surroundings, within them, other than those rotten and dried corpses, only Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were left now.

Fang Yuan closed the great hall's door, half squatting on the ground as he stretched out his right palm, grabbing onto Tai Bai Yun Sheng's skull.

His Gu worms had been prepared long ago, he activated them one by one.

Very soon, above Tai Bai Yun Sheng's head, a weak shining white light was formed, becoming the only source of light in this dark and dim great hall.

As the light got more and more intense, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's face gradually showed a painful expression, and his brows were frowning more intensely.

After a moment of stillness, Fang Yuan suddenly opened his eyes!

His eyes had no pupils, it was pure white in color.

The whites of his eyes gave off a weak light as at the same time, a large number of images flashed across in Fang Yuan's mind.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life, from his old age all the way until he was young, all the memories had been extracted by Fang Yuan.

　　...

An old man was walking in northern plains, the sky was vast and the wilderness was boundless, the winds blew as the grass was drooping in response, wolf groups were howling freely.

　　...

"Old sir, we brothers will never forget the kindness you have displayed by saving our lives!" Gao Yang and Zhu Zai kneeled down together before Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

　　...

A purple haired old beggar opened his mouth, showing his remaining few teeth, laughing in a weird manner: "What kind of Gu Master do you want to become? Hehehe, I happen to have three complete sets of inheritances with me here!"

　　...

"Mm, this lad has a passable appearance, we will choose him." In the inkmen city, an inkman was pointing at Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was in his youth as he laughed loudly and said.

Even further back, during the time when he was even younger...

"Why, why did you betray me?!" On the night of their joyous wedding, Tai Bai Yun Sheng fell weakly on the ground as extremely loud shouting and fighting noises resounded outside the tent.

As for his wife, she had an expression full of coldness and hatred, she slowly got close to him as her eyes shone with a ruthless light, she gritted her teeth as she said: "Tai Bai Yun Sheng, if you want to blame someone, blame your parents. They were the ones who devoured my tribe, they killed my parents, I want to exact revenge for them!"

During the time of his childhood...

"My son, you are the next generation tribe leader of our Tai Bai tribe! You are not allowed to cry, do not have the heart of needless sympathy! To survive in northern plains, we need to have a tougher heart, a tougher stance! After all in the future, you have to lead our Tai Bai tribe." His father was scolding him in a very strict manner.

　　...

"Ahhh..." Fang Yuan was screaming from the intense pain.

In his mind, countless images were flashing, they were depicting Tai Bai Yun Sheng's entire life, a legendary tale. Such a huge amount of information had a large impact on Fang Yuan's mind and caused great damage to him.

Thankfully, the images were not endless and unceasing, there came a time when they finally ended.

After browsing through Tai Bai Yun Sheng's entire life, Fang Yuan immediately stopped using his Gu worms, sitting down on the ground to rest.

He was breathing roughly and panting, his entire body was coated in sweat. A long time later, his pupils regained their original color.

Soul searching, this was not an easy action. Especially when Fang Yuan was concerned about Tai Bai Yun Sheng's safety and did not want to cause harm to his life, he could only endure most of the pressure of the soul search himself.

After stopping the soul search, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was still sound asleep, but his tightly knitted brows had slowly eased as he relaxed. His breathing was more stable now, and his expression was rather peaceful.

In contrast, Fang Yuan's brows were starting to frown instead.

"I did not find it!" He heaved a long sigh in pity.

"What did you not manage to find?" In his mind, Mo Yao's will could not hold in her curiosity as she asked.

Fang Yuan's actions were very strange, it made her very curious.

Fang Yuan did not answer her, he only frowned even more as time passed. The matter of landscape as before Gu was related to his grand scheme after rebirth, how could he possibly tell this to Mo Yao?

Landscape as before Gu was an Immortal Gu that Tai Bai Yun Sheng obtained only after he became an immortal.

Rumors said: This Gu was created naturally on its own when Tai Bai Yun Sheng became an immortal, and heaven and earth resonated with him, causing it to spontaneously condense.

But there was another possibility, that within Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mind, he had the Immortal Gu recipe for Landscape As Before from the start.

If he really had the Immortal Gu recipe, then Fang Yuan could steal this Gu recipe, along with river as before Gu and mountain as before Gu, bringing to Lang Ya blessed land and asking Lang Ya land spirit to help by refining this Immortal Gu on his behalf.

This way, he did not have to take a risk and seize the food from the tiger's mouth, it would greatly reduce his danger.

But after this soul search, Fang Yuan obtained a horrible result.

Fang Yuan did not manage to find the Immortal Gu recipe for Landscape As Before, this indicated that the rumors were really true. Landscape as before Gu was indeed a product of the resonance of heaven and earth during the moment when Tai Bai Yun Sheng became a Gu Immortal.

That also meant that: If Fang Yuan wanted to obtain this Immortal Gu, he would have to snatch this Gu by force from Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had already become an immortal by then.

Fang Yuan was still not a Gu Immortal, as for battling an immortal as a mortal, Fang Yuan had never heard of any examples of success in his life, it was no doubt tougher than ascending to heaven!

But what other choices did he have?

Back then, among the three options, this was no doubt the easiest way. He had already invested time and effort into this plan, although Fang Yuan did not have absolute confidence of success, he had no choice but to continue making preparations and take a risk to try it anyway!

　　...

Outside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's image appeared slowly.

"He is back, he is back!"

"How was the result? Someone saw Tai Bai Yun Sheng fighting his way into the main hall."

"Oh no, Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng is motionless, it seems he has fallen unconscious!"

The surrounding Gu Masters immediately went over as a crowd.

After taking a look, all of their expression changed mildly. Tai Bai Yun Sheng's body was filled with extremely serious injuries, they were all secretly stunned in their hearts.

"He is still breathing!" Someone stretched out his finger and placed it below Tai Bai Yun Sheng's nose, shouting loudly: "Quick, who is a healing Gu Master, quickly stabilize Old Sir's current injuries!"

"I will do it, I will do it!"

"I am also a healing Gu Master!!"

Many healing Gu Masters quickly helped out, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's reputation and extremely kind hearted nature had already been ingrained in everyone's hearts.

There was no doubt that he was much more popular and loved by people compared to Hei Lou Lan and Chang Shan Yin.

"Even Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng suffered injuries to such a grave extent, sigh, it seems that this time, the round might not have been passed." Someone sighed.

"The time for the challenge has already ended, but most of the Gu Masters did not return safely, we have truly suffered a huge loss this time!"

"Among all of you, has anyone seen Lord Gao Yang and Zhu Zai coming out?" Someone jolted abruptly, suddenly asking.

Everyone started looking around frantically, but they just ended up staring at each other.

No one saw the figures of Gao Yang and Zhu Zai, meanwhile in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, that round was still intact and available for challengers. Except that in this short period, Gu Masters were not allowed to enter again.

Everyone was very clear about what this implied.

Ever since Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had formed, five rank five experts had already been sacrificed.

Such grave casualties and losses, it caused the entire area to go into deep silence.

When Tai Bai Yun Sheng opened his eyes eventually, he found himself lying on a bed, his entire body was feeling weak to the point where he even had difficulties sitting up.

Seeing that he opened his eyes, a servant nearby who was attending to him shouted immediately out of joy: "Old sir, you are finally awake, you have finally woken up! Someone quickly come, someone quickly come, old sir has woken up!"

Very soon, Tai Bai Yun Sheng could hear a large number of footsteps rushing over towards him.

A group of healing Gu Masters came to his side, checking his body's condition for him collectively.

"Lord elder, rest assured, your injuries are no longer a problem. Except that you are of old age, so the injuries this time have affected your physical condition. From now on, you have to recuperate carefully, especially for the next few months, your body is weak and lacking in nourishment, you need to rest and recover slowly." The head of the healing Gu Masters urged him in a gentle tone.

In order to get a team to challenge the round, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had no choice but to agree to Hei Lou Lan's request and had already become an external elder of Hei tribe.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze was completely unfocused, ever since he woke up, he had been in a daze, after hearing these words, he regained some of his senses as he asked: "Where is this place?"

"Replying to lord elder's question, this is Lord Hei Lou Lan's residence. Ever since lord elder failed in challenging the round, and returned barely alive, our tribe leader has been very concerned, he personally brought you here to receive treatment. The servants have already reported your awakening, I believe that very soon, lord tribe leader will be here to see you." The leader of the Gu Masters once again replied.

"Failed in challenging the round, and returning barely alive?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng frowned slightly, the memories in his mind were slowly surfacing, as he recalled that final scene that had happened —

He expended his final portion of primeval essence, activating his defense Gu as he successfully charged into the great hall amidst the attacks and rampaging of the blood beasts.

But soon after, he fainted and fell unconscious, losing perception of all his senses!

When he woke up, he found that he was lying here.

"Does that mean, I really failed in challenging the round?!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's tone suddenly turned sharp, as his gaze became sharper than ever.

"Lord elder..." The healing Gu Masters around the bed all looked at each other, they wanted to offer words of consolation, but they could not bring themselves to say a thing.

Thus, they could only lower their heads silently.

The room suddenly became completely quiet.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze was staring into the distance, after being silent for a while, he suddenly raised his head and laughed: "Haha, so I failed after all. All that sacrifice for nothing, all that sacrifice for absolutely nothing!"

He could not get up now, so he could only use his palm to slam the side of the bed with all his strength, laughing maniacally.

"Lord elder, lord elder!" The healing Gu Masters were frantic, they quickly tried to calm him down.

"My pitiful Gao Yang, my pitiful Zhu Zai, they sacrificed their lives in order to protect me!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes were overflowing with tears, his laughter was filled with pure agony.

"My condolences to lord elder, there is a limit to what a person can do, lord elder had already done his best!"

"Lord elder, the fact that you managed to survive is already the greatest fortune among misfortunes."

"People die when they are killed, the dead cannot be resurrected, old sir, you have to stay strong for all of us..."

Everyone spoke one after another, trying to calm down the unstable Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

But these words felt like utter sarcasm when they entered Tai Bai Yun Sheng's ears. They were like needles stabbing into his heart one by one.

At the final crucial moment, Tai Bai Yun Sheng preserved his primeval essence and did not choose to save Gao Yang and Zhu Zai. It was for himself, to activate the defense Gu and charge into the main hall.

That was him, for his own selfish gains, he had ignored the sacrifices of his comrades.

Was this still Tai Bai Yun Sheng?

Was this still that admirable and publicly recognised figure in northern plains who helped and saved the injured, healing people everywhere, the Tai Bai Yun Sheng who eliminated pain and suffering?

Why did he do that?

But at that crucial moment, he had no time to think about it carefully, he chose to do it in an instant!

Purposely sacrificing Gao Yang and Zhu Zai to obtain a chance for himself to obtain that fifteen year lifespan Gu which was the reward for passing the round! It was for his own purpose of extending his life!

Such a decision made Tai Bai Yun Sheng feel very unfamiliar with himself, he felt extremely ashamed, extremely inferior, and extremely regretful!

Back then, there was no hesitation, he did not think about it, that decision had transformed his morals into a whip, interrogating his soul and lashing at his conscience!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng shut his eyes in great pain, his fists were tightly clenched.

"Lord tribe leader has arrived!"

"Subordinate pays respects to lord tribe leader."

The entire room kneeled, as Hei Lou Lan carried a smiling expression and walked towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Seeing Tai Bai Yun Sheng's pained expression, Hei Lou Lan frowned lightly, but soon his frown vanished: "Elder Tai Bai, I am very glad that you are awake. I have already heard about the situation, you, Gao Yang, and Zhu Zai had displayed the bravery and courage of us northern plains men, although you failed, it was an admirable attempt! As long as you learn from this attempt, I'm sure you'll be able to pass this round in the future, overwriting failure with success and washing away the humiliation."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not open his eyes, he did not speak a word as his expression remained painful.

He had already understood the reason why he failed.

After he charged into the main hall, he had successfully avoided the attacks of the blood beasts as he fell on the main hall. But after succeeding, he laughed wildly in great joy, and because his state of mind had been greatly volatile and fluctuating, together with his grave injuries, he lost consciousness.

To get through this round, there was a time limit as well.

Once the time was up, his unconscious self was sent out forcefully along with the other Gu Masters at the fringe of the battlefield.

He was obviously a single step away from success, but he failed because he had fallen unconscious.

Such an ironic ending, this was not the source of the intense pain in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart.

His pain was because he had abandoned his comrades for his own selfish gains.

Was this still Tai Bai Yun Sheng?

His memories flashed in his mind one by one once more.

From youth, he had always believed in the power of love.

Since he was a child, he had been reputed to have a kind heart.

When Tai Bai tribe devoured other tribes, he saw that his childhood friend was going to suffer the horrible fate of becoming a female slave, thus he stepped up and requested to marry her. Because of this, the batch of captives were also spared.

But on the night of their wedding, his wife betrayed him. The captives contacted outside enemies and assaulted his tribe, causing his parents to die from this incident.

His slave life after that was extremely tough and pitiful, and he had always been suffering the intense guilt and regret in his heart.

Finally, one day, he gave an unacquainted old beggar a bowl of water out of kindness, and the old beggar gave him three immortal inheritances to choose from.

The first could allow him to bathe in flames and step on fire, surpassing the mortal realm.

The second could allow him to control wind and fly in the air, roaming the world freely.

The third could allow him to surpass life and death, gaining the ability to assist the world's people.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng chose the third inheritance.

From then on, it was as if he found the light in the darkness, his heart was no longer in turmoil as he had no regrets anymore, he had been completely reborn!

After so many years, the old beggar's laughter was still ringing in his ears.

Surpassing life and death, gaining the ability to help people, this had become his life's goal.

And indeed, he truly achieved this in his life later on.

Countless people felt gratitude towards him, his kind reputation had spread widely, his light was shining over the entire northern plains.

He was a living legend.

But right now!

He had failed!

His failure was not in that he did not receive the lifespan Gu. But because he betrayed his comrades, he betrayed the way of life that he had set for himself!!

But the most ironic thing was, all these were done by his own subconscious.

He spent almost his entire life to establish a way of life for himself that he believed in. But that at moment, he completely destroyed his own ideals.

He had seen the other side of himself, his own selfish nature.

He had once thought, he was the person everyone knew him as — walking on the grassland under the setting sun, helping and saving people throughout the region, the savior of the world.

But now, in his heart, this image was slowly leaving him, it was limping away from him.

In the brilliance of the setting sun, his shadow was stretched out and extended into the horizon.

The shadow was extremely dark...

Chapter 593: Appearance of the strength path Immortal Gu

Hei Lou Lan's brows furrowed as he walked out of Tai Bai Yun Sheng's room.

"An expert cannot become conceited by success nor discouraged by failure; who could have thought the grand, renowned Tai Bai Yun Sheng was no more than this." he was very dissatisfied with Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mental state.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng is the number one healer, if his state is not good, the difficulty for me to cross the rounds will increase by a lot." Hei Lou Lan raised his head and looked above.

On the summit of the sacred palace, the bright aurora was surging majestically.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had already condensed sixty-seven floors and was currently condensing sixty-eighth floor.

Hei Lou Lan gazed at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building with an obsessed look, a cold light of ambition flashing in his eyes.

In the sixty-eighth floor there existed a strength path Immortal Gu!

Hei Lou Lan possessed an one-edge owner token, this strength path Immortal Gu was assimilated into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building just moments ago, and he could immediately perceive it.

This was a rank six strength path Immortal Gu called flying bear strength Gu.

The flying bear was a desolate beast with battle strength that could match Gu Immortals.

Flying bear strength Gu could allow the Gu Immortal to have a definite probability of bursting out with a flying bear phantom during battle and strike with the divine strength of flying bear.

This was the Immortal Gu Hei Lou Lan wanted. With it, he could advance into a strength path Gu Immortal!

"I must get this Immortal Gu in my hands. My plan for revenge only has hope if I have it!" Hei Lou Lan unconsciously clenched his fists, but soon relaxed.

His trusted aide Hei Shu came towards him in short, quick steps, and kneeled before him.

Hei Lou Lan's expression quickly changed back to normal.

Even in front of his trusted aide, he did not reveal even a trace of his true emotions.

Every day, during this time, Hei Shu would come to report on the movements of every great expert in the sacred palace: "Lord Chang Shan Yin is still at the ninetieth round of seventh floor and has still not made any progress. Lord Ye Lui Sang is at the forty-ninth floor, he has crossed the eighty-first round, thirty percent of the Gu Masters with him have perished...."

Hei Lou Lan had completely opened up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to everyone; it was a generous move that was rarely seen in the history, attracting a craze in everyone to explore Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Even though every owner token's price was raised to a sky-high amount, there were still countless people scrambling for them madly.

Humans die for wealth and birds die for food; blinded by greed, many had lost their lives.

Adding the casualties from the attempt of Tai Bai Yun Sheng, five rank five experts had died already - Chang Biao, Pan Ping, Hao Ji Liu, Gao Yang and Zhu Zai. This was an enormous loss to Hei Lou Lan.

The smaller the forces he could mobilize became, the harder the difficulty in getting flying bear strength Gu.

Of course, there was also a certain benefit by completely opening up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. As long as the participating Gu Masters could survive, most would be able to experience rapid increase in strength.

There were also not a small number who were able to successfully advance, creating many new rank four and rank five Gu Masters.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was originally arranged by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable for the benefit of his descendants.

"This sixty-eighth floor is the main focus of our tribe, it even far surpasses winning over the thirty-ninth floor. This is a task specially handed to me by a certain supreme elder of our tribe. Thus, every bit of strength in the sacred palace needs to be treasured. Hei Shu, make this news public: Starting now, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building will be closed and everyone will listen to my arrangements. After breaking through the sixty-eighth floor, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building will be opened again." Hei Lou Lan instructed, his tone containing a will that could not be questioned.

When Hei Shu heard this was actually a task given by the tribe's supreme elder, his body shook and his expression turned extremely solemn.

"Get to work." Hei Lou Lan waved his hand.

Hei Shu accepted the command and retreated.

Every Imperial Court contest was a chess game played by Gu Immortals. Even the stronger Gu Masters were no more than chess pieces.

To seek some kind of Immortal Gu, Gu Immortals would provide support to certain tribes participating in the Imperial Court contest. This was a common set of circumstances.

Hei Lou Lan was sure that everyone would be dissatisfied by his decision to close Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, but under the pressure of a Gu Immortal's reputation, no one would dare to raise an issue.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng's injuries are too severe, but I can make him participate in the battle after he rests for about half a month. After all, he is a healing Gu Master and will be in the rear of the battlefield. He needs lifespan Gu, I can start from this aspect to mobilize him."

"Chang Shan Yin is fighting the seventh floor. Hehe, his days have not been easy because his son suddenly perished in this round. To get back his reputation, he must pass this round. But he demanded flying bear phantom Immortal Gu from me before, taking loans and owing me a great deal of resources. I can mobilize him."

"There is also Ye Lui Sang, he has a fire path support type Immortal Gu and would be of strong help to me. I can entice him with heavy bait...of course, the crucial point will still be using the strength of the three Gu Immortals, Xue Song Zi, Hei Cheng and Hei Bai. Hehehe, I should send them letters."

　　...

Hei Bai was extremely excited after reading Hei Lou Lan's letter: "I waited so long and now finally the wooden chicken Gu has appeared, I did not think it would be within the sixty-eighth floor."

He did not doubt the contents of this letter in the least.

After all, Hei Lou Lan was Hei Cheng's son, and was the current Hei tribe leader. If his loyalty was doubted, then was there anyone in the world who was worth trusting?

Hei Cheng smiled brightly: "Virtuous brother, every cloud has a silver lining, hard work will eventually pay off. Did the letter mention anything about strength path Immortal Gu?"

Hei Bai's face flushed red: "I am ashamed, I was only thinking of wooden chicken Gu and forgot about nephew's situation. Nephew has Great Strength True Martial Physique, he must have a strength path Immortal Gu to advance to Gu Immortal. Nephew has mentioned about this in the letter, but unfortunately a strength path Immortal Gu has yet to appear in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building."

"Still no strength path Immortal Gu?" Hei Cheng frowned.

Previously, when Hei Bai had been worried about wooden chicken Gu, he was consoled by Hei Cheng. This time, it was Hei Bai's turn to console Hei Cheng: "Brother, no need to worry, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has altogether eighty-eight floors, there are still twenty floors that have not condensed yet."

Hei Cheng nodded, sighing: "Immortal Gu Dark Limit won't be able to mask his physique any longer, this can almost be considered as my son's final chance at life. Sigh... Man proposes and God disposes, we can only leave things to the will of heaven."

Hei Bai's heart was fervent as he changed the topic back to wooden chicken Gu. He reminded: "Brother, time waits for no man, let's quickly prepare to give some help to Hei Lou Lan!"

"Yes. This matter demands immediate actions, which place did the letter mention?" Hei Cheng slowly stood up from his seat.

Hei Bai also followed suit and stood up: "It is near Demon Blood Hill."

"Let's go."

The two Gu Immortals were very straightforward as they immediately set off.

Not long later, they arrived at the sky above Demon Blood Hill.

Demon Blood Hill was a famous area in northern plains where four great tribes of the righteous path had allied to annihilate a gang of demonic path bandits who had been ravaging around northern plains.

The demonic path bandits were extremely fierce because of their deep background, with demonic path Gu Immortals secretly supporting them from the dark.

After the intense battle, the bandit gang was completely annihilated while the righteous path also suffered serious losses. The blood of demonic path Gu Masters dyed the whole hill red, and thus later generations called the hill 'Demon Blood Hill'.

Hei Lou Lan had requested help in the letter.

Hei tribe's two Gu Immortals had already prepared for a long time and were ready to leave at any time; this was to help Hei Lou Lan to clear the floor as fast as possible.

But Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was located in Imperial Court blessed land, why would the two Gu Immortals from Hei tribe come here?

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's structure needed to be mentioned for this.

The previous ink text had explained: Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was a rank eight Immortal Gu house formed from innumerable small towers, with divert disaster Gu as one of the main cornerstones.

There were gaps of several li between each small tower, covering Imperial Court blessed land in accordance to each region of northern plains. During ordinary times, the small towers would be taking in the wild Gu within Imperial Court blessed land. As every ten year period arrived, these small towers would start to sink one after another, sacrificing the wild Gu inside them while also resonating with the blizzard in the outside world to achieve a miraculous power.

This power would carry out an enormous plundering of the whole of northern plains, taking in the precious Gu resources of northern plains to above the sacred palace in Imperial Court blessed land, and thus condensing floor after floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

These floors would form on top of one another, finally forming the complete Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!

Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's plan had been rejected by Long Hair Ancestor. Long Hair Ancestor was a refinement path supreme grandmaster, and thought of an exquisite plan with a different approach, refining the current Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Every time Eighty-Eight True Yang Building formed was a process of refining Gu once again.

It not only made use of the wild Gu in the small towers but also the Gu worms absorbed into it.

For example, looking at the sixty-eighth floor, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building first absorbed flying bear strength Gu and refined it, using the strength of the Gu to form the hundredth round.

Again, absorbing other strong Gu worms to form the ninety-ninth round. Following was the ninety-eight round, ninety-seventh.....

It was like building a high building, one must first build a strong foundation.

If there were not qualified Gu worms, then Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would replace it with Gu recipe, primeval stones, inheritance secrets and so on.

Everyone knew the harder the rounds in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building were, the more bountiful the rewards would be. Conversely, the more bountiful the rewards or stronger the Gu worms, the more difficult the round would be.

One could say every Gu worm assimilated into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was a part of its structure.

Countless Imperial Court contests passed by while countless generations of sagely immortals had been probing before the workings of this mechanism of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building were finally discovered.

Originally, there were no flaws in this.

But with the passing of time, changes started to appear which created a loophole, allowing northern plains' Gu Masters to exploit it.

This loophole was in the aspect of 'refinement'.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building plundered northern plains and absorbed Gu worms, 'refining' them and using their strength to form rounds.

What did Gu refinement rely on?

Will!

Back then, how did Fang Yuan refine the liquor worm?

By using primeval essence as a carrier for the Gu Master's will to continually wear down the Gu worm's will, until the Gu worm was filled with the Gu Master's will, thoroughly turning into the Gu Master's tool.

When Fang Yuan refined Gu, he had used Immortal Gu Spring Autumn Cicada to get the desired result at the least expense.

If the Gu worms differ by two ranks or more, there would be suppression. Fang Yuan used Spring Autumn Cicada's aura to force the lower ranked Gu worm's will to curl up at a corner, and then poured in his primeval essence and will straight into the Gu worm, swallowing the withdrawn Gu worm's will.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was not a Gu Master, how could it refine other Gu worms?

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, thus, intentionally left behind his will!

Giant Sun's will!

Fang Yuan had seen Giant Sun's will when he was refining the guest halt stele before. It was genuinely majestic and vast like the sun.

Comparatively speaking, the will Fang Yuan left behind after refining the guest halt stele was as minute as an ant.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building refined Gu worms by using Giant Sun's will.

Immortal Venerable were unrivalled, their wills were also similarly unrivalled and could easily extinguish other wills.

Thus, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had never encountered any problems when refining Gu worms.

However, there was a problem.

Wills were formed from thoughts, if there was not a soul to act as the carrier, continuous thinking would only lead to unceasing consumption.

To resist such astonishing consumption, the will would often choose to hibernate.

When Fang Yuan entered Water Pavilion, Mo Yao's will which was stored inside had awoken from her hibernation.

Giant Sun's will might be vast as the Sun, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had passed away for countless years now; the will was gradually unable to resist the power of time and also chose to hibernate!

When Giant Sun's will went into hibernation, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's Gu refinement speed slowed down.

This reduction in speed caused a loophole to appear in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Chapter 594: Plan activated!

Strong winds blew and snow wreaked havoc.

Demon Blood Hill which used to have dark red grass growing all over was now a scene of whiteness.

The lofty hill also had surrendered to the power of ten year's blizzard, appearing weak as a baby.

Roar Roar Roar....

Enormous figures that were as tall as thirty feet, appeared and disappeared in the blizzard. These were monsters that only appeared during the blizzard — snow monsters.

These snow monsters were stronger the larger their size.

A thirty feet tall snow monster could battle a rank three Gu Master. Forty feet tall had the strength of a rank four Gu Master. And fifty feet tall had the terrifying power of a rank five Gu Master.

Following the blizzard, the snow monsters began to devastate the whole of Northern Plains.

They slowly converged together and attacked several surviving areas of Northern Plains, bringing destruction to the dying humans and living beings.

But there is a weakness to everything, snow monsters were snowmen's prey.

Snowmen could rapidly propagate by devouring snow monsters' meat and blood, even prolonging their lifespan.

Hei Bai and Hei Cheng stood on the summit of the Demon Blood Hill for a while.

Their black robes were exceptionally conspicuous in the white snowy land.

Beside them were corpses of hundreds of snow monsters. Unless snow monsters that had reached the height of sixty feet appeared, even in great numbers they could only be trash throwing away their lives when fighting Gu Immortals.

Hei Bai and Hei Cheng had already waited for a long time now.

Suddenly, Hei Bai's expression shook as he got a response, his sharp gaze looking at his left.

There, maelstroms of wind and snow started to form in the air.

Within a blink of an eye, they turned one by one into whole giant hands formed from wind and snow — flying snow hand.

After the enormous flying snow hands condensed completely, they grabbed at Hei Bai and Hei Cheng.

"Haha, we have been waiting for you." Hei Bai laughed brightly and flicked his finger repeatedly, sending out large numbers of rank five Gu worms.

Hei Cheng also made his move.

The enormous flying snow hands grabbed Gu worms and soon each of them clenched tightly. The snow hands crumbled apart while the Gu worms inside disappeared without a trace, captured tightly by a power that took them into Imperial Court blessed land.

Hei tribe's two Gu Immortals did not resist in the slightest and let the Gu worms be taken by the flying snow hands.

Such a situation lasted for a whole hour before all the rank five Gu worms were captured away. Hei Bai and Hei Cheng only then stopped, looking at each other with a smile before flying away rapidly, disappearing into the horizon in a blink of an eye.

"Support has arrived!" After some time, Hei Lou Lan got a response, his gaze burned as he gazed above at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

At the peak of the sacred palace, an aurora was shaking.

The sixty-eighth floor was still condensing with the hundredth round already being formed before. The still not formed sixty-eighth floor was only in its embryonic stage, the aurora around it continually shook like liquid, holding the large numbers of Gu worms captured just before from outside the blessed land.

A part of these Gu worms were wild Gu whereas a portion came from Hei Cheng and Hei Bai, two Gu Immortals.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building chose the strongest among them to form the ninety-ninth round, ninety-eighth round....

Hei Lou Lan carefully sensed it for a while before slightly frowning: "The two from Hei tribes have already made their move but that Xue Song Zi is still biding his time, hmph!"

He had bribed Xue Song Zi to reach an agreement. One of the contents of the agreement was Xue Song Zi help him at a designated time period.

However, Xue Song Zi was not showing any signs of movement at present.

Hei Lou Lan was displeased, immediately sending a letter through a Gu worm.

Soon, he received the reply.

In the letter, Xue Song Zi complained about how the two Gu Immortals from Hei tribe were pressuring him these days and how his snowman business had taken a dive, already running at a loss. He also added how he had already supported Hei Lou Lan with many rank five Gu for wooden chicken Gu some time ago. And it was beyond his power to send support now.

"Lies!" Hei Lou Lan was furious, almost pinching this letter Gu to death, "There is indeed no one good in the demonic path, they all are treacherous and sly bastards."

But soon, Hei Lou Lan's anger subsided.

Truthfully, he had predicted this.

After all, he was only a mortal while Xue Song Zi was a lofty Gu Immortal. A mortal dealing with a Gu Immortal was like an ant negotiating with an elephant.

The two were simply not at the same level. If the Gu Immortal refused to acknowledge and reneged back on the promise, the mortal could do nothing about it.

Hei Lou Lan was secretly worried.

The sixty-eighth floor was in the process of condensing and the longer the time went by, the weaker the effect of a Gu Immortal's support would be.

"It seems, I need to first obtain wooden chicken Gu to make Xue Song Zi help me!" Hei Lou Lan sneered, immediately sending an order to convene everyone.

Wooden chicken Gu was on the thirty-ninth floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

For months now, Hei Lou Lan's efforts had been concentrated on this floor. He also had Xue Song Zi's help, thus the progress was very smooth, succeeding in pushing to the last round.

Wooden chicken Gu was exactly the reward for this final round.

This last round; it was difficult in a sense, but it was also very simple.

What it tested was patience in putting in effort over a long period of time.

Hei Lou Lan had personally led people and attempted the round for forty to fifty times altogether, now already having grasped its details. Every time, he would progress slightly and the accumulation of such progress gave shocking results. He was only a paper-thin distance away from success.

"This is good too. Grasping this thirty-ninth floor would raise the morale for when we tackle the sixty-eighth floor." Hei Lou Lan thought for a while and immediately took action.

The next day, he mustered large numbers of people, convening all the Gu Masters in the sacred palace, and held a pep rally.

That very evening, he led everyone and successfully broke through the hundredth round, obtaining rank six Immortal Gu Wooden Chicken.

Just like Hei Lou Lan expected, the breakthrough of the round raised morale and fighting spirit greatly, sweeping away the haze of Tai Bai Yun Sheng's defeat.

With Immortal Gu Wooden Chicken, Hei Lou Lan's confidence rose greatly and he used it to lure Xue Song Zi into helping him.

Seven days later, the sixty-eighth floor had completely taken form.

Hei Lou Lan impatiently led everyone to charge into the floor.

However, after arriving at the floor, he did not tackle the rounds anxiously, instead commanding the Gu Masters to spread out.

Over a hundred refinement path Gu Masters were included in the troops.

These people were all carefully selected and their loyalty could be trusted. Although they had not attained master level, they were elites.

The refinement path Gu Masters formed a round formation upon which Hei Lou Lan slowly walked into the center.

He sat down cross-legged and took out the two-edge owner token.

The two-edge owner token slowly flew into the air and at the same time, Hei Lou Lan's body also began to let out grey light.

The light rays were sharp as needles, piercing into the air.

Not only Hei Lou Lan, the remaining refinement path Gu Masters also let out sharp grey radiance.

These needle sharp light rays continued to strengthen, becoming thicker and longer, flooding the whole round formation.

The individual needle sharp rays started to touch each other, instantly linking together. A giant grey radiance slowly stretched out from the round formation, directly piercing into the two-edge owner token which was floating in the air.

Outside the round formation were large numbers of Gu Masters spectating this while guarding against emergencies.

"What are they doing?" A young Gu Master asked in confusion.

An aged senior beside him patted his shoulder: "Hehe, this is the ability of super tribes! Kid, watch properly, the next scene will make your eyes open and jaw fall down."

As he was saying this, the owner token suddenly shook.

The tremor was weak, but following the dissemination of the giant sharp grey radiance, the scope of the tremor quickly increased.

By the time this tremor spread to the round formation, it had already become a heavy tremor.

The grey light rays condensed in the round formation like a light lake. From this heavy tremor, the lake suddenly erupted with dazzling light, forcing everyone to narrow their eyes.

The grey light shone on every corner of the first round's area.

Just like the melting of snow, the world in the round gradually started turning transparent before completely dissipating.

It was like a cover had been lifted, and as if the second layer underneath was revealed, Hei Lou Lan and the group arrived at the second round.

"This is?!"

"We actually passed the round without even making a move?"

After a moment of silence, many young Gu Masters started making a big fuss.

That young Gu Master from just before had eyes wide open and his jaw hanging down: "What in the world is this method?"

The aged Gu Master beside replied with satisfaction: "This is a refinement path killer move that all super tribes have — Grey Meltdown. It can be used to rapidly pass rounds in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Kid, the scope of your vision should have expanded, right?"

The young Gu Master whose vision was expanded, nodded his head nonstop and praised: "Amazing! Truly an amazing method! But, what do they need us for with such a method in their disposal?"

The aged Gu Master's smile turned forced: "This method is not effective every time. Some rounds can be crossed with this method, while some cannot."

"Tsk tsk, this trick is quite interesting..." In Fang Yuan's mind, Mo Yao revealed her body.

Her posture was enchanting and her eyes had a hint of seduction. She mumbled to herself in an analytical way: "This should be digging into the hibernating will of Giant Sun's control, attacking with coordination from both outside and inside. The Gu Masters outside the blessed land would release Gu at certain places, and these Gu worms would be absorbed into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, refined into the rounds. But Giant Sun's will is hibernating, so the speed in refining the Gu worms has become slower. At best, they could only be considered half-refined."

"The so-called killer move grey meltdown uses the owner token to connect with the half-refined Gu worms. As such, the core of the round will be directly refined. The round will naturally not be able to continue anymore and switch to the next round."

"To do this, the crucial key is time. The state of the half-refined Gu won't continue for long. Even if Giant Sun's will is hibernating, as long as there is sufficient time, it will completely refine these Gu worms. In the case that these Gu worms are refined, the Gu Masters tackling the round cannot induce any reaction and the chance to forcibly refine them would be thoroughly lost."

"Hehehe, you are indeed a refinement path grandmaster, being able to analyze so thoroughly with just a glance." Fang Yuan laughed in his mind, not stinting on his praise towards Mo Yao.

To speak bluntly, this method was fighting with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to refine the Gu worms.

If Giant Sun's will was awake, the Gu worms would be refined instantly, not leaving behind any opportunity.

But it was hibernating now, the refinement had become slow and as such, there was a loophole that could be used.

Fang Yuan was from the future, thus he knew this clearly.

In his previous life, after central continent's Gu Immortals had broken through Imperial Court blessed land, they had shown this method in the image clips they had disseminated everywhere.

But this method could only be used as support.

What central continent's Gu Immortals truly relied on was still the glass owner token.

This secondary owner token could be considered a divine treasure! Who knew how much energy and resources central continent's forces had to spend for it, and now it was in Fang Yuan's possession, raised to six edges.

Taking advantage of everyone concentrating on the second round, Fang Yuan secretly took out the six-edge owner token.

He stroked the six edges of the owner token and sighed, muttering inwardly: "Such a long time of planning and now it is finally time for the plan to begin in full. Flying bear strength Gu with my flying bear phantom Gu, isn't that what it should be? Hehe, I also think so."

With that and a thought in his mind, he instantly grasped control over this floor!

Chapter 595: Green vines blocking the round, Fang Yuan’s backstab

Hei Lou Lan gazed ahead at the troops making slow progress in the dense jungle.

The intense battle had already lasted for over six hours.

This was the second round; the weather here was hot and damp, and the terrain was a vast ancient rainforest.

To cross this round, Gu Masters needed to traverse through the whole jungle and reach a stone palace at the other side.

However, this jungle could not be taken lightly.

There might not be any beasts in the jungle but it was full of green vines.

These green vines were coiled around tall trees and piled up on the damp ground. Every green vine had the thickness of a king-sized bowl and length of seventy to eighty feet in the minimum.

The common green vines among these were called green snake vines which had snake scales growing all over their surface. And when Gu Masters neared them, the vines would suddenly move and coil around the Gu Masters, constricting them to death.

In every one hundred paces of the rainforest, there were about a thousand green snake vines, filling the whole area.

The difficulty in progressing forward was thus extremely high.

The whole journey was filled with green snake vines attacking from all sides; some shot down from sky, some creeped through the ground and some ambushed from under the ground, causing the group to struggle and not be able to defend properly.

The group's progress was met with attacks from the green vines at all times, seemingly like they were among an ocean of green vines.

The green vine had powerful attacks and quick speed. Even more dangerous were the wood path Gu worms that lived on their bodies. It was precisely because of these Gu worms that the group had suffered huge casualties.

"Reporting, we have discovered a green snake vine king ahead. Currently, Lord Ye Lui Sang is already in a fight with it." After a while of moving forward, an investigative Gu Master returned from the front group to report to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan nodded, still continuing with his slow movement.

In every group of green snake vines, there was a green snake vine king which had the battle strength of a rank four Gu Master.

However, Ye Lui Sang was a rank five peak stage expert, the current tribe leader of the super force Ye Lui tribe, and the fire path he cultivated subdued wood path Gu worms completely. There was also the fire path support type Immortal Gu on him, taking care of a green snake vine king was a cinch.

Sure enough, after a while, the report of victory came from ahead: "Lord Ye Lui Sang has eliminated the green snake vine king and has now retreated from the front lines. Lord Chang Shan Yin has switched with him and is leading the wolf group to open the path."

"Okay." Hei Lou Lan lightly replied.

Wolves were good at offense and not at defense, and were not a good match for the vines. But Chang Shan Yin had defense specialized wolves like turtleback wolves. He also had vermillion fire wolves upon which lived fire path Gu worms. In this situation, they were a sharp weapon to cut open the path.

'Wolf King is truly powerful, he can even be said to have the number one battle strength. Especially when he also has the flying bear phantom Immortal Gu, a mere minor round cannot obstruct him.' Hei Lou Lan pondered while walking.

'Flying bear phantom Gu and flying bear strength Gu, if the two are paired up, that would be perfect. Hmph, I will first make Chang Shan Yin pour in his utmost effort for me and when the time is ripe, I must make him hand over that flying bear phantom Gu! As long as I become a Gu Immortal, wouldn't a mere Wolf King be mine to toy with?"

'This second round seemingly tests the Gu Master's strength in doing prolonged battles, but more than that, it is actually testing investigative ability. In this jungle, there are not only the green snake vine groups, but also green dragon vine groups. Green dragon vines are dozens of times more terrifying than green snake vines, they are mutated beings among plants! The path we took avoided these green dragon vines as much as possible. There are only one or two territories of green dragon vines in this path, and presumably there will be one or two tough battles, and that will be the greatest difficulty of this round."

Hei Lou Lan felt proud: 'We are getting closer to the finish line, at this speed, we will cross this round in an hour!"

He had just thought of this when suddenly a change occurred.

Swish swish....

The green snake vines around the group suddenly penetrated the air with terrifying speed, even producing sonic booms!

The offense of the vines had suddenly increased by dozens of times.

The previous battles were the ones where the Gu Masters fought with the green snake vines nearby while the vines outside the range stayed still.

But now, the green vines within a hundred li, no, a thousand li, were engaging in the battle, surging out crazily like a tsunami as they pounced towards the Gu Masters.

The Gu Masters were caught unprepared, immediately suffering heavy losses. Countless Gu Masters were killed within a few moments of time.

"How could this happen? The green snake vines are rioting all of a sudden!" The experts shouted in fright.

"Someone, save me quickly!" Surrounding Gu Masters were wantonly constricted and twisted apart by the green vine group.

"I command all troops to attack, hold them off no matter the consumption! If we can't hold them back, it will be our death!!" Hei Lou Lan shouted and rose to the air, attempting to control the situation.

Soon, a hundred or so green dragon vines rose to the sky, charging towards him.

Hei Lou Lan gave a shout of fury and used his dark path abilities, killing twenty to thirty green dragon vines instantly before moving towards the ground.

But the ground was also not safe, countless green snake vines and green dragon vines broke through the soil, trapping the entirety of the troops.

"How can this be? The scouting had been done properly, how could we encounter a green dragon vine group here?" The corners of Hei Lou Lan's eyes were threatening to tear as he could not make sense of this no matter what!

Green vines were strongly territorial. But as long as one does not encroach upon their territory, they would remain still and not take the initiative to attack.

These green vine groups, however, had completely gone crazy, pouncing upon the Gu Masters like they had killed their father.

Green vines possessed strong vitality and even if they were cut into five to six parts, these five to six parts could still attack before dying. Hei Lou Lan even saw many green dragon vines struggling free from their root systems, and flying out to attack.

'This, how is this possible? What the hell is happening?!' Hei Lou Lan could not make sense of it no matter how he thought. By cutting off their own roots, these green dragon vines were looking for their own death.

All living things possessed survival instinct.

How deep a hatred was it for them to erupt in such bitter suicidal attacks?

The large army was broken apart, each fighting for themselves while slowly starting to retreat bit by bit; in a moment, many youths lost their lives.

"Could it be this second round is actually a giant trap?! This is too strange, this is only the second round, how could its difficulty be so high?!" Hei Lou Lan was dumbstruck, a huge doubt rising in his heart.

This was indeed a huge trap.

But the one who laid this trap was not Eighty-Eight True Yang Building but the one in control of this floor - Fang Yuan.

He had been patient, ordering the green vines everywhere in this round to stealthily move here. He then accepted the command to participate in the front line and switched with others from time to time, intentionally lowering the speed of progress to stall for time.

When large numbers of green vines had gathered, Fang Yuan immediately ordered a surprise attack without any hesitation.

The Gu Masters suffered disastrous losses because of the ambush!

Fang Yuan was an enslavement path master; the green vines which had lower intelligence than beasts, coordinated together under his control, and disregarded their own lives to burst out with a hundred times their normal strength!

Especially for the experts like Hei Lou Lan, Ye Lui Sang and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he had paid even more attention and mobilized green dragon vines which were comparable to mutated beasts, to obstruct them.

"Retreat, retreat quickly."

"There are green vines everywhere around us, if we continue on, the casualties will become even more severe!"

"Lord Hei tribe leader, my tribe leader requests to retreat!"

Several large tribes hurriedly sent their representatives.

Anyone could see they had landed into an ambush by the green vine groups. How could the green vines become so sinister? Right now, no one had the time to tackle this issue.

Hei Lou Lan fiercely gnashed his teeth, his face showed a struggling expression several times before he squeezed out a word: "Retreat!"

He also knew the situation was already out of control, the green vines were charging without fearing death and had already led the formation to turn chaotic. And the experts were not able to fight properly for the fear of hurting their own men.

If they suffered such serious casualties in the second round, then how could Hei Lou Lan have the power to seize the Immortal Gu in the last round?

Retreat was naturally a wise move, but it would depend on whether Fang Yuan would allow it.

He was in control of this floor, sealing the exit and entrance was only a small thing.

Soon, everyone made a terrifying discovery - they could not leave!

This discovery was huge blow on the morale.

The whole army seemed to be about to crumble apart.

At the crucial moment, Hei Lou Lan felt the situation going awry and stood up, his voice spreading everywhere: "All of you, persevere. I will use the killer move grey meltdown to forcibly cross this round. If we persevere, we will win, we will survive!!"

The despairing Gu Masters heard these words and felt like they were drowning men who had found a life saving straw.

The morale that had fallen to the bottom did not crumble in the end and instead stabilized.

Everyone again started fighting, opening a path and forming a tight and connected formation.

Under the heavy protection from all the troops, Hei Lou Lan led a group of refinement path Gu Masters to form a round formation and began to use the killer move grey meltdown.

"Lord, if we forcibly activate it, we will probably lose thirty percent of our men." An old refinement path Gu Master who was familiar with the inside information advised Hei Lou Lan with a pale face.

The killer move grey meltdown naturally had its limitations.

This killer move relied on the coordination of the inside and outside; this required the reward of the round to be Gu worms deliberately provided by either Hei tribe's Gu Immortals or Xue Song Zi.

But Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would not coordinate, it only chose the suitable Gu worms from those absorbed and refined them to form the rounds.

The first round's reward were Gu worms that came from Hei Bai. Thus, Hei Lou Lan could use the killer move grey meltdown to exploit Giant Sun's will still not having fully refined the Gu worms, to forcibly refine them. Like this, he would get the reward and pass the round.

But the second round's Gu worm reward was wild Gu. Hei Lou Lan was unable to connect with these wild Gu and the killer move grey meltdown could not be used.

The second round could only in accordance with this be completed by going through its requirement.

But the current situation was critical, Hei Lou Lan was left without a better option but to forcibly activate killer move grey meltdown to skip through the second round and connect to the Gu worm reward of the third round.

The third round's Gu worm reward came from Xue Song Zi. The Gu worm was only half-refined, thus still contained most of Xue Song Zi's will.

As Hei Lou Lan was working together with Xue Song Zi, Xue Song Zi's will approved him. He could thus use grey meltdown to connect to the third round's reward and refine it.

As such, the third round would be passed. And when the third round is crossed, the second round would have no foundation, collapsing apart. Because when Eighty-Eight True Yang Building condensed each floor, it would first form the hundredth round, then ninety-ninth round, ninety-eighth round....

However, if Hei Lou Lan did so, the killer move grey meltdown's power would increase by several times, far surpassing the amount these refinement path Gu Masters could bear.

Whether it was success or failure, a portion of the refinement path Gu Masters would not be able to bear it and die.

"Tens of refinement path Gu Masters dying is better than the whole army dying!" Hei Lou Lan gritted his teeth, his eyes filled with chilly and cruel light. The situation had forced him to choose the lesser of the two evils.

The old Gu Master did not say any more and retreated back to the formation.

Chapter 596: Preparations from long ago, Mo Yao’s shock and suspicion

The refinement path Gu Masters had solemn expressions while quickly moving into formation. Grey rays of light gradually blossomed and merged into one.

Under everyone's expectant gaze, Hei Lou Lan waved his hand and threw the two-edge owner token into the air.

The owner token floated in midair, and the giant grey radiance which had been condensed in the round formation shot towards the owner token.

The grey radiance was so dazzling that one could not look at it directly.

"Haha, this is the moment." Fang Yuan had been observing this from the outside, and sent a thought at this time.

The two-edge owner token immediately disappeared, landing in his hand the next moment.

He was in control of this floor, teleporting a small owner token was as simple as breathing.

Without the owner token, the grey radiance immediately collapsed and the killer move grey meltdown forcibly ended; the refinement path Gu Masters in the round formation gave a frightened howl, puffing out blood, with almost all of them dying from the backlash in that instant.

Spurt.

Hei Lou Lan, who was in the center of the formation was no exception to this, spurting out a mouthful of blood and retreating back several large steps like he had received a heavy impact.

"My owner token!" He lost his self control and howled with an extremely shocked, angered and doubtful expression.

Everyone was also stupefied by this change.

Sun Shi Han was baffled, Tang Miao Ming covered her mouth and Pei Yan Fei was also despondent.

Even Mo Yao's will was raving in Fang Yuan's mind: "Brat, what did you do? His owner token has no more than two edges now. Adding in your six edges, it is only eight edges! What are you in such a hurry for? Wouldn't it be good if you had waited for his owner token to rise to four edges?!"

"You don't know shit." Fang Yuan sneered and under the cover of his large sleeve, calmly put away the two-edge owner token.

The whole process happened under the bystanders' gazes, but it was completed in total secret without incurring any suspicion.

"This, what the hell happened!" Ye Lui Sang rushed towards Hei Lou Lan with a fretful expression and asked, "Where is the owner token?"

"I... how would I know!!" Hei Lou Lan's eyes seemed to shoot out flames of anger, his voice raised an octave higher as he burst out with foul language, "What the f*ck happened?!"

In the past records of history, there had never been a situation where the owner token suddenly disappeared!

Grey meltdown had been used so many times by all the large forces and the winners in the past, how could it suddenly fade away in Hei Lou Lan's hand?

"Damn it, how do we go on without the owner token?" Fang Yuan also hurried over at this moment, his brows were furrowed into a knot and he had a genuine and heavily anxious expression, making others sympathize with him.

The killer move which everyone had placed high hopes on failed at the crucial moment. The two-edge owner token was also inexplicably lost.

The green vines' offensive was becoming more fierce like a flash flood, not giving anyone the time for a breather.

Morale had fallen to the abyss and many started fleeing in disorder.

"It's over, we are done for." Xi Xue mumbled.

"Will I die in this place? Is this the final ending?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed bitterly. In this recent period, he was being tormented by his conscience and his body looked extremely weak and thin.

However, the next moment, someone shouted in joy: "We can leave, someone left! We can leave!!"

Fang Yuan did not want to get rid of all these people in one go and left a lifeline, allowing the Gu Masters to freely enter and exit this floor.

If Hei tribe was completely annihilated, he would definitely attract the all-out revenge of Hei tribe's Gu Immortals.

Moreover, Fang Yuan still required Tai Bai Yun Sheng to refine landscape as before Gu.

Therefore the collapsed and despairing army started retreating.

"I am actually alive!"

"This time was too terrifying, I don't want to enter there again."

"Boo hoo hoo....father, you died so miserably."

The plaza around the True Yang Building became a scene of gloomy misery.

Hei Lou Lan had convened a large army and entered the tower with grand and vigorous momentum, but such a change while leaving the tower was beyond the expectations of almost everyone.

Hei Lou Lan's expression was ashen as he glanced at the plaza before leaving without any words.

Hei tribesmen followed behind him, silent and heads lowered.

Ye Lui Sang heaved a long sigh and shook his head, leaving the plaza.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a complex expression as he looked at Hei Lou Lan's receding figure: "After this expedition, it will probably be difficult to form a presentable party within a short period of time."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was wrong.

The very next day, Hei Lou Lan again formed a large army and attacked the second round.

So what if he lost the owner token?

Even if he could not use grey meltdown, he could use brute force to pass the round!

Hei Lou Lan had deceived two great Gu Immortals in his pledge to take revenge; he could no longer turn back.

He must force himself to continue on!

However, during the night of the defeat, Fang Yuan had quietly entered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"You are too impatient, you now only have eight edges. What can you do now!" Mo Yao sneered in his mind.

Fang Yuan walked slowly along the secret treasury corridor while gently touching the crystal wall, looking on as treasure after treasure swept past his gaze.

He had a slight smile on his face, replying calmly to Mo Yao's will: "You are an impressive refinement path grandmaster, a fairy of Spirit Affinity House, just speak clearly if you want to ask, why probe so superficially?"

Mo Yao heard this and immediately changed her expression, smiling coquettishly: "Young man, looks like you already have a plan..."

"That goes without saying." Fang Yuan's steps paused and he lightly stroked the right crystal wall, taking out a treasure stored within.

Ever since he had refined the guest halt stele, he could take out any treasures around this distance.

Fang Yuan walked a few steps further and took out three Gu worms on top of that.

He then moved to the left crystal wall and took out the objects within.

As this went on, Fang Yuan had taken out tens of Gu recipes, over a hundred Gu worms, all kinds of information on inheritances and over twenty documents on cultivation insights.

Fang Yuan kept around eighty of the Gu worms outside while sending the rest into storage Gu worms.

Mo Yao had observed the whole process quietly, getting more curious as time went on. These Gu worms that Fang Yuan left out here did not match together, she really could not tell what he was doing.

The video of central continent's Gu Immortals attacking Imperial Court blessed land in his previous life appeared in Fang Yuan's mind.

There were altogether eleven Gu Immortals who attacked Imperial Court blessed land, men and women, each with extraordinary presence.

A female immortal was the leader, a domineering aura lingered around her which pressured people; other Gu Immortals were cautious and respectful towards her.

She was known as Fairy Black Moon. A half-mask covered her nose, mouth and cheeks, only revealing the upper half of her face which showed her strong contours, sharp and long brows, bright eyes and a heroic aura. A dark gold armor covered her whole body, bringing a heavy feeling of suppression on any that looked at it.

Fang Yuan's current actions were replicating Fairy Black Moon's actions to the smallest details.

The treasures he took out were actually of great background. Countless years back, central continent's Gu Immortals sent outstanding Gu Masters to infiltrate into northern plains; the Gu Masters would pass some rounds with high grade evaluation, entering the treasure room and arranging these treasures here.

The whole process consumed close to a millenium.

Fang Yuan walked past the guest halt stele, and walked over three hundred steps into the long crystal corridor before stopping.

"It is here." He looked around him and after confirming it, began to put the Gu worms he had taken earlier into the crystal wall. Whether it was left or right, top or under his feet, they were placed in a certain pattern.

As for the original treasures within the crystal wall, Fang Yuan took some, left some and shifted the position of some.

"This, could it be...." Mo Yao was bewildered; she had been watching carefully and had gradually inferred some clues with her refinement path grandmaster attainment.

In the range of tens of steps, after Fang Yuan's adjustments, the Gu worms in the crystal wall had ingeniously formed a formation.

"Right, this is precisely the refinement path killer move grey meltdown. No, to be even more exact, this killer move originates from grey meltdown but its effects are much stronger!" Fang Yuan chuckled.

"What in the world are you trying to do?" Mo Yao asked.

Fang Yuan's gazed eerily, a confident smile appearing on his face: "Just watch."

He then sent out several Gu worms which floated in the air.

The Gu worms in the surrounding walls started to shake slightly one by one.

Dust seemed to rise up in the air.

The dust gradually became denser till it formed a thick grey fog.

The grey fog kept on accumulating and soon entirely submerged Fang Yuan; he could not even see his own hands.

Fang Yuan stood within the grey fog with his eyes closed and his right hand clutching the six-edge owner token, as he tried to carefully sense something.

Suddenly, he opened his eyes and shouted: "Come back, Fixed Immortal Travel!"

Rumble!

The crystal corridor shook strongly and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had a sudden tremor.

The twenty-first floor where seventeen rounds still remained, disintegrated into nothingness.

The rewards for the seventeen rounds penetrated through space and appeared before Fang Yuan.

Among them, one Gu worm was dispelling a rank six aura, shining with a green gem-like luster, and flying elegantly like a green jade butterfly.

Its powerful presence pushed the rest of the Gu worms to the side.

What else could it be but Fixed Immortal Travel?

"Immortal Gu! This is Fixed Immortal Travel?!" Mo Yao blurted out.

Fang Yuan stored the other rewards into storage Gu worms while the Immortal Gu Fixed Immortal Travel was left outside, sitting on his shoulder.

Immortal Gu Fixed Immortal Travel was a rank six Gu and at its peak state, his mortal aperture could not store it.

Fang Yuan had not stored flying bear phantom Gu either, instead directly holding it in his pocket.

"There is one more." Fang Yuan licked his lips in excitement.

Another explosive sound rang out.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building shook greatly, the twelve remaining rounds of the thirty-fourth floor were immediately passed!

The rewards appeared in front of Fang Yuan out of thin air and one Gu among them, an Immortal Gu that looked like nothing special, just like a lump of earth, it was —

"Immortal Gu Gruel Mud!" Mo Yao's will blurted out the name.

Fang Yuan laughed and stored the other rewards while putting the Gruel Mud into his pouch.

Back then, he had buried Fixed Immortal Travel and Gruel Mud deep under the ground, waiting for this precise moment.

When Eighty-Eight True Yang Building condensed, it plundered the whole of Northern Plains. This was the arrangement of an Immortal Venerable, his might extended up into the heavens and down into the abyss, nothing could stop his overwhelming force.

Immortal Gu Wooden Chicken had escaped the pursuit of Xue Song Zi and Hei Bai, but was still captured by Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in the end.

The wild Immortal Gu ended up like that while Fang Yuan's meticulously buried Immortal Gu did not even have the will to resist, and were naturally collected by Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

After the capture, they were placed separately as the last rewards for the twenty-first and thirty-fourth floor. But due to Giant Sun's will being in hibernation, the two Immortal Gu had all along been in a half-refined state, just as Fang Yuan had planned for.

"Brat, who in the world are you? Hmph, this is not a small arrangement. You were actually able to mobilize two Immortal Gu. Tell me, which region are you from, which force sent you here?" Mo Yao was unable to hold back after she saw this, and began to ask questions after questions.

Chapter 597: True Inheritance Secluded Domain, Unexpected Event

The appearance of two great Immortal Gu was way out of her expectations, Mo Yao was very surprised.

What was even more scary was, Fang Yuan had made ample preparations!

The Gu worms he used were originally treasures kept inside the crystal walls. His killer move was even more perfect than grey meltdown, and had stronger effect.

To get to this point, it was not something a single person could achieve, in fact, this could not be achieved with merely decades of set up. Huge amounts of strength and effort needed to be invested, at least hundreds of years of infiltration in order to hide all the Gu worms inside the crystal walls, and to prevent the Gu worms from being taken away by people, they needed to prepare several of each Gu.

All in all, this was not something a person or an ordinary force could accomplish, it had to be a super force with Gu Immortals at least!

Against Mo Yao's suspicion, Fang Yuan smiled lightly and did not speak.

All these were the set up of central continent's Gu Immortals. But Mo Yao had died long ago, her will was slumbering within Water Pavilion and was unaware of the changes in the outside world.

Fang Yuan was someone who had been reborn, he had a huge advantage, using the Gu Immortals' set up, he could accomplish all of this successfully!

To speak the truth, he should thank those central continent Gu Immortals who went around to distribute the footage.

Without the guidance of this clip, Fang Yuan would not be so sure of the inside information of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

His method was inherently the same as Hei Lou Lan's, but Fang Yuan was sensing his own Immortal Gu, while Hei Lou Lan was sensing other people's mortal Gu.

Refining an Immortal Gu was at least a hundred times as difficult as refining a mortal Gu, thus, Fang Yuan was not in such a rush for time unlike Hei Lou Lan. The two Immortal Gu were constantly in a state of half-refinement.

Most importantly, the refinement path killer move that Fang Yuan activated was the revised version of grey meltdown that central continent's Gu Immortals had painstakingly researched in, it had an amazing effect, freeing the Gu Master and saving them the trouble of facing backlash as Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would be the one enduring the pressure.

At the same time, he had to thank all of the Gu Masters who charged through the rounds enthusiastically. If the rounds were intact, Fang Yuan would need to traverse a hundred rounds to communicate with the Immortal Gu, it would be filled with difficulty.

But there were only seventeen rounds left on the twenty-first floor, and the thirty-fourth floor had even fewer rounds, at twelve.

After Fang Yuan successfully took the two Immortal Gu, these two floors were passed automatically.

He took out the two owner tokens, the glass owner token was still at six-edges, after all it was a cheat item and was not authentic.

Meanwhile, the owner token snatched from Hei Lou Lan had turned from two-edges to four-edges.

Combining the two, they were — ten-edges!

Ten-edges, that meant that Fang Yuan had met the minimum requirements to receive an Immortal Venerable Inheritance.

"Immortal Venerable Inheritance..." Fang Yuan chuckled, according to what was shown in the footage, he combined the two owner tokens and created the ten-edge owner token.

Swoosh.

The next moment, he vanished on the spot.

The scenery before him changed drastically, when Fang Yuan finally reacted, he found himself in an area of void.

The surroundings were pure darkness, there was neither heaven or earth, Fang Yuan was floating silently in the air.

Several traces of green or red starlight shone from far away.

"This is Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's true inheritance secluded domain, to think that after so many years, I can come here again!" Mo Yao's will was surprisingly dejected and downcast, as she muttered to herself.

"Eh? You've been here before?" Fang Yuan's heart jumped.

"Back then... hmph, I'm not going to talk about it. It is your greatest fortune to be able to come here! Although with ten-edges, you can only receive the lowest grade ordinary true inheritance. But this will not hinder you from gaining some knowledge and experience. What you are going to see will surely broaden your vision, you will never forget it!" In just a moment, Mo Yao's will went back to normal.

Fang Yuan laughed, Mo Yao's arrogant tone did not make him angry, in fact he nodded in agreement: "Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, I cannot compare to him yet! Today, this will indeed hugely broaden my vision."

Saying this, he waved his hands like he was swimming in water, moving his body forward slowly.

In the video from central continent in his previous life, there were many details omitted during this period.

Central continent's Gu Immortals invested more heavily than Fang Yuan, they used more than ten Immortal Gu to raise the owner token to forty-three edges.

They gained a lot, but all of the gains were concealed, such an act was no doubt a defensive measure to prevent attracting the greed of the viewers. This, however, increased Fang Yuan's interest and anticipation towards Giant Sun's true inheritances.

He followed after a blood red starlight, getting closer to it.

As he got closer, the starlight became brighter, and eventually, Fang Yuan stopped before a round circular light.

This lump of red starlight was the size of a bowl, silently floating around.

"This is an ordinary true inheritance, if you want to understand the contents, you just need to let your consciousness enter it." Mo Yao advised at the appropriate timing.

Fang Yuan was carefully navigating with his mind, as images flashed before him.

A grand and huge ancient forest!

Ancient and tall trees, beasts at the size of mountains!

"Hahaha!" A person with a broad shoulder and thin waist was laughing with his head facing up.

His image was blurred, but his skin was covered in rainbow colors, as ancient totems of every description were carved on it, his dominating presence pervaded heaven and earth!

He stepped on the grey clouds and treaded strong winds, his purple hair was fluttering as there were seemingly flames burning within his double pupil eyes.

Fang Yuan saw this and his heart was pounding, he could feel difficulty breathing. He recognised this person immediately: "This is one of the three Demon Venerables of the olden antiquity era, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable! He is facing the immemorial desolate beast — Primordial Ash Owl! Strange, why is there a Demon Venerable's item within Giant Sun's inheritances?"

"What's so strange about this? Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was the venerable of an era, the supreme ruler of heaven and earth, the invincible being in the universe. He searched the entire world and obtained an item of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, placing it inside his building for his descendants, this is very normal." Mo Yao said.

Immemorial desolate beast, overlords that had existed within heaven and earth since the immemorial era, they had rank eight Gu Immortal battle strength.

This primordial ash owl had a bird head and beast body, it had two pairs of golden pupils and a dragon's horn on its head. Its muscular body was covered in thick rainbow feathers, its bestial aura could overwhelm the world.

Its limbs moved quickly, and could easily destroy mountains and rivers. With one growl, its voice could travel ten thousand li, causing ripples in the air of the entire world.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable praised: "Good beast!"

The primordial ash owl had intelligence that could rival men, it got angry upon hearing that, shooting out thunder like that of the heavens from its mouth, the blue thunderbolt shot out and pierced ten thousand li into the sky, instantly arriving before Reckless Savage Demon Venerable.

Fang Yuan's expression changed, the magnitude of the lightning and thunder was beyond his imagination! Right now he was like an ant, but even if it was his Gu Immortal self from his past life, he could not survive for three breaths' time from this!

But Reckless Savage Demon Venerable did not move at all, he allowed the frenzied thunderbolt to hit his body directly.

From within the electricity, his bronze colored body was intact, shining brightly. His muscles were like stone blocks, and all the totems on his body were like living beings, as all sorts of fierce beasts were roaming on his body.

From within the exploding lightning plasma, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's face showed an expression of enjoyment. He laughed heartily as he punched with his right fist.

Bam — !

Immediately, heaven and earth changed colors, as winds and clouds moved violently.

The lightning vanished slowly, mountains were trembling, and forests were weeping.

With just one punch, the intense winds blew like an apocalypse, the clouds in the sky vanished, the heavens were stripped bare, and permeating sunlight dispelled all darkness!

Just one punch.

With the intensity of the force that repelled ghosts and deities, the primordial ash owl was crying out pitifully!

It was an immemorial desolate beast, an overlord of a region, it was untamable and wild earlier, giving off a strong aura, but the next moment, its bones were crushed to bits as its rainbow feathers floated in the air, its golden pupils were full of fear and it laid on the ground, like a dead dog.

Fang Yuan was completely moved, this was the first time he had seen the attack of a venerable.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, with the prowess of rank nine, he was truly invincible in all heaven and earth!

"Nine thousand nine hundred and ninety-ninth ash owl." Reckless Savage Demon Venerable said plainly, opening his palm and grabbing the air.

The next moment, the primordial ash owl was held by a formless strength. It was like a chicken that was grabbed by a butcher, it was helpless and was shrieking for help.

"Transform." Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's body shuddered, he expanded along with the wind, becoming a giant in an instant!

What a true giant.

He was as tall as heaven and earth, as if he could grab the sun if he wished. No tribulations could move him, as he could barely be held by the universe itself!

The giant slowly opened his mouth, as the primordial ash owl struggled intensely, and yet to no avail as it was sent into the giant's mouth.

The giant swallowed in one mouthful, chewing several times with a sound as if a mountain collapsed, lightning striking everywhere, it was loud as thunder.

With a gulp, the giant sent the primordial ash owl into its stomach.

He actually ate an immemorial desolate beast, a rank eight level existence, just like that.

The prowess of Reckless Savage, it was truly terrifying!

After eating this rank eight desolate beast, the giant patted his stomach, the sound was loud as thunder but his expression was like he did not have enough.

And on his belly, there was a new totem, in the form of the primordial ash owl, but among the innumerable totems on his body, it was not eye catching.

The giant seemed to have sensed something as he suddenly turned around and looked straight at Fang Yuan!

Urgh!

Fang Yuan fell on the ground like he had suffered a huge blow, vomiting out a mouthful of blood in the process.　　

His soul was trembling intensely, a strong sense of dizziness assaulted him, only recovering after a long time.

Gasp, gasp, gasp...

He breathed roughly, barely opening his eyes.

His eyes could not take it either, as two streams of bloody tears flowed out, flowing from his face towards the ground.

But thankfully, this place did not restrict Gu worms, such an injury could be easily healed with Gu worms.

"This is the test of the inheritance?" Fang Yuan healed himself as he asked.

"Hehehe, what sort of test is this?" In his mind, Mo Yao was gloating, replying in an arrogant tone: "This inheritance has a trace of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's will within it, only Gu Immortals could withstand it. But after getting this inheritance, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already modified it such that mortals could endure it. You owe it to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's mercy that you are still alive."

Fang Yuan snorted coldly: "His mercy is only towards his bloodline descendants, what does that have to do with me? Anyway, Giant Sun true inheritances are not so easy to obtain, there is great danger inside."

"That is of course the case. But you have already survived this test, and remember that this true inheritance is only an ordinary true inheritance. With the ten-edge owner token, you already have the authority to inherit it." Mo Yao said.

As expected, when Fang Yuan's mind entered, the red light lump opened its 'doors', as Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's figure did not appear again.

"Primordial ash owl transformation..." Fang Yuan realized now that this was a transformation path killer move. This killer move could allow a Gu Immortal to transform into the primordial ash owl, gaining a huge boost in strength.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable was the progenitor of strength path, but he was also the creator of transformation path.

His strength could shake heaven and earth, he was the fiercest venerable out of the ten. At the same time, he could transform into countless fierce beasts, having an endless number of transformations, and he could even revive from a drop of blood.

Fang Yuan did not hesitate, he let go of the red light lump and allowed it to fly away from him.

Although the true inheritance was precious, it did not suit him currently.

Fang Yuan was very calm, and held even more expectations.

To think that within Giant Sun's true inheritances, there would be something involving Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, and this particular inheritance was only the lowest grade ordinary true inheritance.

He could not imagine what other ordinary true inheritances there could be. As for the even greater unparalleled true inheritance, what would they be?

He moved his arms, and swam towards another area within this silent and dark void.

Chapter 598: Three Olds, Three True Inheritances, Using Will

Fang Yuan worked hard to swim towards a jade light.

This lump of jade light was harder to get closer to compared to the red light from before.

It was flying slowly, continuously twisting and turning, as Fang Yuan chased after it for a while before managing to grab it.

It was also as large as a bowl, and Fang Yuan's consciousness carefully entered it.

An unspeakable force of vibration spread from the jade green light into Fang Yuan's body.

"Be careful, this is Old Immortal Kong Jue's item!" In his mind, Mo Yao's will recognised this item and warned.

"Don't worry, it cannot escape!" Fang Yuan's tone was certain, he grabbed onto this light lump tightly.

"Idiot, I am not referring to that. Quickly let go." Mo Yao said this, but it was already too late.

The mystical vibration spread from within the jade light, all the way into Fang Yuan's aperture.

Fang Yuan's aperture started vibrating.

In his ninety percent filled aperture sea, waves were crashing violently.

Swish swish swish...

The huge waves crashed on the surrounding aperture walls, the rank five peak stage crystal clear walls were starting to develop cracks from the pressure of the waves.

Fang Yuan was shocked!

This true inheritance's test was very peculiar, it was hard to defend against, it actually directly affected the Gu Master's aperture.

"Lad, quickly cut off your arms using Gu worms. Only by making a sacrifice can you save your life!" Mo Yao's will shouted in Fang Yuan's mind.

"Cut off my arms?" Fang Yuan's expression sank, sweat was forming on his forehead.

He tried letting go of it but this lump of jade light gave off an extremely strong suction force, keeping Fang Yuan's hands tightly attached to it.

Fang Yuan could not get free from it, and the vibrations in his aperture were getting stronger.

"I got it!" In the moment of crisis, Fang Yuan had an inspiration as he quickly moved the primeval essence in his second aperture into his first aperture.

The vibration moved into the second aperture through the primeval essence.

The second aperture also started vibrating uncontrollably, but this way, the two apertures were enduring this together, and the first aperture's crisis was soothed to a great extent.

Mo Yao gasped.

As the jade light became dim and the vibrations vanished, it seemed that Fang Yuan had passed the test.

"What is going on, you have two apertures?" Mo Yao said.

With two apertures enduring the test together, although the aperture walls were cracked, they did not break.

"Lad, you hid this very deeply, you actually have two apertures! Second aperture... to think that the rumors that had been going around have been confirmed by you." Mo Yao said with deep emotions.

Fang Yuan was not willing to talk about this, he asked instead: "You mentioned Old Immortal Kong Jue earlier, is it that refinement path supreme grandmaster from the olden antiquity era?"

"That's right, it's him. Refinement path supreme grandmaster... even throughout human history, since ancient times, there had only been three. Future generations called them the 'Three Olds'. They were the remote antiquity era's Old Eccentric Tian Nan, olden antiquity era's Old Immortal Kong Jue, and medieval antiquity era's refinement path supreme grandmaster Long Hair Ancestor."

Mo Yao continued recounting: "Among them, Old Eccentric Tian Nan had a weird personality, he tried to refine the sky and ended up losing his life. Old Immortal Kong Jue had the deepest research in apertures, he created the \<\<Immortal Aperture Strategy\>\>, and helped the ten extreme physiques to become immortals. Before him, there had never been any cases where a person of the ten extreme physiques rose to become an immortal. As for Long Hair Ancestor, he had the longest lifespan and refined the most Immortal Gu. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was refined by him. In fact, there were rumors that he could refine lifespan Gu, causing Old Ancestor Giant Sun to attack Lang Ya blessed land, although there were no results from that."

Mo Yao talked about many famous pieces of information.

Three old beings, three supreme refinement grandmasters, each of them was a legend.

They were the three peaks of refinement path in human history, even rank nine venerables could not mask their glory and reputation.

"Old Immortal Kong Jue's inheritance tests the fated person's aperture. You actually had two apertures, you managed to get through luckily. Look, this inheritance is very good, it will be a huge help to you." Mo Yao continued.

Fang Yuan's consciousness went in again.

This inheritance was known as the 'immortal ascension vital information', it recorded Old Immortal Kong Jue's understanding of the immortal ascension process of all the different paths of Gu Masters, all the difficulties they might face and how to deal with those difficulties, it listed the most crucial points for rising to immortal.

Fang Yuan assessed in his heart: "Although this is not a Gu recipe or an Immortal Gu, it has a huge value in terms of theoretical guidance. If Gu Masters get it, it will not only help themselves but even allow them to understand other paths, it is truly an important treasure."

"This immortal ascension vital information dates back to long ago, it might not be useful for the currently trending paths. After all, these years of development have caused the rise of many new paths, it is no longer as dull and simple as back in the olden antiquity era. What I want to remind you is, the essence of this inheritance is not the immortal ascension vital information itself, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's notes when he read through it. His assessment is like the summary of the most important points, it gets right to the point and is truly worth more than a thousand gold." Mo Yao gave another shocking revelation.

Old Immortal Kong Jue was a refinement path supreme grandmaster on par with Long Hair Ancestor.

His research, along with the Immortal Venerable's notes, truly has immense value.

When a Gu Master reads it, it will greatly increase the chances of them successfully rising to immortal. In addition, using the perspective of an Immortal Venerable, they can develop in the right direction, their Gu Immortal journey would be guided and they could avoid many pitfalls along the way.

This inheritance had really shocking attraction. Especially for geniuses like Fang Yuan who desired to take one more step and was not satisfied with being a mortal.

But Fang Yuan did not choose it.

He had his previous life's experiences, he could repeat his run on the blood path.

He had other motives for coming into the true inheritance space.

Thus, Fang Yuan let go and allowed the jade lump to fly away from him, at a speed faster than the red light as it went into an unknown zone.

"You are really giving it up? When you think about this in the future, don't regret it." In his mind, Mo Yao sighed.

"Regret? Hehe, there is no such word in my life." Fang Yuan laughed lightly, continuing his search.

He swam in the darkness for a while, discovering the third light lump.

This light lump was shining with a grey light, its speed was even faster than the first two light lumps, it was like a shooting star. As it flew in the space, there was a frost colored tail trailing behind it.

Fang Yuan tried to get close to it, but Mo Yao said: "Actually, you don't have to take such a risk every time, since you have already collected many wisdom path Gu worms, why don't you display their true value?"

"Oh? What do you mean?" Fang Yuan's speed did not get any slower.

"Lad, thank me well, the move I'm going to teach you will allow you to avoid the test of the true inheritance and search for the content of the true inheritance directly."

Mo Yao's method was not very complex.

After Fang Yuan found the true inheritance light lump, the first step was for his consciousness to enter the lump, and that would trigger the test of the inheritance.

Mo Yao's advice was, to use wisdom path Gu worms to create wills. By injecting this will into the true inheritance, he would wait for a while before recalling it.

This way, he would be able to avoid intimate contact with the true inheritance, it was a opportunist method.

"Wisdom path has thought, will, and emotion. The so called mind is made up of heart sense and divine sense. When your mind enters, your thoughts are exploring and interacting. Thoughts are like water droplets, they are the easiest to create, and also the most fragile. Because the numbers are huge, the droplets will merged into a river and enter to do the investigation. During this process, the Gu Master's mind has to continue creating them without any pauses. As for will, they are superior to thoughts, like an ice cube. They have greater defense but are harder to create. They can however, move independently, and recalled when needed." Mo Yao explained.

Fang Yuan was silent.

"Lad, at this point in time, why are you hesitating? Hehehe, I know you have been collecting information on wisdom path, and also purchasing those wisdom path Gu worms. Your special will Gu, deliberate will Gu, play will Gu, keep will Gu, and new will Gu are all useless now, when will you use them?" Mo Yao laughed alluringly.

Pausing for a while, she continued urging: "Right now, you must already be clear: My will is residing in your mind, it is already deeply connected to you. When you use these Gu to create wills, they would be pure and flawless, I cannot infiltrate them. Haven't you been wary of me? This method has a huge advantage, you can use it to avoid those true inheritance tests and check the secrets of the unparalleled inheritances. Unparalleled inheritance, they have much greater value than ordinary inheritances."

"What are you..." Fang Yuan's gaze was hesitant.

All along, he had never been so outspoken about his situation with Mo Yao. To think that Mo Yao would talk about it openly like this now.

What was her true intention? Was it really like what she said, she only wanted to return the rank seven Immortal Gu house Water Pavilion back to Spirit Affinity House?

Mo Yao's honest expression created ripples in Fang Yuan's heart.

Maybe he was too vigilant, and was too wary of Mo Yao? But wills were not like thoughts, thoughts were simple and were not good at deception. A land spirit formed from obsessions only spoke the truth.

But wills were different. They were the product of many thoughts fusing together, they were much more complex than thoughts. Thus, they could lie to others.

Fang Yuan shook his head, sending these chaotic pieces of information out of his mind, now was not the time to think about this.

Honestly speaking, Mo Yao's words were truly useful in Fang Yuan's viewpoint, he was successfully convinced to attempt it.

Fang Yuan took out the wisdom path Gu worms that he had bought.

He had the land spirit little Hu Immortal and could connect to treasure yellow heaven at any time. Standing on the foundation of a Gu Immortal, it was extremely easy for him to purchase mortal Gu.

Right now, the eight wisdom path Gu worms in his hands could produce wills, but they were all different.

Special will Gu could produce special wills, it could only be activated under special circumstances.

Deliberate will Gu could create deliberate wills, when such a will is produced, it would be like carvings on a steel board, extremely difficult to get rid of compared to other wills.

Play will Gu, creates playful wills. It is the will that is most capable of creating 'emotions'.

There are also keep will Gu, new will Gu, battle intent Gu and others...

What was worth mentioning was that these wisdom path Gu worms could produce different types of wills that were effective against other wills.

For example, special will Gu can produce special wills, but can also devour special wills. Deliberate will Gu can create deliberate wills, they were hard to get rid of but if one uses the right methods and finds the deliberate will Gu, it can be easily removed.

Why did Fang Yuan buy these Gu worms?

It was because of this.

He wanted to deal with Mo Yao's mysterious will. But he had already bought so many of these Gu, and discovered that none could deal with Mo Yao's will.

With the current situation, choosing which will Gu to use was not important.

He casually chose the special will Gu, injecting primeval essence as a will was formed.

The appearance of the will was similar to Fang Yuan, he looked like a youth with dark eerie eyes, but different from the main body, his face was more manly and had a more decisive expression.

"Wills can only reside within the soul, if you want to send this will out, you will need a small soul worm." Mo Yao reminded.

Small soul Gu was a rank one Gu in soul path, it was very common but was the foundation of soul path. Many higher rank soul path Gu worms were refined step by step with it as the foundation.

Mo Yao's reminder was redundant.

Before she finished speaking, Fang Yuan summoned a Gu worm.

It had no solid body, it was palm sized and looked like a butterfly, flickering like light and shadow. If someone grabbed it, they would not be able to catch its hollow body.

It was the rank two big soul worm.

Fang Yuan patted it lightly, sending his special will into the big soul worm's body. Next, he used the big soul worm and made it fly to the closest lump of green white true inheritance light lump.

The big soul worm's speed was much faster than him moving alone.

In just a short moment, it entered the true inheritance light lump and a while later, the big soul worm with a tattered body flew back while wavering.

Fang Yuan retrieved his will and looked.

This third true inheritance was also an ordinary true inheritance, but to some Gu Masters, or even Gu Immortals, it had much greater value than the first two true inheritances!

Chapter 599: Longevity, Hard, Hard, Hard

The third true inheritance had huge value, because it talked about the method of extending lifespan.

The saying goes: Better to live a bad life than have a good death.

Unless there were special reasons, there was nobody who wanted to stop living or not live longer.

Gu Masters, although they could cultivate, and reaching rank six would improve the essence of their life, they could not gain lifespan directly.

Ever since the way of Gu had developed, countless talents had tried all sorts of methods to create a method to extend their own lifespan.

Like First Gen Gu Yue on Qing Mao mountain who chose to become a zombie. Or the demonic path Gu Master in southern border Century Boy, using the return to childhood Gu on himself to maintain a child's appearance and reduce the speed of the loss of his lifeforce.

These were only mortal methods, Gu Immortals had even more mystical methods.

This third inheritance was a lifespan increasing method targeted at Gu Immortals. The person who created it was none other than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

A lifespan increasing method created by an Immortal Venerable! One could imagine the value of this true inheritance!

According to the content, on a certain year, month, and day, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had an inspiration, and it created a brilliant idea.

He named this immortal art — Possession.

The core was a rank six possession Immortal Gu! Other than that, there were about three thousand rank five mortal Gu of all kinds.

"To think that possession Immortal Gu's origin is actually here." Fang Yuan looked at this with a palpitating heart, in his previous life, during the chaotic battle of the five regions, possession Immortal Gu had been extremely well-known, many high ranking Gu Immortals managed to extend their lifespan and that changed the situation of the five regions battle.

Although possession Immortal Gu was rank six, it was a crucial Gu worm that could change the very structure of the world!

In an instant, Fang Yuan had a sudden urge — this is the origin of the possession Immortal Gu, as long as he took it and grasped the origin, in the future during the five region battle, he would be able to sell this possession Immortal Gu and gain a terrifying profit!

Especially with his previous life's memories, he knew who had the greatest need for this possession Immortal Gu, as long as he planned properly, the benefits were unthinkable!

But soon, Fang Yuan calmed down.

The special will on the big soul worm sent even more information.

This true inheritance was only an empty shell, the possession Immortal Gu inside along with the three thousand mortal Gu had all been taken away by someone already.

Inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there were eighty-eight true inheritances that were set up by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

But after so many years, a portion of them had already been taken by people. Mo Yao had once said, during her time, when she explored Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, out of the eighty-eight true inheritances, only fifty-three were left.

Mo Yao was an expert from ten thousand years ago, as Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's rounds were hard to pass, for every ten years of the Imperial Court contest, there were very few occasions in which a winner reached ten-edges. But even so, after so many years, there were some capable individuals who managed to enter the true inheritance secluded domain.

The number of true inheritances left now was definitely smaller than fifty-three.

"Eh? This is..." While communicating with the special will on the big soul worm, Fang Yuan's pupils expanded suddenly.

Although the true inheritance was taken away, Fang Yuan's special will still made some shocking discoveries.

"Using the soul to take over a body, it is nothing but a struggle at death's door, death is still unavoidable. To extend one's life, lifespan Gu is the best option. The road of a Gu Immortal is filled with calamities and tribulations, it is hard for the body to resist them, and it is hard for the soul to exist independently, the maintenance of longevity means the defiance of heaven... it is hard, hard, hard!"

Inside the true inheritance, there was such a paragraph.

These words directly criticized Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's method of possession, the tone was simply too arrogant! After looking at multitudes of lifespan extending methods, lifespan Gu still remained as the best choice. The final three 'hard' words, were truly filled with emotions.

Finally, the person who wrote this also left his name — Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

Seeing this name, one would feel that it was only natural for the criticism to exist.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had the same status, they were both rank nine Gu Masters. But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was an Immortal Venerable during the medieval antiquity era, while Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was a Demon Venerable who appeared after Giant Sun.

Two hundred thousand years after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's demise, the demonic path venerable Spectral Soul who had the greatest nature for murder was born. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had such a huge reputation, when Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was invincible in the world, he naturally found his way into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it was nothing strange.

"Don't tell me possession Immortal Gu was taken by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable? No, the possibility is very slim. Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was the creator of soul path, he was the greatest expert in terms of souls, not even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could match him in that. From the words that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable left behind, he had no interest in the possession method at all. He wanted to exist alongside heaven and earth, but he as one person was facing increasing difficulties one after another, seeing that a predecessor had also searched for a longevity method, he felt some deep emotions and left behind these words." Fang Yuan analyzed.

Even rank nine venerables invincible in the universe during their time could not resist the flow of time.

Time was the greatest enemies of heroes and beauties.

Lifespan Gu was hard to find, their location was fixed, and they were produced in limited supply, only heaven and earth could create them naturally.

The rank nine venerables searched the lands, using up all of the lifespan Gu, but failed to find new lifespan Gu, thus they can only find new ways to extend their lives.

The number one people in this world, behind their invincible authority, there was the sadness and anxiety towards their limited lifespan.

Thus, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's possession technique made Spectral Soul Demon Venerable lament about the difficulty of longevity.

"Even Immortal Venerables or Demon Venerables, such invincible beings, cannot escape the fate of death. Sigh... the wheel of fortune goes round and round, they may rule for generation after generation, but after their primes they will inevitably break down, and those at rock bottom can have their fortunes reverse. In this world, can there be any eternal existences?" In his mind, Mo Yao had a heavy emotion as she sighed deeply.

But this was not what Fang Yuan thought.

He had an eerie gaze: "The Great Dao of heaven and earth focuses on the balance of all beings, and the restraints they place on each other. But when a Gu Master cultivates, they search all over the world and gather resources, using them to promote the growth of oneself, thus this is really the path that defies the way of heaven. Maybe this is why tribulations and calamities occur. But precisely so, eternal life that surpasses longevity is the goal that is worth my pursuit!"

Thinking so, there was a fire burning in his heart, becoming brighter and hotter!

Immortal Venerables and Demon Venerables could only have a long life, but his goal was the greater level of eternal life! This was a realm that venerables could not reach.

Using a phrase from Fang Yuan's previous world, that would be 'competing against heaven, competing against earth, competing against humans, the joy is endless!'

Water can only produce beautiful waves when they hit on rocks, people can only feel the joy in life when they engage in competition.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, he was only rank six, close to seven.

Towards the rank nine existences, he had never looked up to them, he only felt a strong aspiration in his heart.

Here, he saw another side of the venerables: fatigue, weakness, helplessness. These made his fighting spirit surge to another level!

The true inheritance ahead of him was empty, it was not worth wasting time for.

Fang Yuan continued searching.

Next, he found two ordinary inheritances, they were all involving wisdom path.

These two true inheritances had two rank six Immortal Gu respectively.

One was 'false emotion fake will Gu', and the other was 'loving affection Gu."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's wisdom path attainment was very profound, this was a well known fact. Especially in terms of emotion Gu, he had expanded it and created many new Gu recipes.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created a harem and collected beauties, making girls all over the world fall for him, this showed the power of his emotion Gu.

These two inheritances were not what Fang Yuan wanted, he chose to let go.

"Strange, didn't you say that there were not only ordinary true inheritances, but also unparalleled inheritances in this secluded domain? After searching for such a long time, why haven't I found one?" Fang Yuan was confused and asked Mo Yao.

During this period, Mo Yao had not said a word, she seemed to have taken a blow from the possession immortal art, her fighting spirit had dwindled and she had hidden in Fang Yuan's mind without showing herself.

Hearing Fang Yuan's words, she showed her figure and said plainly: "Hmph, how long has it been, you are already impatient? Back in my day, I searched for a whole three months. The secluded domain is extremely huge, and all the inheritances are moving around, there are only a few unparalleled true inheritances, it is normal that you have not found one. Have some patience, lad."

Fang Yuan asked again: "Actually, you came here before, what good inheritances did you find, give me some details about it."

This was his true question.

"Hmph, I saw many inheritances of course, but here, the true inheritances fly around random with no pattern, there is no use in telling you, you can only rely on your luck to search. Heh, beware of the time, the more inheritances you come into contact with, or the longer you stay here, the faster these true inheritances fly, and the more dangerous your situation becomes. Back then, with my Gu Immortal realm, I could only stay for three months, and nearly died here."

As Mo Yao said this, her tone was filled with lingering fear.

"Even you almost died here?" Fang Yuan saw the main point in her words.

"Lad, you are a mortal, you are too weak. I estimate that you can only check eight true inheritances, and can stay for at most a month. Right now, you have already seen five inheritances, you have to be careful!" Mo Yao vaguely reminded him.

"What was it that threatened the life of a grand Gu Immortal like yourself?" Fang Yuan asked.

But Mo Yao only smiled tenderly, saying, "If you are fated for it, you will know when you experience it," before concealing herself.

Fang Yuan's expression turned slightly grim.

He had always held a suspicion.

In the video in his previous life, there were eleven Gu Immortals from central continent, but after they entered the true inheritance secluded domain, after the omitted parts, there were only nine of them who reappeared, all with injuries.

Does that mean, the two missing had died in the secluded domain?

Sometimes, having this Mo Yao's will was advantageous.

Fang Yuan had gotten Mo Yao's reminder and became more careful, slowly investigating.

Three days later, he got close to the sixth true inheritance, and used the special will Gu and big soul worm to obtain the information inside the true inheritance.

This inheritance came from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, it was similar to the third inheritance in that they were both lifespan extending immortal arts.

It involved a new path that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had created from researching Ren Zu, he called it 'yin-yang path'.

To use this method, two Gu Immortals, one male and one female, have to cooperate and copulate, to achieve the result of one of their lifespans increasing.

But there was a flaw.

If one gains lifespan, the other must lose the same amount.

In other words, it was transferring the lifespan of one person to another.

This inheritance had also been taken by others already.

The popularity of lifespan extending methods could be seen clearly here.

"This is the sixth true inheritance." Fang Yuan muttered, thinking of Mo Yao's reminder.

According to Fang Yuan's endurance, he could see eight true inheritances at most, beyond this number, a huge crisis would descend upon him.

If he wanted to obtain a true inheritance, Fang Yuan needed to be careful now.

After all, he only had two chances left, and at the same time he needed to be wary of the inheritance being emptied out already.

Thirteen days later, Fang Yuan found the seventh true inheritance.

This true inheritance light lump was the size of a washing basin, it was shining brightly in white light and had a stronger aura compared to ordinary inheritances.

"Lad, this will broaden your vision, this is an unparalleled true inheritance!" In his mind, Mo Yao said.

Chapter 600: Supreme True Inheritance!

"Unparalleled true inheritance!" Fang Yuan's gaze brightened upon looking at the lump of burning white light in the distance.

He quickly took out special will Gu and a big soul worm. He condensed a will and moved it into the big soul worm, looking as it flew towards the true inheritance light lump.

"Unparalleled true inheritances far surpass ordinary true inheritances, I want to see what is so different about it." Fang Yuan was waiting expectantly.

But an unexpected thing happened.

As the big soul worm approached closer to the true inheritance light lump, Fang Yuan sensed his connection with the big soul worm was weakening.

When the big soul worm had not even reached three hundred steps from the light lump, the connection between it and Fang Yuan had thoroughly broken.

"This... What is this situation?" Fang Yuan was startled, looking at the unparalleled true inheritance flying away leisurely in its original orbit. And the big soul worm he had released showed no signs of movement, being completely still. Saying it was dead was also not appropriate, but no matter how Fang Yuan commanded it, it quietly hovered without the slightest bit of response.

"Eh? This unparalleled true inheritance is not simple, be careful." Mo Yao's will also gave a sound of surprise and warned Fang Yuan.

"What is going on?" Fang Yuan curiously and cautiously approached the big soul worm, picking it up for examination.

There was no signs of injury on the big soul worm, but the will that had been instilled into it was completely gone.

Big soul worm was a rank two Gu; and its wild will was removed after being refined by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's will occupied its body, thus he could maneuver it like moving his fingers.

But right now, Fang Yuan's will that was in it, refined into special will by using special will Gu, had inexplicably disintegrated with not even a trace remaining.

The big soul worm had become completely ownerless, anyone would be able to send a trace of their will and instantly refine it.

This was also the reason why Fang Yuan could not command it regardless of what he did.

The previous several times, Fang Yuan had exploited special will to probe out true inheritances, ingeniously avoiding the test of the true inheritance. This method had been proved successful time and time again, he had never expected it to fail before even verifying the unparalleled true inheritance.

What was this unparalleled true inheritance hiding that could completely clear Fang Yuan's will?

"Ah, I remember! So it was this." Just as Fang Yuan was hesitating, Mo Yao suddenly spoke up.

She laughed coquettishly: "Kid, should I say it is your good luck or bad luck? There are not many unparalleled true inheritances but there are not few either, and what you are encountering now is the most special among them."

"Please advise me." Fang Yuan's expression turned calm.

"I saw this true inheritance before and it also left behind a deep impression on me. Back then, even I had to expend a lot of effort to approach it. Hehehe, inside it is a rank seven Immortal Gu Giant Sun Immortal Venerable personally refined, called human qi Gu. Its ability is mysterious and could even be said to be strange, even I had to spend a lot to investigate it clearly." Mo Yao sighed.

While Mo Yao was alive, she had been a rank seven Gu Immortal, a fairy of Spirit Affinity House with awe-inspiring reputation.

However, she had to pay a considerable price to approach this true inheritance. Fang Yuan was only a mortal now, it was natural for him to not even be able to approach it.

"Human qi Gu..." Fang Yuan pondered over this crucial name.

He had a realization and asked: "Could it have some relationship with the three elements of immortal ascension?"

"Lad, your guess is correct." Mo Yao sighed and explained, "In the advancement to Gu Immortal, the three qi of heaven, earth and human are particularly crucial. When advancing into a Gu Immortal, you would need to completely shatter your aperture and take in the heaven qi and earth qi. The more heaven qi and earth qi you can take in, the higher your chance of succeeding. But heaven qi and earth qi cannot be accumulated limitlessly, they need to be on an equal level with human qi."

"And human qi is the sum of the Gu Master's own accumulation. The Gu Master's battle strength, toughness of their physical body, the depth of their soul, familiarity with Gu worms, understanding of heaven and earth, awareness of their own nature as well as luck, talent, aptitude, fortuitous encounters, insights and so on would transform into human qi when advancing to Gu Immortal."

"The more the Gu Master has accumulated, the more human qi they would have. The more human qi there is, the more heaven and earth qi they can take in, and the higher their chance of advancing to Gu Immortal. And this human qi Gu's purpose is to take in the human qi of other people, purify them and add it to oneself when advancing to Gu Immortal, thereby greatly raising the chance of the breakthrough, as well as deepening the foundation and the potential of Gu Immortals."

Mo Yao's words greatly broadened Fang Yuan's vision.

He could not help but praise: "There is actually such an Immortal Gu, created with such an idea! Terrific!"

In human history, Gu Immortals had always been in extremely few numbers. The difficulty of advancing to a Gu Immortal, among numerous famous rank five Gu Masters, there might only be one who could successfully advance.

Among the crucial keys of advancing to a Gu Immortal, one was at the top - the Gu Master's accumulation.

Many Gu Masters don't have deep accumulation; the human qi they could condense when advancing to Gu Immortal would be very little but the amount of heaven and earth qi instead appears in very high amounts. As such, the balance would not be reached, heaven and earth qi would suppress and swallow the human qi, finally the Gu Master would be assimilated by heaven and earth and perish.

But if there was human qi Immortal Gu, this difficult test would be eliminated.

By collecting other's human qi, purifying them and gathering it into one's body; even if the accumulation is not enough, it would not matter.

One could say, with human qi Immortal Gu, the chances of advancing to Gu Immortal would increase to the extreme, raising the numbers of Gu Immortals.

And raising the numbers of Gu Immortals would mean a distinct increase in a region's strength.

No doubt, this was a Gu that could change the battle situation of the five regions! As long as the news was leaked, all super forces would fanatically rush over like ducks.

However, human qi Immortal Gu was too strong, it was at rank seven, higher than the Spring Autumn Cicada currently.

Fang Yuan had a mortal body, he could not endure the might of human qi Immortal Gu.

His will had been devoured by the Immortal Gu before it was even able to approach it, purified into a negligible amount of human qi and stored.

If not for Mo Yao giving the information, Fang Yuan would still be in the dark and unknowing of what happened.

"Human qi Gu is definitely good, but it does not suit me." Fang Yuan regretfully glanced one final time at the burning white light lump and sighed, shaking his head before leaving in another direction without the least bit of reluctance.

Human qi Gu's realm was too high, Fang Yuan simply did not have the qualifications to control it.

Man is the spirit of all living beings; Gu is the essence of heaven and earth. To Gu Masters, Gu were tools. But human qi Immortal Gu was too strong; if it was an ice blade, Fang Yuan was an infant, he would be frozen by the cold aura let out by the ice blade before he even approached it.

"The most crucial point is that I cannot use human qi Immortal Gu. I need to breakthrough from mortal to advance to Gu Immortal, before that I simply cannot handle human qi Gu. And if I become a Gu Immortal, what would I need human qi Gu for?" Helping others?"

Human qi Immortal Gu was not suitable for the lone Fang Yuan. Only those super forces would need it.

Unless Fang Yuan formed his own force.

He slowly flew around in the true inheritance secluded domain.

Fang Yuan gradually comprehended something and said after a moment of silence: "Mo Yao, I realized the danger you spoke of."

"Hehehe." Mo Yao smiled, not surprised, "When Gu Masters enter the true inheritance secluded domain, every time they come in contact with a true inheritance or the longer the time they stay here, the faster these true inheritances would move around. Thus, urging the Gu Masters to quickly choose a true inheritance. By the end, the true inheritances would move as fast as meteors, Gu Masters simply would not be able to capture them. Because of this, the Gu Masters could lose their lives at any minute."

Pausing a while, Mo Yao continued: "And the danger to life originates from the true inheritances. You saw the unparalleled true inheritance just before. Your will had not even neared it before it was refined into human qi by human qi Immortal Gu. Think about it, if it crashes into you with the speed of a meteor, you won't have any time to dodge, what will happen then?"

Fang Yuan lightly snorted.

He could completely imagine that scene.

If a mortal body was struck by the burning white light lump, no matter their physical body, soul or will, everything would probably disintegrate and be refined into human qi.

"Like I said before, you are too weak, only at the mortal realm. Even the tests of the ordinary true inheritances are a difficult hurdle to you. Unparalleled true inheritances are even more troublesome. Let me tell you, there is a higher level of inheritance above unparalleled true inheritance - Supreme True Inheritance." Mo Yao revealed a sensational piece of information.

"Supreme true inheritance?!"

"In this whole true inheritance secluded domain, there are only three supreme true inheritances." Mo Yao sighed with deep emotions, seemingly immersed in the depths of her memory, "It is simply impossible for a mortal to receive these three supreme true inheritances. The difficulty of an unparalleled true inheritance is already extremely high, moreover Imperial Court blessed land prohibits the entry of Gu Immortals. This is also the reason for Eighty-Eight True Yang Building being able to stand tall for so long, among the eighty-eight true inheritances, there are still over half remaining."

Fang Yuan carefully pondered and approved of Mo Yao's words.

Entering true inheritance secluded domain was extremely difficult, and the opportunity was very uncertain. First of all, one needed to be the winner of the Imperial Court contest held every ten years. Secondly, they needed to complete at least ten floors of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Finally, after entering, they still needed to successfully pass the test of the true inheritance.

In other words, every ten years, among the many heroes of northern plains, there would only be one who would rise above others and take control of the owner token.

Simply relying on the owner token was still not enough, the winner must have a strong force which should not be exhausted too greatly in the Imperial Court contest, and also should have enough experts beside him. His force should have enough talents in all fields and involving a wide range of paths, only then could he hope to pass ten floors.

After fortunately being able to enter true inheritance secluded domain, the tests of the true inheritances would further wipe away a batch of these winners.

The tests were very difficult, even Fang Yuan, a reborn old monster, almost suffered a setback, let alone these people.

What was more absurd was that even if they passed the test, would that true inheritance be coincidentally suitable for them?

Not necessarily.

Those who could reach this step were usually dragons among dragons, phoenixes among phoenixes, heroes among heroes, with all three aspects of aptitude, talent and fortuitous encounters. Such characters would have extremely high aspirations, and would naturally think about it a lot and look through more options.

As such, by the time they could no longer stay within true inheritance secluded domain, it would be too late for regret.

Who is to say they might not die here?

"The true inheritances' flying speed is getting faster, you have one more chance left. No matter which true inheritance it is, take it quickly and leave... eh?! Not good, leave!" Just as she was persuading him, Mo Yao's tone suddenly changed and let out a startled cry.

Fang Yuan turned his head around to take a glance and saw a true inheritance, the size of an adult man, blossoming with all kinds of mysterious colors, whizzing towards him. In the dark secluded domain, it had a very long dazzling and burning tail trailing behind it.

A light lump the size of a large bowl was an ordinary true inheritance.

A basin sized light lump was an unparalleled true inheritance.

Then what was a light lump the size of an adult?

Fang Yuan instantly thought of the name - Supreme True Inheritance!

In the whole true inheritance secluded domain, only three supreme true inheritances existed, and now, one was heading towards Fang Yuan!

Chapter 601: Profiting from the situation

"Supreme true inheritance!" Fang Yuan's pupils enlarged and his gaze burned brightly.

When the true inheritance light lump was still a thousand steps away, Fang Yuan felt its surging aura.

This was a feeling which ordinary true inheritances and even unparalleled true inheritances did not have.

Under the effect of this aura, thoughts started to gather in Fang Yuan's mind; countless thoughts emerged out of thin air and his memories flashed past continuously.

If his mind was like a deep pond during normal times, then right now, the rapidly increasing thoughts were like a huge waterfall crashing down into this deep pond.

Thoughts surged madly, creating waves after waves!

This feeling was incomparably wonderful, and Fang Yuan was not able to find an accurate word to describe it.

The memories buried deep within his mind started to emerge one after another, the dust on them removed as they realistically and vividly appeared in his mind.

Great numbers of inspirational lights flashed past and all sorts of lively ideas emerged in Fang Yuan's mind. Some problems and doubts regarding cultivation were being instantly solved under the inspirational lights.

An extremely strong self-confidence involuntarily arose in Fang Yuan's mind.

This was an indescribably wonderful feeling, as if everything was within his control, as if there were no problems he could not solve.....

This was a special 'power' that people could not help but be deeply addicted to.

"Lad, wake up quickly, I also know how intoxicating this feeling is, but if you don't want to die, don't lose yourself in it! Look at yourself quickly!" Mo Yao shouted.

This voice awakened Fang Yuan, and when he looked at himself, he was pale with horror!

In just a short moment, his body had become weak and exhausted, his glossy forehead now had wrinkles, his strong arms gave a feeling of being old and decayed and were turning even more weak.

If not for Mo Yao's reminder, Fang Yuan might have lost himself in that wonderful feeling and overlooked the changes to his body.

"This Gu is...?!" Fang Yuan thought of an incomparably shocking answer, and at the same time, used his movement Gu to quickly retreat!

True inheritance secluded domain did not prohibit the use of Gu worms.

The supreme true inheritance also was not chasing Fang Yuan and just continued to fly on its path.

Fang Yuan rapidly pulled distance with it before fearfully looking at this supreme true inheritance that was flying far away, cutting open the dark space.

"This is only the aura of a supreme true inheritance and it almost made me lose myself and die. How difficult would its test be?" Fang Yuan exclaimed in shock.

He could not even get near human qi Gu, an unparalleled true inheritance. There was no need to speak of supreme true inheritance; let alone approaching it, just by nearing it a little, the aura it leaked out almost took his life.

Just like Mo Yao said, Fang Yuan as a mortal was too weak!

This inheritance was definitely a great thing but he did not have the strength to bear it. It was like a bee picking honey, if the honey was as big as a fist, the bee would instead drown to death.

"The Immortal Gu of this supreme true inheritance, could it be... that legendary Gu?" Fang Yuan spoke with almost eighty percent certainty. But this answer was too shocking, making him somewhat unable to believe it.

"Hehehe." Mo Yao laughed, "Lad, your guess is correct. Even I did not dare to believe it back then, but the truth is right before your eyes, there is no choice but to believe it! Right, the Immortal Gu contained in this supreme true inheritance is the rank nine Gu of legend, wisdom Gu!"

Wisdom Gu!

It was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

This was a rank nine Immortal Gu which could give endless wisdom to the Gu Master!

But the price to use it was extremely high.

The legends of Ren Zu clearly recorded that Ren Zu and Desolate Ancient Moon had to give their middle age to it to obtain its help.

In other words, using wisdom Gu meant using up lifespan!

Fang Yuan had not even approached it, but his lifespan had been worn down rapidly; wrinkles appeared and his body aged in just a short period of time.

In regards to Fang Yuan, wisdom Gu was a true death god!

"I really don't know how Giant Sun Immortal Venerable obtained it back then and even more, what heaven defying methods did he use to seal it here. No wonder Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought up all kinds of methods to extend lifespan, he must have used wisdom Gu a lot." Fang Yuan was deeply moved.

Mo Yao instead sighed: "Giant Sun Immortal Venerable probably used wisdom Gu for one reason - to extend lifespan. Unfortunately, the more wisdom Gu was used, the shorter his lifespan became, and in the end, he did not obtain the solution he wanted as well."

According to the historical records, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable lived for over eight thousand years before dying.

Eight thousand years was already a result on the middle to upper level among rank nine venerables. Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable who had the longest lifespan, lived for twenty-five thousand years. The one with the shortest lifespan was Red Lotus Demon Venerable who only lived for three thousand years.

Other venerables generally had a lifespan of around seven thousand years.

"There are three supreme true inheritances in true inheritance secluded domain. Tell me, what are the other two like? I really want to experience them." Fang Yuan's eyes let out an indescribable radiance.

Mo Yao felt something wrong with his tone, and quickly persuaded: "Lad, don't have stupid thoughts, pick up an ordinary true inheritance quickly and leave! You have the ten-edge owner token and can only take away an ordinary true inheritance anyway. Even if you pass the test of an unparalleled true inheritance, you cannot take them. Don't even mention supreme true inheritances, your weak body that can be blown away by the wind cannot even endure their aura!"

Fang Yuan laughed loudly: "Your words make me even more interested to see them! This opportunity is extremely rare, I am afraid I won't get another chance if I miss it this time."

"Brat, have you gone mad? Do you not know you lost at least two years of your lifespan just a few moments ago! If you continue squandering time like this, and the true inheritances start flying with the speed of a meteor, you won't be able to get anything, and you might even lose your life!" Mo Yao was anxious.

Fang Yuan kept on laughing without being moved.

He continued to wander, detouring far away when he saw ordinary true inheritances and unparalleled true inheritances, with not even a bit of intention to take them.

Mo Yao's will became more anxious: "You lunatic! Heavens, what in the world are you thinking in your brain? You are letting so many true inheritances go away just to broaden your horizons? You idiot, if you die, what should I do? What about Water Pavilion?"

"If I die, this will of yours will also not be able to survive, but you can rest easy, you still have a will left in Water Pavilion. You can wait for a fated person and entrust this precious task upon them." Fang Yuan unhurriedly replied.

Mo Yao tried to persuade him again, but Fang Yuan was adamant in doing things his own way.

He kept on exploring non-stop, and after several days, the true inheritances were moving faster; Fang Yuan went into dangerous situations every now and then.

Several times, he faced the danger of losing his life, but narrowly managed to escape in the end.

Mo Yao had been trying to persuade him the whole time, the anxiety making her go mad: "Lad, I surrender, you are truly stubborn! Alright, you don't have to continue, I will tell you about the other two supreme true inheritances."

"The first is a luck path inheritance founded by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, using his unique luck path attainment, he was able to become invincible in the world! Second is the control rights of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. This tower was refined by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Long Hair Ancestor; it can plunder the Gu worms of a region, there would be endless Gu cultivation resources for one who obtains it!"

She was truly anxious.

Normally, she might not necessarily be in the mood to provide such inside details to Fang Yuan even if he asked. Now, however, she revealed it, afraid Fang Yuan would continue acting foolishly.

But what she was afraid of happened.

Fang Yuan chuckled and as if he had not heard anything, continued to wander.

Several days later, the true inheritances' flying speed was already as fast as birds. It was extremely easy for Fang Yuan to evade one or two, but true inheritance secluded domain seemed to be shrinking and all sizes of true inheritances had to fly in the narrowing space. The long tails of all sorts of colorful lights they dragged were almost interweaving a thinly spread light web. Fang Yuan could only survive moving through the cracks of it.

At this stage, Fang Yuan was using all his concentration and did not dare to relax for even a moment, for a moment of carelessness would lead to the tragedy of his death.

"Leave quickly. You can't even take away ordinary true inheritances now. As long as you continue to stay here, the danger will increase by each second. Sigh, you have actually gone crazy in such a crucial moment!" Mo Yao was getting dispirited from all the persuading.

Fang Yuan's gaze was burning, suddenly asking: "Tell me, is there a possibility I can find an opportunity to reap benefits when two true inheritances collide?"

Mo Yao was stunned upon listening to this.

But soon, she shouted in a shrill voice: "You fool, you idiot! Would the grand Giant Sun Immortal Venerable commit such a clear mistake? So you were thinking like that, I overestimated you! I overestimated you too much! You have clearly become a victim of your own ingenuity, how could there be such an obvious loophole for you to exploit? You have thought too wishfully, you are too naive!"

"Eh, so it was just my wishful thinking." Fang Yuan chuckled, his expression undisturbed as he continued to explore.

Actually, he had already known this, but intentionally said it to provoke Mo Yao.

"Why are you still not leaving? Are you looking to die?!" Mo Yao was provoked and was completely driven mad by Fang Yuan.

"Whether I die or not is my matter, it is none of your concern. You have already died, why is a dead person making such a din?" Fang Yuan indifferently ridiculed her; his expression still tranquil as if the one in danger was not him.

"Damn it! Scoundrel! Idiot!" Mo Yao's face flushed with rage and started hurling out curses.

Rumble...

Right at this time, an explosion suddenly occurred a great distance away.

Fang Yuan gazed at the source of the sound, seeing two true inheritances colliding which then sprang towards different directions.

Fang Yuan was dumbstruck.

He had not expected his nonsensical words to come true, true inheritances actually collided!

Especially when one of the inheritances seemed to be a supreme true inheritance!!

Mo Yao was also dumbstruck.

"How is this possible?" Her voice rose an octave higher into an ear-piercing sound that had no demeanor of a refinement path grandmaster, "Back then, when I explored this place, why did not I encounter such a good thing?!"

But soon, her eyes opened wide, coming to a realization: "So it was like that! That is the luck path supreme true inheritance, back then I did all I could to open up a crack in it to obtain the fortune rivalling heaven Gu, but in the end it flew away. I could only use the other inheritances I obtained to settle for the second best option, refining calamity beckoning Gu!"

Mo Yao had created a crack in this supreme true inheritance, because it was no longer in a perfect state, the original balance was tilted, allowing true inheritances to collide into one another.

Boom!

Another sound of a collision.

Fang Yuan's eyes opened wide, this collision seemed to have caused a Gu to fly out from the luck path supreme true inheritance?

Fang Yuan was stumped: "What is that?"

Mo Yao was also stupefied before shouting: "That is a luck path Gu worm, what are being dazed for, aren't you going to take it?"

Fang Yuan, however, hesitated: "If I try to take this Gu, wouldn't I be met with the luck path true inheritance's test?"

Luck path true inheritance was a supreme true inheritance, Fang Yuan would never be able to endure its test.

"What damned test! The collision has enlarged the crack in the true inheritance light lump, it is breaking down. Take it and leave quickly, if you don't leave now, you are going to die here!" Mo Yao shouted.

Fang Yuan chuckled and moved forward, dodging here and there, before being able to approach with great difficulty and pick up that Gu worm.

This was a rank five mortal Gu and not an Immortal Gu.

"Lad, you are still not leaving?!" Mo Yao was almost howling by now.

"Haha, what's the rush." Fang Yuan laughed heartily, but did not leave, instead staying within true inheritance secluded domain, observing everywhere.

"Looking at the time, with the current chaos, it is almost ready." he mumbled.

"Lad, what did you say?"

Mo Yao had just spoken when Fang Yuan sprinkled many Gu worms which activated together to form a whirlpool.

The whirlpool let out a majestic force of attraction, absorbing all the true inheritance lights.

Several breaths later, the whirlpool slowed down and crumbled with a loud sound, revealing a door.

"All according to plan!" Fang Yuan threw himself in without hesitation.

The next moment.

He saw the land spirit!

Chapter 602: Frost Jade Peacock

The scene before one's eyes was that of a grand and elegant white jade hall.

Four huge pillars were holding up the roof, on the ground, light casted shadows on a person.

Be it the walls, pillars, or roof, they were pure and white as snow, they were all created using white jade stones.

At the center of the hall, there was an elevated area with twenty-three steps of stairs.

On the elevated area, there was a green copper divine bird statue. The divine bird was looking up, and spreading its wings, but there were countless black chains, each with the size of an ancient tree, coiling around the divine bird's body, tangling around its long neck, its slim legs, and even piercing through its feathers and lodging itself into its body.

The divine bird's eyes were sharp as daggers, it was frowning and had its mouth wide open, almost as if screaming out loud. Its expression was very moving, it looked so real with delicate details, and there was an indomitable spirit of resistance oozing from it, this spirit could leave a firm impression after a single gaze.

Fang Yuan appeared on the stairs, looking at the tall and huge green copper divine bird statue covering his vision, his dark pupils seemed to have flames burning within.

"This, this, this!" The sudden turn of events shocked Mo Yao to the point of stuttering.

She gulped as she pointed her finger, shouting: "This is actually the Frost Jade Peacock, Imperial Court blessed land's land spirit!!"

"Ah, what's there to be surprised about?" Fang Yuan's lips curled into a smile, he said: "Imperial Court blessed land originally had a land spirit, otherwise it would not have recognised Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and made him its master. The land spirit is formed by the combination of an obsession and the blessed land's heavenly power, to get rid of the land spirit, you will have to deal with the entire blessed land. If the land spirit dies, the blessed land will be destroyed. If the blessed land is destroyed, the land spirit will die too. Currently Imperial Court blessed land is still in good shape, it means the land spirit is still alive."

His words made Mo Yao shout in anger: "You bastard, such obvious reasoning, how could I not know this!"

Mo Yao had done all she could to research Eighty-Eight True Yang Building for her lover Bo Qing, in an attempt to get the fortune rivalling heaven Gu, and help Bo Qing advance to rank nine.

Eventually, although she succeeded in entering the true inheritance secluded domain, because of her insufficient power she could not obtain fortune rivalling heaven Gu. Instead she had to settle for something else, using her inheritance information and her own foundation as a refinement grandmaster to refine the calamity beckoning Gu.

Because of this, she understood the value of the land spirit of Imperial Court blessed land extremely clearly!

Back then, when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was not rank nine, he had won in the competition for Imperial Court blessed land's inheritance, and became the owner of Imperial Court blessed land.

When he became rank nine and was invincible in the world, he had the superior grotto-heaven, Longevity Heaven, and thus Imperial Court blessed land became one of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's multiple residences within the world.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and set it up within Imperial Court blessed land.

This formed a relationship — if one was targeting Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, they would need to first enter Imperial Court blessed land. Imperial Court blessed land thus became a protective shell for Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

After Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement, this shell had been exerting great use, in that Gu Immortals could not enter.

But in this setup, there was a huge flaw, any Gu Immortal could see it clearly!

That was the existence of the land spirit of Imperial Court blessed land!

This flaw did not exist when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was still alive. Because Giant Sun was the master of the land spirit, the land spirit would obey and do whatever he told it to do.

But after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable died, Imperial Court blessed land became ownerless. As long as one could meet the land spirit's expectations, anyone could become Imperial Court blessed land's new owner.

And Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was situated inside Imperial Court blessed land, thus whoever controlled Imperial Court blessed land would have Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in their grasp.

As long as one was a Gu Immortal, they would understand this from just a small amount of thinking.

In Mo Yao's lifetime, when researching Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, she had spent a huge amount of time and effort in this field.

But eventually, she made no progress.

All the hard work and effort she put into this resulted in nothing.

What sort of person was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, how could he be unaware of this loophole? He dealt with this perfectly, sealing the land spirit deep within, and in Mo Yao's eventual exploration, she could not even find a single feather of the land spirit.

"To think that the land spirit was hidden inside the true inheritance secluded domain! Only when the true inheritances fly at a certain speed would this loophole appear, and allow for the possibility of opening this gateway!" Mo Yao's heart was shaken, at this moment, she understood what had happened.

The more she thought about it, the more she viewed Fang Yuan with a new and higher level of respect.

"This lad, I underestimated him! What sort of background does he have, he actually knew this method of entry?" Mo Yao was shocked and curious.

Fang Yuan's performance was very shocking, it greatly exceeded her expectations.

What she did not know was, this was inside the video from central continent's Gu Immortals in Fang Yuan's previous life.

In fact, the deep research of central continent's Gu Immortals was actually built upon the foundation of Mo Yao's findings.

Mo Yao was an impressive refinement grandmaster, for her lover, she researched the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and charged in alone. After she died, the previous research material that she left behind was in the hands of Spirit Affinity House.

For the ten thousand years after that, generations after generations of geniuses within Spirit Affinity House continued their research on it. At the same time, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had been corroded by the power of time, showing more and more loopholes over the years, becoming easier to exploit.

But Spirit Affinity House knew that to take down this juicy meat called Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it was not something a super force could do alone. Thus, Spirit Affinity House secretly worked with several other central continent sects and planned this for thousands of years.

Spirit Affinity House took the lead as they controlled the most important research materials from beginning to end. Later, good preparation would be the key to success, when central continent's Gu Immortals attacked, the group was led by Spirit Affinity House's fairy of that generation, Black Moon.

As he walked up the stairs, Fang Yuan arrived at the foot of the green copper divine bird.

This tall statue was Imperial Court blessed land's land spirit, Frost Jade Peacock!

Except that it was sealed tightly by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, and could not move. Since hundreds of thousands of years ago, throughout the ages, it had been standing here without any movement.

As they got closer, Mo Yao had a discovery: "Heh, lad, your plan will be hard to execute. The green paste on the Frost Jade Peacock's body is created by the rank seven Immortal Gu Earth Prison. The black chains that are coiling around its body are made from the rank seven Immortal Gu Earth Net... Eh!"

While saying this, Mo Yao thought of something and her words stopped.

At once, in Fang Yuan's mind, she was staring with her eyes wide open, like she had seen a ghost.

Because she had suddenly remembered: Not long ago, Fang Yuan summoned two Immortal Gu, one of them was Gruel Mud!

Earth prison Gu, earth net Gu, although they were rank seven Immortal Gu and were higher than Gruel Mud by one rank.

But they were one time expenditure Gu, they vanished after one use.

The two rank seven Immortal Gu worked together to seal the land spirit, but after hundreds of thousands of years of corrosion from time, this strength had weakened greatly.

And Gruel Mud was a direct counter to this strength!

"Hahaha, it seems you have already thought about it, you are not too stupid." Fang Yuan laughed heartily as he took out the gruel mud Immortal Gu from his pocket.

Although this Gu was rank six, because it was an expenditure type Gu, it was comparatively easier to use, there was no need to inject immortal essence into it, he just needed to squeeze it.

Fang Yuan squeezed lightly and it shattered.

The Gu worm burst and oozed out a brown-green light that was like liquid.

The light followed Fang Yuan's will and flew up, fusing into the divine bird statue.

Throughout the process, Mo Yao watched in a daze, unable to say a word.

After the light fused into the statue, a slight tremor occured, but this tremor was simply too light, it was almost like an illusion.

But soon, this tremor became larger.

The entire divine bird statue starting shaking. Cracks were forming on the green paste covering the divine bird statue, next, the chains starting colliding with one another, making a loud and sharp noise.

"Su... success?! Don't tell me, after hundreds of thousands of years of wear and tear, the powers of the two Immortal Gu were used up?" Mo Yao muttered to herself, she had a complex expression, there were disbelief, surprise, suspicion, and denial...

But afterwards, the tremors became smaller.

The divine bird statue became silent, and the chains stopped clashing, the entire white jade hall became quiet once again.

Mo Yao was deeply disappointed, she sighed: "Failed in the end! There was the difference of a rank, plus this was the setup of an Immortal Venerable."

"Hehehe." But at this point, Fang Yuan laughed lightly: "Mo Yao, look at the divine bird's head?"

Mo Yao's will looked over and was shocked: "The green paste on the land spirit's head is slowly melting! That's right, this is the gruel mud Immortal Gu's real effect, I was too caught up with the commotion and got carried away, I lost my bearings and did not think of this. Hehe, laughable, how laughable."

Mo Yao suddenly shook her head and sighed, immediately afterwards her expression had vanished completely, restoring the demeanour of a legendary Gu Immortal, a refinement grandmaster.

Actually, she could not help but briefly lose her cool.

In her life, she had paid too huge of a price for Imperial Court blessed land, for Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Right now, earth prison Gu and earth net Gu, the powers of these two Immortal Gu, although corroded mostly by the power of time, they still had a portion remaining.

Although gruel mud Immortal Gu was effective against them, it was only rank six, it was still very difficult to get rid of the remaining power.

But don't forget about the existence of the land spirit!

The tremors earlier were due to the land spirit.

It was the one which exerted strength, causing the two Immortal Gu to divert the majority of their power to suppress it, allowing the gruel mud Immortal Gu's power to sneak in.

As the green paste melted, it turned into gruel mud on the white jade floor, the green-black mud was a great contrast to the white tiles on the ground.

Drop by drop, they fell on the ground.

The Frost Jade Peacock's head was released, but after getting to its neck, the speed of melting greatly reduced.

Evidently, earth prison and earth net Gu's remaining power reacted and started to resist Gruel Mud, causing the efficiency to reduce greatly.

"Heh, just like in the video in my previous life, it is exactly the same." Fang Yuan laughed as he looked at the land spirit, Frost Jade Peacock: "Oh Imperial Court land spirit, look down at your feet, I was the one who released you. How does it feel to breathe again after hundreds of thousands of years? As long as you recognise me as your master, I will help you to regain freedom!"

Frost Jade Peacock's angry expression was still fixed on its face, hearing Fang Yuan's words, it laughed arrogantly: "I am one with the blessed land, all the things that happened in the blessed land for the last hundreds of thousands of years are clear in my heart. If you want to be my new owner, you will need to fulfill one condition."

Hundreds of thousands of years ago, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's fulfilled this land spirit's request and became Imperial Court blessed land's owner.

Today, Fang Yuan was facing this request as well.

At this point, the video in his previous life had no more value. Fang Yuan laughed as his eyes shone, asking —

"What condition?"

Chapter 603: Sleepless Night

"No, don't abandon me..."

"Save me, save me, benefactor!"

The voices were reverberating in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's ears, he opened his eyes suddenly and sat up on his bed.

Huff, huff...

He was panting, with his body covered in sticky sweat, it was very uncomfortable.

Another nightmare!

Under the dim light, this rank five peak stage expert's face showed an old and weary expression befitting his age.

In the silent room, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's breathing sounds became softer, as his frown slowly eased.

Sitting on his bed, he fell into deep silence, like he was in a daze, there was an extreme fatigue hidden in his gaze.

Ever since he failed the round, he had been in deep guilt and self-blame for causing Gao Yang and Zhu Zai to be sacrificed due to his own greed.

Almost every night, he had the same nightmare.

In the nightmare, blood was pouring everywhere, the smell was overbearing. All sorts of ugly blood beasts bared their claws and fangs as he was encircled, facing Gao Yang and Zhu Zai's pleas.

They called him benefactor, they asked him to save them.

But every time, even though Tai Bai Yun Sheng had an aperture full of primeval essence, he would be unable to move, watching Gao Yang and Zhu Zai get surrounded by blood beasts and eventually consumed, leaving behind their pale white bones.

Throughout the process, Gao Yang and Zhu Zai would sometimes beg him, sometimes they would protect him, or curse furiously, or taunt him.

Eventually, when they turn into pale white skeletons, lying in the pool of blood, they would still say with their remaining skulls—

"I believe in Lord Tai Bai, he is so kind and righteous, he will definitely never abandon us!"

"Mm, I believe in him too! Even if I die, I will believe..."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was in pain, he felt sadness, helplessness, and regret!

Especially at the end, he would kneel on the ground helplessly in his dream, letting the blood dye his white hair red as he cried profusely.

He felt that he was no longer Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

This experience made him reevaluate himself.

But every time he examined, it resulted in a severe negative answer.

Sometimes when he looked in the mirror, he felt that he was looking at a stranger!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was not the only person who had a sleepless night.

It was late at night.

Imperial Court blessed land's night was dazzling with silver light, shining on the land.

Hei Lou Lan looked out of the window, above the sacred palace, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was still forming new floors, the dazzling aurora was shining brightly in the sky, creating a beautiful scenery.

"Damn it! The owner token went missing, what in the world happened?" Thinking back to the time when he challenged the round, Hei Lou Lan gritted his teeth, he clenched his fists as his eyes shone with ruthlessness, ready to devour people with one glance.

Throughout history, there had never been any Lord of the Imperial Court who lost their owner token, but this had to happen to Hei Lou Lan.

"Forget it! So what if I don't have the owner token, so what if I cannot use the Grey Meltdown killer move? Whatever the difficulties, they cannot stop me from getting the strength path Immortal Gu! Mother, if you can watch this from the afterlife, see how I take revenge for you!"

Fang Yuan was slowly walking in the sacred palace's garden.

His expression was not nice, he had a grim look on his face.

In the flower garden, there was a jade fountain and a stone bridge, with flowers blooming and flourishing like it was spring, this beautiful environment was not something he could currently enjoy.

Right after coming out of the white jade hall, Fang Yuan was feeling vexed about the matter of subduing Imperial Court land spirit.

In his mind, Mo Yao's will chuckled: "Hehehe, to think that Imperial Court blessed land's condition for ownership was like that. Lad, with your gloomy personality, it will not be easy for you to find a woman that you love, while she also has to be deeply in love with you."

Not long ago, Fang Yuan faced Imperial Court land spirit Frost Jade Peacock, and was told the condition to become the owner of Imperial Court — true love!

To make the Frost Jade Peacock willingly submit to a master, and obey every command, one person was not enough, it had to be a Gu Master couple who were deeply in love.

It was very easy for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to fulfill this condition.

But for Fang Yuan, it was filled with difficulty.

Not mentioning the other parts, just requiring Fang Yuan to be truly in love with a certain woman was a near impossible matter.

"If this was in my previous life, I would be able to fulfill it. But now..." Fang Yuan took a few steps and stopped at the stone bridge, he rested on the railing and looked at the jade lake below the bridge, laughing coldly.

The lake was like a mirror, under the radiance of the silvery night sky, it was a dazzling sight.

What he did in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building that night was really a scary experience, but that was over now.

At this moment, he was basking in the beautiful scenery around the sacred palace, compared to the dangerous predicament he was in earlier, this truly felt like a dream or illusion.

"Life is like a dream, like morning dew and nocturnal flower, like the shadow of a bubble..." Fang Yuan muttered, going into a daze.

The light breeze caused ripples on the surface of the lake.

Among the ripples, a blurry image of a woman's figure seemed to appear in Fang Yuan's absent-minded gaze.

That was the woman he had buried deep in his memories.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, he had faced disaster and was a destitute wanderer, during the lowest time of his life, he had met her, the world's encounters were just so amazing, and the toying of fate was simply cruel and merciless.

"If we are talking about true love... why am I thinking of her?" Fang Yuan's fingers which were holding the railing exerted force unknowingly.

He frowned suddenly, and his gaze turned ice cold, the woman's figure silently vanished, and the surface of the lake appeared before him once again.

Fang Yuan fell into deep thought.

The current situation was not looking good!

Frost Jade Peacock was formed from the obsession of the blessed land's original owner, although it was arrogant, it would acknowledge true love.

But it was near impossible for Fang Yuan to meet its requirements.

If he could not subdue the land spirit, then Fang Yuan's plan for taking over Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would fail completely, he would have to stop here.

"No wonder the central continent Gu Immortals in my previous life chose to destroy Imperial Court blessed land, and destroy Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Gu Immortals have lots of deep secrets and often have extreme personalities, it is harder for them to experience true love than mortals."

"After using Gruel Mud, even though the melting is slow, the land spirit's seal is getting weaker. After being sealed for hundreds of thousands of years, the land spirit is filled with hatred and desires freedom badly, it will definitely try to break the seal. Although Giant Sun's will is still slumbering, when the seal melts to a certain degree, or if the land spirit continues to resist, it will definitely awaken!"

This was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's will!

When an Immortal Venerable rages, blood would flow like a river, all beings would mourn. But the land spirit has the territorial advantage, as long as the blessed land remains intact, it would have a continual source of strength.

When the two contest, it would be scarier than deities fighting. At that point, those who were mortals like Fang Yuan would suffer.

Especially when Fang Yuan was the culprit who released the land spirit, if he was targeted by Giant Sun's will, he would face a terrible end, there was no way out!

Fang Yuan's original plan was like this.

First, he would enter northern plains and make his way into Imperial Court blessed land.

He achieved this flawlessly, using his previous life's memories, he killed the Wolf King Chang Shan Yin who was at his last breath, taking over his identity and becoming a higher-up of Hei tribe army. Next, he hid within the alliance army and got into Imperial Court blessed land.

The second step was to get into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and gain the most benefits for himself. Using the video from the central continent Gu Immortals in his previous life, he would subdue the land spirit and without alerting the Immortal Venerable's will, he would become the new owner of Imperial Court blessed land.

The third step, after becoming the owner of the Imperial Court, he would not be in a rush to take down Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, instead he would hide in the background and develop in secret.

Within Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there was an Immortal Venerable's will, it was not easy to deal with. Imperial Court blessed land was a sacred place in the hearts of northern plains' Gu Masters, it could not be defiled or tainted.

If he was discovered, Fang Yuan would face the assault of the entirety of northern plains!

Such frightening power, even if Fang Yuan escaped to other places, it would be pointless. There would not be a single super force that would protect him from the pressure of the whole of northern plains' forces.

Unless it was during the chaotic five regions battle, when no one had the spare energy to bother with him, and when all five regions suffer setbacks, Fang Yuan would survive even if he was exposed.

After becoming the land spirit's owner, Fang Yuan would order the land spirit to stay inside the white jade hall, while cooperating with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's operations.

This way, everything would progress smoothly.

First, he could use Imperial Court blessed land's strength to deal with the Gu Immortal Tai Bai Yun Sheng. This way, he would have a greater chance of success, and regardless of how their battle end up, Fang Yuan would not lose. Even if he failed to take the Immortal Gu Landscape as Before, Fang Yuan would not be in any mortal danger due to the land spirit's protection.

Secondly, Fang Yuan could use Fixed Immortal Travel to move between Hu Immortal blessed land and Imperial Court blessed land freely. Hu Immortal blessed land was being covetously eyed by Immortal Crane Sect, and every once in a while, there would be an earthly calamity, it would be the centre of many struggles and not the ideal place to cultivate peacefully.

By becoming the owner of Imperial Court blessed land, he could use Hu Immortal blessed land as his cover and Imperial Court blessed land as his true base. While cultivating, he could scheme against Immortal Crane Sect to gain the most benefits. If it failed, he could discard Hu Immortal blessed land and retreat into Imperial Court blessed land.

Imperial Court blessed land was protected by an Immortal Venerable's setup, it was hard for wisdom path Gu Immortals to make deductions involving it. Moreover, Fang Yuan would continue to fix and repair the loopholes in the future, thus it would be much safer than Hu Immortal blessed land!

Thirdly, Fang Yuan would own this precious resource, every time True Yang Building opens up, he could collect all these vast amounts of resources including Immortal Gu without putting himself in danger. When the time comes, he would do what he did in his previous life, subduing a blood path Gu worm and becoming a blood path Gu Immortal. It would be slow and steady, safe and sound.

But though the plan was perfect, reality was not.

Fang Yuan put in his best effort, but he was stuck at the second step.

Unable to become the land spirit's owner, he could not borrow its strength, as a mortal, there was nothing much he could do.

The situation was progressively getting worse, Giant Sun's will was definitely going to awaken. If Fang Yuan wanted to escape, he could use hole earth Gu and connect to Hu Immortal blessed land to flee. But he could not bring these few Immortal Gu with him!

Moreover, even if he obtained landscape as before Immortal Gu, how would he quickly and safely return to Hu Immortal blessed land?

Without the land spirit's help, as a mortal, Fang Yuan could not do that.

"At present, the plan can only be to first think of every possible method to convince the land spirit. If I am on its side, we can deal with Giant Sun's will together, and I might be able to borrow some of its strength. Sigh... I really do not want to use that final method."

Fang Yuan thought about it for a while, but could not think of any better ideas.

Chapter 604: Luck Inspection Gu

Half a month later.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The wind scythe birds were densely packed together, a great number of them engulfed the sky as they charged towards the alliance army.

These wind scythe birds had beaks as sharp as swords, their wings were curved and razor-edged, like that of a scythe. They flew extremely fast, leaving behind afterimages in the air, and had no fear when they charged towards their enemies.

"Kill, kill, kill!" Hei Lou Lan shouted, the black smoke around his body was rolling, creating multiple black tentacles as they captured the surrounding wind scythe birds one after another and devoured them.

The battle of the army fighting against the wind scythe birds had been ongoing for an hour, with both sides suffering heavy casualties.

The floor was littered with bird corpses, but there were also many dead Gu Masters.

"Ahhhhh..." Hei Lou Lan screamed, he was going berserk from fighting, stretching out his right hand.

His right arm was in a claw shape, as a dark spiral was formed, it rotated in the air and converged at the center of his right claw.

In the blink of an eye, thousands of dark streams gathered like they were flowing into the sea, into Hei Lou Lan's right claw like a black light ball.

The light ball was dark and mysterious, it spun on its own and gave out a thunder like sound.

"Go!" Hei Lou Lan's eyes suddenly opened wide as he shouted, using all his strength to point his claw at the sky.

He grabbed the round ball of black light like he was lifting heavy weight, his movement was very slow and strenuous.

Following this movement, the light ball slowly flew into the air.

In the air, it rapidly expanded, in a few breaths' time, it expanded to the size of a mountain.

At once, the black light ball occupied the sky covering half the alliance army's surface area.

Countless wind scythe birds were engulfed by it, melting and corroding, not even their bones were left intact.

The entire process was silent and strangely overbearing, people's hearts were turning cold from seeing this.

This was Hei Lou Lan's signature killer move — Dark Vortex!

After lasting for six breaths' time, the vortex killed tens of thousands of wind scythe birds.

The numbers of the wind scythe birds were too huge, and because they gathered above the alliance army, they were a terrifying threat.

After the dark vortex vanished, a huge clear hole appeared in the sky, but soon, the wind scythe birds flooded in like a tide, covering up the hole again. Above the alliance army, there were countless wind scythe birds again.

This was the twenty-fifth round of the sixty-eighth floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The numbers of wind scythe birds were too great, among them were large numbers of bird kings, their assault was too powerful.

Actually, according to their experiences, they knew there had to be an easier way to challenge this round, but Hei Lou Lan directly charged in and mobilized all his strength to overwhelm the birds.

This attracted the revenge and counterattack of the frenzied wind scythe birds.

"Hahaha, kill all these damn birds!" At one side, Ye Lui Sang laughed. Hei Lou Lan's explosive strength triggered his fighting spirit.

Ye Lui tribe was on the same level as Hei tribe, they were both super forces, having Gu Immortals backing them. Ye Lui Sang and Hei Lou Lan had the same status, they were both the tribe leader of their respective super tribes.

When he saw Hei Lou Lan's killer move that killed countless wind scythe birds, he was not willing to hold back anymore.

"Look at my newly developed killer move — Flame Demon!"

Ye Lui Sang shouted loudly as his sleeves fluttered, and his primeval essence rushed into the Gu worms in his hands.

With a loud thud, his body was clad in flames as the flames burst out, all Gu Masters near him moved away.

Within the radius of a few hundred steps, he was the only person left.

His body trembled and the flames that could rise to heaven split to form a ten metre bronze ape that was completely made of flames.

The flaming bronze ape had an ugly appearance, with teeth like a gorilla, strange horns and bulging muscles. This was the flame demon!

The flame demon rose into the sky, crashing around as all the wind scythe birds that collided with it were ignited, screaming from being burnt alive.

Along its path, flames were burning, causing a straight line of them to form in the sky. Large numbers of wind scythe birds were roasted, falling to the ground.

The flame demon rampaged arrogantly, attracting the attention of many birds, it greatly reduced the pressure of the Gu Masters in the grand army.

"What fire demon, it is nothing much!" Far away, Hei Lou Lan laughed loudly, showing his smug arrogance.

Ye Lui Sang laughed as well: "Hei tribe leader, take another look!"

In saying this, his body shook as the flames fell off him, forming another flame demon.

Hei Lou Lan's expression changed, not just him, even Fang Yuan who was in the army took a serious look. The flame demon had great strength, but to think he had more than one.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building gave lots of opportunities, it was not just Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan who were improving, other Gu Masters were gaining many rewards as well.

When six flame demons entered the battlefield, the flames on Ye Lui Sang were finally extinguished.

"Six flame demons, thankfully..." Fang Yuan retracted his gaze.

Hei Lou Lan's expression soothed as well.

Ye Lui Sang had true capability, this killer move was really extraordinary, but that was as far as it got. In terms of power, it could only be on par with dark vortex.

The flame demons rampaged for an hour as their strength fell more and more, eventually perishing among the wind scythe birds.

But soon after, Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Xi Xue, Pei Yan Fei, Tao You, Gu Guo Long and others attacked, using all their killer moves. The great strength of rank five experts quickly changed the battlefield, tilting the scales of victory towards the alliance army.

Eventually, they succeeded, getting into the twenty-sixth round.

"Reporting to lord tribe leader, thirteen tribe leaders have submitted a letter of request, they are asking for a temporarily halt of advancement. They are worried about the huge casualties, they need to rest and recover." Before Hei Lou Lan had finished probing this round, his attendant Hei Shu had already reported.

Hei Lou Lan frowned immediately, shouting: "Begrudging already despite such few casualties! These useless bums, they are all useless cowards! Return this request to them, and tell them we will advance no matter what. Whoever dares to escape or run away from the alliance army will have their entire tribe and any related tribes executed, none will be spared!"

Saying so, he held the letter in his hand and tore it into pieces immediately.

"Continue advancing, charge!" Hei Lou Lan waved his hand, shouting as he commanded the army.

He was anxious.

These days, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would emit a strange tremor every few days.

Coupled with the disappearance of the owner token, Hei Lou Lan felt that this was not a simple matter, his instincts were telling him that something unthinkable was about to happen.

To avoid any accidents in the future, he had to quickly get the strength path Immortal Gu now. Only after advancing to a Gu Immortal would he have the strength to control this changing situation.

The challenge this time lasted until the twenty-eighth round. Only after everyone was unable to continue and the casualties were too heavy did Hei Lou Lan have no choice but to retreat and recuperate.

　　...

In his room, Tai Bai Yun Sheng showed a bitter smile as he held several east window Gu in his hand.

These east window Gu contained the cultivation experience of previous generation Gu Masters, among them, most were time path attainment!

These were all the round rewards obtained from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"Don't tell me, this is the arrangement of destiny, for me to advance to Gu Immortal realm?"

Back then, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had failed in searching for a lifespan Gu, after wasting all his life's savings, he had to become Hei tribe's external elder.

He was a time path Gu master, rank five peak stage, with his sensitivity towards time he knew that he had little time left since a few years ago.

Although advancing to Gu Immortal realm could allow a Gu Master's life to improve qualitatively, it could not increase his lifespan. But Tai Bai Yun Sheng's situation was a little special.

His time path inheritance was extraordinary, it was a Gu immortal inheritance.

The core of his inheritance had three Gu, river as before Gu, mountain as before Gu, and man as before Gu.

The inheritance has theorized long ago: When he becomes an immortal, using the supreme opportunity of the resonance of heaven and earth, he could advance his man as before Gu into an Immortal Gu.

The mortal man as before Gu could only be used on others.

Immortal Gu Man As Before, could be used on himself.

"If I have the man as before Immortal Gu, I can use it on myself and extend my lifespan. Unfortunately, man as before is not like the Spring Autumn Cicada, I cannot save Gao Yang and Zhu Zai. Sigh..."

Thinking of this, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart was worried, the intense regret and guilt assaulted him once again.

　　...

Fang Yuan stood at the peak of the tall tower, looking at Hei tribe.

Luck inspection Gu had been activated for a while, it gave him a different field of vision from others.

This rank five mortal Gu was the sole, unexpected gain that he obtained inside the true inheritance secluded domain.

Luck inspection, as the name suggests, could be used to inspect luck. It was an investigative Gu worm.

In his vision, in the living quarters of Hei tribe, there were countless smoke-like luck strands. But among them, two were extremely thick, like cranes among chickens, even the palace's rooms could not hide them.

One came from Hei Lou Lan, his luck was like a huge pillar, with an azure color, it was thick and long. The other came from Tai Bai Yun Sheng, his luck was like the flames burning during sunset, red and bright, it accumulated above the roof of his house, it was like the feeling of dazzling flames.

"The luck of these two are extremely high, but they are different. Hei Lou Lan's luck has a lasting feeling. Tai Bai Yun Sheng's luck is like a pile of old firewood, burning at the last moment. In recent days, I secretly manipulated the rewards and placed many time path attainment experiences as rewards to give them to Tai Bai Yun Sheng. Every time he gets one, the firey red luck above him turns brighter by a bit. The possibility of becoming an immortal also increased slightly."

Fang Yuan thought about it for a long time, he sighed in his heart when he thought about the mysterious and unfathomable luck path.

But he had only obtained a single luck inspection Gu, he did not know the details of the inheritance, it was like opening a new window, towards this new path, he could only explore it slowly.

He used the luck inspection Gu on himself.

Fang Yuan's body was shrouded in black ink-like luck. This luck gathered and formed a huge coffin shape, completely covering his body, they were emitting a dense death energy, the energy of great misfortune.

Even though Fang Yuan had looked at this many times, his heart always sank when he observed this.

"My luck is not looking optimistic. But these days, all my talks with the Imperial Court land spirit have had no progress. This land spirit is too arrogant, it only wants to break the seal and regain its freedom. True Yang Building has already shaken thirty-eight times, eventually, Giant Sun's will would awaken."

"Eh?" Fang Yuan gasped, he looked at a group of Gu Masters, they were all shrouded in a black coffin-like luck, heading in the direction of Hei tribe.

A moment later, they all entered Tai Bai Yun Sheng's residence.

Fang Yuan thought about briefly before understanding their intentions.

"This is a good opportunity for me to understand the meaning of this black coffin luck." Fang Yuan's gaze was dark, he gave a deep glance towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng's location.

Chapter 605: Pitiful Person (Double chapter)

"We implore you to help us, old sir Tai Bai!"

"I am sincerely asking old sir to go forward and plead for us."

"The whole of my tribe, our elderly, the weak, the women and children too, the future of all of our tribesmen are in lord's hands..."

In the room, a group of Gu Masters were kneeling on the ground, crying profusely or showing a sad expression, they were desperately asking Tai Bai Yun Sheng for help.

These Gu Masters had rather special identities, they were all the tribe leaders of their respective tribes.

Lou tribe, Lu tribe, Xi tribe... all of these tribes were middle sized tribes or small sized tribes, during the process of challenging Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, they suffered the greatest numbers of casualties, if this were to continue, they might face the threat of being wiped out for good.

The previous few times, they had as a group written letters of request, asking to retreat, but they were all harshly rejected by Hei Lou Lan.

Survival was the number one priority.

Hei Lou Lan's oppressive and all out tactics had already severely harmed the survival and development of these small and middle sized tribes.

But because of the Black Tyrant's fierce reputation, these tribe leaders did not dare to approach Hei Lou Lan himself. After discussing among themselves, they decided to jointly approach Tai Bai Yun Sheng for help.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was the current number one healing master in all of northern plains, he was well known to be kind and merciful, his reputation in northern plains was second to none. Now that he had become Hei tribe's external elder, he was greatly trusted and depended on by Hei Lou Lan.

If they could obtain Tai Bai Yun Sheng's help, their respective tribes might very well gain the precious time to rest and recuperate.

"Please get up and speak." Tai Bai Yun Sheng urged them.

"Old sir, if you do not accept our request, we will not get up!"

"Please go take a look at our tribes, you will understand our pain and grief then. Our injuries and casualties are simply too great, our women have lost their husbands, our children have lost their parents, and our elderly have lost their children..."

"Old sir, please go and talk to Lord Hei Lou Lan, if this carries on, our tribe is going to perish for good."

"Hmph, we did not die in the Imperial Court contest, but instead, we are facing extermination within Imperial Court blessed land, if word gets out, where would Hei tribe's reputation go to? This is simply too ironic!"

The tribe leaders talked one after another, they held a firm attitude and refused to get up from the kneeling position.

"Sigh..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng heaved a long sigh, he had already been very unhappy with Hei Lou Lan's actions to begin with.

There was enough time to go about this slowly, why did he have to be so anxious and rush their advancement?

Causing such grave and severe casualties, he could not bear to see this in his heart.

From Tai Bai Yun Sheng's perspective: Most likely, losing the owner token during the challenge of the second round had triggered Hei Lou Lan. Another reason was that the supreme elders of Hei tribe were pressuring him greatly. Because of this pressure, Hei Lou Lan had no choice but to give it his all in challenging the rounds.

"My servants, quickly come and serve tea to the tribe leaders." Tai Bai Yun Sheng instructed his servants.

He next turned around and consoled the band of tribe leaders: "This old man will do his best to talk to tribe leader Hei Lou Lan, but all I can say is, I will try my best."

"Old sir, you are truly a kind person, you are so benevolent."

"Gaining old sir's help, it is truly our tribe's greatest fortune!"

"Old sir, this is a letter of request that we have written collectively, we will be waiting for old sir's good news patiently."

All the tribe leaders were filled with gratitude and joy.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng received the letter of request from them and kept it in his pocket, after bidding farewell to the tribe leaders, he came to the grand hall and looked for Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was not settling the administrative matters of the army in the grand hall, instead, he was relaxing in the flower garden.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng hurried over quickly and when he saw Hei Lou Lan, the latter was playing chess in the lake pavilion.

Hei Lou Lan heard his intentions and first rejected him strictly, but when Tai Bai Yun Sheng urged him with reasoning and kind words, Hei Lou Lan slowly became less strict as he said: "How about this, I can let these tribes rest and recover temporarily, but they must lend out all of their Gu worms. My army will continue to advance, but we cannot reduce our strength just because of their absence! Every Gu worm that they lend will entitle them to one person who can rest, rank two Gu worm will exempt a rank two Gu Master. A rank three Gu worm will exempt a rank three Gu Master, and so on."

"Lord tribe leader is wise and merciful, I will thank tribe leader for his magnanimity on behalf of all the different tribes and their tribesmen." Tai Bai Yun Sheng knew this was the best result he could get, thus he returned and informed all of the tribe leaders about this result.

The tribe leaders looked at each other as they pondered over this, eventually accepting this condition.

Gu worms were the foundation and base of a Gu Master. Gu worms that were lent out were easy to get damaged, but it was much better than losing their own lives.

The casualties that these tribes were facing were simply too severe.

The next day, Hei Lou Lan ordered the black banner army to go to the respective tribes' resting area and collect their Gu worms, being late was not an option. He also sent Tai Bai Yun Sheng to control the situation and settle the relevant administrative matters.

After three days, this matter was finally settled.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng returned and reported to Hei Lou Lan, who invited him to a banquet.

During the banquet, Hei Lou Lan lifted his wine cup as he said: "Old sir, please have a drink! It was our great fortune that old sir joined our tribe, allowing the army to face much fewer casualties and injuries. Old sir, you revived countless people, you have accomplished great deeds."

"I am not worthy of such praise, but we have to try our very best at things, whether we succeed or not is up to heaven. With Longevity Heaven watching us, we can only do our best." Tai Bai Yun Sheng showed a look of shame, replying as he raised his cup. Hei Lou Lan's praise reminded him of Gao Yang and Zhu Zai.

In truth, every since he returned from the blood hall, every word of praise that he heard felt like an insult, like sarcastic comments that were whipping at his soul.

But today, after settling this matter, he resolved the conflict between Hei tribe and many small and middle sized tribes, in a way, he saved the lives of many Gu Masters.

This made him feel slightly better.

"With Longevity Heaven watching us, we can only do our best..." Hei Lou Lan drank his wine in one gulp, putting it down as he muttered, sighing: "Old sir's words are very accurate and articulate, it is truly well said. Longevity Heaven is watching us, the road to the future is filled with mystery and unexpected circumstances, as mortals, we can only do our best. Elder Tai Bai had already done his best, I, Hei Lou Lan, should do the same as well!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard this and suddenly felt that Hei Lou Lan had some additional meaning in his words, he immediately asked: "Lord tribe leader, what do you mean by that?"

Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily, he was about to speak when Hei Shu came in with a report.

His body was covered in blood, his expression was respectful and cautious, he came to Hei Lou Lan's side and said: "Reporting to lord tribe leader, the black banner army has not failed your expectations, we have already settled it appropriately."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt the killing aura around him and had a very ominous feeling, he quickly asked: "What do you mean by settled it appropriately? Hei Shu! What did you guys settle?"

Hei Shu did not speak, he raised his eyebrows as he gave Tai Bai Yun Sheng a passing glance, showing disdain in his eyes towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng's compassionate and benevolent attitude.

"Hahaha, elder Tai Bai! It is exactly like what you said — we can only do our best! You are doing your best, and I am doing the same! I have to do all I can to break through the rounds, and accomplish the mission given to me by the supreme elder. Tell me, these people ran away in the middle of our task, what crimes have they committed? They were able to develop to this extent because they relied on me. Taking advantages when they can, and hiding when there is trouble, is there such an easy and simple thing in this world? Hmph! If everyone was like that, would my army need to exist anymore? Will there be anyone left who would challenge the rounds with me?" Hei Lou Lan said this with a sharp and resolute tone, his eyes were shining with a ruthless light.

Saying this, there was no need to mention what the task given to the black banner army was!

"Hei Lou Lan, you!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng stood up in a flash.

He stared at Hei Lou Lan with a furious gaze, he showed shock, anger, and even hatred on his face.

"Insolent!" Hei Shu was unhappy and was about to strike, but Hei Lou Lan stretched out his hand and stopped him.

"Elder Tai Bai, do not forget your current status." Hei Lou Lan kept away his ruthless expression and poured another cup of wine indifferently.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng clenched his fists, his body was shivering from pure anger.

He stared at Hei Lou Lan fixatedly, he wanted to scold him, but no sound came out of his mouth.

Hei Lou Lan chuckled, pouring a cup of wine for Tai Bai Yun Sheng personally: "Old sir, take a seat, such beautiful and relaxing scenery paired with good wine and food, we should not let it go to waste."

"Screw your good wine and food!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng swept his sleeves furiously, with a loud crash, all the wine cups fell onto the floor.

Hei Lou Lan was unmoved, instead he pointed at the dishes on the table as he laughed loudly: "Elder Tai Bai, this is a banquet to celebrate your success. If not for your support, why would they trust us so much and lend out their Gu? As they did not have their Gu worms with them, my black banner army could quickly swoop in and take them down, easily obliterating them. I have no one but you to thank for this."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard this and felt like lightning had struck him, he staggered three steps back as his face turned completely pale as paper.

"Hei Lou Lan, you are really an unscrupulous scoundrel!"

"Unscrupulous? I cannot believe this, you are saying such naive things? Elder Tai Bai, you were also once the young tribe leader of a tribe, after living for so many years, have you not seen the reality of this world? These so called political affairs have always been dirty."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to rebuke him, but there were no words he could say.

He snorted coldly, turning around and leaving, walking out of the hall quickly without even turning back once.

"Lord tribe leader, should I send people to surveil Tai Bai Yun Sheng?" Hei Shu inquired.

Hei Lou Lan raised his wine cup, his expression was plain, without a bit of nervousness. He glanced at Tai Bai Yun Sheng's back as he laughed coldly: "Tai Bai Yun Sheng is merely a healing Gu Master, what's there to be afraid of? His reputation? Hehe, after this matter, who would dare believe in him again? Good deeds go unnoticed, while bad deeds travel a thousand li..."

Hei Shu heard this and his heart jumped: "Anyone who holds a high political position is an unfathomable schemer indeed!"

At this point, he could see that Hei Lou Lan's actions were killing three birds with one stone.

Firstly, by causing bloodshed in these small and middle tribes, he was creating an example to show the others. Secondly, he could suppress Tai Bai Yun Sheng, making him understand what status he is currently holding. Thirdly, it is to attack Tai Bai Yun Sheng's reputation, in order to strengthen his own political power.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng walked quickly towards the scene of the incident.

The slaughter had ended, in order to create more fear in people, Hei Lou Lan did not order his men to clean up the area.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked around, his expression turning white, and his heart was shivering.

The sacred palace was dyed in blood, corpses were everywhere on the ground.

Not just strong adult men, there were even the old, the weak, women and children. Some of them had their eyes wide open, dying an indignant death; some of them had their arms and legs chopped off, some were cut in half, it was a gruesome sight; some had messy clothing, their expressions were twisted and in agony, it was evident that they had been humiliated in an inhuman way before they died...

All of this... all of this...

"It was all caused by me. If not for me trusting Hei Lou Lan, if not for me trying to mediate the tension between the two... I was too foolish, I was too naive! I did not manage to see Hei Lou Lan's ugly and evil intentions! All these people, they all died because they placed their trust in me!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's body was shivering, the intense smell of blood was assaulting him, and the scene of a sea of corpses lying on the ground was causing a huge impact on his fragile state of mind.

His back was hunched, the mild wind blew at him and caused his beard to move slightly, he had deep wrinkles and a dazed expression, his fists were tightly clenched, soundlessly expressing the grief, agony, regret, and self blame that he was feeling deep in his heart!

Plop.

He kneeled on the ground weakly, holding himself up with his hands as the blood dyed his palms, his knees, and his pants bright red.

"Sorry, I am sorry..."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wept profusely, at once, his face was like an overflowing river.

"This is a good person... even though there is also darkness in his heart, in the end, there is great terror when one is between life and death. Facing death, which normal person would not lose themselves?" Far away, at a hidden corner, Fang Yuan had been observing this intently and silently.

He watched the scene unfold with his very own eyes.

It turned out that the black coffin luck represented a severe disaster that would threaten his life. The extermination of these tribes was the best proof of that.

Meanwhile, the death energy on his body was more than dozens of times thicker than these tribes' members, even a hundred times as thick!

"Hehe, this is so interesting. Luck huh..." Fang Yuan's lips curled into a cold and arrogant smile, he wanted to see if this so called bad luck could stop him in his steps.

"In this life, there is no person, any reason, or any difficulties that can affect my determination in moving forward!" His gaze was cold and still as ice, looking towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Who said that kind people will be rewarded?" Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's cold expression turned into one that had a trace of sarcasm: "Then let me give you a hand."

He activated his Gu worms in secret, forming an illusory voice that was untraceable, as the soundwaves entered Tai Bai Yun Sheng's ears one by one.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's state of mind was close to collapsing, his mind was extremely susceptible to influences.

At this moment, he could hear a voice, it sounded just like Gao Yang and Zhu Zai.

"I believe in you! You will definitely save us, isn't that right?"

"Old sir, you are our benefactor. We are grateful to you, we are willing to risk our lives in order to come forward and help you!"

"Ah!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng screamed suddenly, opening his eyes abruptly.

With his blurred vision due to his tears, he looked at the blood puddle on the ground.

The blood puddle rippled, as the nightmare that haunted him appeared once again, the image of Gao Yang and Zhu Zai dying from the sea of blood beasts!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's body shuddered, he was still like a statue, but the next moment, he raised his head and screamed with all of his energy.

"AHHHHHHHHHH!"

His shrill and hoarse voice resounded in this bloody slaughterhouse.

"Hehehe, hihihi, hahaha!"

When his screaming ended, Tai Bai Yun Sheng started laughing like a maniac.

His laughter contained the feeling of madness, but also anger and sadness, there was also a trace of mockery towards himself, towards the mortal world.

"Crazy? He's crazy!"

"Elder Tai Bai has gone mad!!"

The surrounding Hei tribe Gu Masters were shouting in shock.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan was curling his lips and smiling, he was a transmigrator, and had also undergone rebirth, his rich life experience had allowed him to grasp the psychology of people to a very precise degree.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a very good person.

But his subconscious action in the blood hall was akin to betrayal.

This action created suspicion, doubts, and denial that he felt towards himself in terms of his personal values.

If a person denied himself, and suspected himself, then he would no doubt fall into a deep abyss of agony.

Very evidently, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was in great pain, he felt guilt in his heart, almost every night, he was tormented by a similar nightmare.

For him to accept that he had some kind of despicable and lowly character as a fact, it would be impossible to do so. His entire life revolved around justice and benevolence, he had walked on this road for too long, he wanted to return to it, but he knew that in the deepest part of his heart, this action formed a barrier that he could not cross.

He was stuck in the abyss of agony, sinking deeper and deeper the more he struggled.

The tribe leaders' request towards him was a chance that he had towards salvation, and a redemption for his mistakes.

If he could really succeed, it was undeniably the best medicine for him to pay for his sins, and he would be able to forgive himself.

But the truth was, Hei Lou Lan ordered a mass slaughter, not leaving even a single woman or child behind. This in turn caused Tai Bai Yun Sheng to become the biggest assistant in this murder spree.

His medicine turned into a heart piercing poison, the intense toxins caused him to lose himself, his mental state was close to breaking down.

At this juncture, Fang Yuan pushed him lightly, finally causing Tai Bai Yun Sheng to explode, breaking from the deepest part of his heart.

Perhaps only Fang Yuan could understand him at this point.

To put it in another way, after searching through his soul, Fang Yuan, who had seen Tai Bai Yun Sheng's entire life, could be said to know him intimately.

But the cruel reality was, this person was not his kin or his friend, he was an enemy plotting against him.

Fang Yuan, who was hidden in the darkness listening to Tai Bai Yun Sheng's laughter, looked on with an expression of appreciation, smiling lightly.

This was a respectable and pitiful old man, he screamed his lungs out, in his laughter, on his face full of tears, he was questioning himself, he was questioning the cruelty of this mortal world, fate was toying with him and he was helpless to resist.

"If you deny even yourself, what can you do?" Fang Yuan muttered lightly, his gaze was as deep as night.

"Go to the blood hall again and try to challenge the round? No, if you are there, your mind will be full of Gao Yang and Zhu Zai's images. Go seek help? Who can help you now? Hei Lou Lan? It can be assumed that you have just fallen out with him. Or rather, even if you manage to get the lifespan Gu, will you be able to use it with peace of mind?"

"Hehe, the current you, what options do you possibly have? What choices can you still make? Denying yourself, wallowing in self pity, feeling intense pain and grief, you, a person who is facing a trial of your conscience, what option do you have?"

In Fang Yuan's heart, an answer was becoming clearer.

"Thus, go ahead and make your decision, I hope you will not let me down!" In the darkness, Fang Yuan's gaze was shining as he looked at the crazy Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was laughing wildly, his voice was bitter like he was wailing.

He tore his clothes, as tears and mucus were mixing on his face, he did not have the demeanour of a rank five peak state expert at this point.

He was someone who feared death, but he was also a good person who was pushed into a corner by this cruel and ice cold mortal world.

In truth, he was more like a —

Pitiful person.

Since some time ago, a mild wind had started blowing.

The wind gradually grew bigger and bigger, as clouds were forming in the sky.

With Tai Bai Yun Sheng as the center, the surroundings were quietly and rapidly transforming

Some sort of mystical change had started, heaven and earth were beginning to tremble.

"You did not disappoint me in the end..." Fang Yuan was extremely excited, he took his leave and vanished without a trace.

He rapidly travelled far away, retreating.

Because...

It was no joke when a Gu Master advances into an immortal.

Soon, the wind and clouds went wild, as heaven and earth changed!

The dark and thick black clouds looked like they were about to collapse at any time, destroying the sacred palace.

In and out of the sacred palace, shouting could be heard everywhere.

"What is going on?"

"What in the world is happening?!"

Countless people did not know what was happening, they fell into a panic.

"This... could it be?!" Some people with greater knowledge and experience stared at this grand scene with a dumbfounded expression.

"Go investigate, go investigate! Who is it?!" In the hall, Hei Lou Lan was furiously screaming.

"Lord, it is Tai Bai Yun Sheng!" Hei Shu was full of sweat as he stumbled his way into the hall and reported this.

Hei Lou Lan's expression froze, he was as still as a statue for a moment.

A few breaths later, he reacted and shouted with a twisted expression: "Retreat! Order everyone to leave the sacred palace. Of course, those who wish to die can stay here!"

Chapter 606: Awakening

The sky turned dark and gloomy, and the wind howled.

A formless heavenly power slowly lifted Tai Bai Yun Sheng into the air.

He laughed maniacally, his white beard fluttering in the wind. There were no signs of the usual warmth and benevolence on his face, it was replaced by a crazed and distorted look.

Everyone in the sacred palace was in panic; Gu Masters fled in a hurry, forming a huge stream of people that was fleeing for life towards the outside.

Only after running an immense distance, did the crowd anxiously stop.

Expert Gu Masters moved toward the peaks of hills or directly flew to the sky, and used investigative Gu worms to observe the scene above the sacred palace with different thoughts going through their minds.

Other Gu Masters also raised their heads to gaze at the floating Tai Bai Yun Sheng with looks of respect, reverence, affection, worry, envy and so on.

The news of Tai Bai Yun Sheng advancing to Gu Immortal had already spread amongst everyone.

Advancing to Gu Immortal!

This was something that most people would not experience in their whole life, and unexpectedly it was happening before everyone's eyes at this very moment.

"Inconceivable, Tai Bai Yun Sheng has yet to use any Gu worms but he actually caused such a change in weather!" Looking at the surging clouds and hearing the raging winds, many Gu Masters shouted out in surprise.

Soon the surprised voices surged into a commotion.

Because it was not only the weather that had changed, even the ground under their feet was beginning to shake.

At first, it was only a negligible tremor, but soon vast smoke and dust started to rise from the ground.

"This is the turbulence of earth qi!"

"According to the records in the tribe, Gu Masters have to first break their aperture to advance to Gu Immortal! After breaking their aperture, they can attract heaven qi and earth qi!"

Ye Lui Sang, Hei Lou Lan and some others were from super tribes, and knew a lot more than normal people. At this moment, shock could clearly be seen in their eyes.

The first step in advancing to Gu Immortal was breaking the aperture.

Using primeval essence in an all-out assault to completely shatter one's own aperture. Like this, the sealed aperture that was covered by the crystal wall would turn into a hole in the Gu Master's body.

"Just this first step needs extremely great courage. Because there is no turning back after shattering the aperture." Gu tribe leader Gu Guo Long said with a sigh.

"Advancement to a Gu Immortal is extremely difficult, with miniscule chances of success! Tai Bai Yun Sheng is too courageous, actually daring to take this step. He truly leaves us in admiration." Nie tribe leader Nie Ya Qing was deeply moved.

Hei Lou Lan's expression was complex.

He knew some inside details, a part of the reason why Tai Bai Yun Sheng was advancing to Gu Immortal was probably due to his actions.

"I was the one who provoked Tai Bai Yun Sheng, leading to him choosing to take the risk to advance in his crumbling mental state. This is good, although I learnt about immortal ascension from records, I really want to personally observe it. Tai Bai Yun Sheng's advancement into Gu Immortal will provide a great reference and be helpful to me. It is just that... so be it if he fails, but if he really successfully advances into a Gu Immortal, how should I treat him?"

Hei Lou Lan immediately frowned at this thought, feeling a headache.

Fang Yuan observed the scene while sitting on a back of an azure wolf king, surrounded by an azure wolf group.

"Advancement to Gu Immortal..." His dark gaze had excitement and also showed an expression of recalling the past.

He again used luck inspection Gu to examine Tai Bai Yun Sheng, the luck on him was now like a raging wildfire, originally it had been like flames with a growing red glow. Now, it was even more flourishing, blazing like an inferno!

"His luck is blazing, he had successfully advanced into a Gu Immortal in my previous life, that should not be a big problem for him in this life." Fang Yuan inwardly nodded.

Unlike Hei Lou Lan with his doubts and hesitation, Fang Yuan already had a plan to face the Gu Immortal Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

He tried to look once more, but the luck inspection Gu actually suffered injuries from the extreme pressure.

His own eyes also felt a burning pain.

Fang Yuan immediately stopped the activation, not surprised at all.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had already broken his aperture, attracting heaven and earth qi in a huge surrounding range. Using Gu worms in this range will naturally create chain reactions, making the heaven and earth qi surge and trigger a backlash.

If one was stubborn and forcibly activated their Gu, even an Immortal Gu would be injured and might even die, not to mention mere mortal Gu.

Fang Yuan had not considered using Gu worms at this time to plot against Tai Bai Yun Sheng because of this reason.

If he rashly made a move in this period, he himself might be implicated.

In an instant, the dark clouds in the sky surged, and together took the shape of a giant vortex.

In response to this, yellow-brown dust churned endlessly on the ground, creating a vortex that resembled the formation of a loophole.

"This Tai Bai Yun Sheng has deep foundation and accumulation, his human qi is so majestic, actually attracting so much heaven and earth qi! This scene is actually more spectacular than when my tribe's supreme elder advanced." Ye Lui Sang was endlessly shocked.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had an immortal inheritance and roamed northern plains his whole life, gaining extremely rich experience. By now, he had almost run the course of his entire life, thus his accumulation was incomparably deep.

The two giant vortexes covered miles of range.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng gazed up and saw the majestic and fierce vortex which looked like a giant beast opening its mouth.

In comparison, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's body was small, like a tiny insect near a pond.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng still kept on laughing maniacally.

"Come, come!" He shouted, his body shook with fear and excitement, but also relief. Even if he failed, he would at least be freed from this nightmare.

Seemingly hearing his shout, the brewing vortex began to slowly rotate.

In the sky and on the ground, two giant vortexes rotated like a millstone.

Lightning flashed in the dark and cloudy vortex in the sky, with the thunder rumbling repeatedly. On the ground, the dusty vortex caused purple smoke to ascend with violent explosive sounds.

Like grinding stone, the dark and cloudy millstone sprinkled down a clear and bright aura. While from the dusty one below, rose a golden aura.

They were heaven qi and earth qi!

Heaven qi was clear and moved freely; earth qi was profound and dense.

And Tai Bai Yun Sheng's body released a white human qi.

This human qi was extremely dense and like a cocoon, it formed a large sphere that tightly covered Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Heaven qi was raining down while earth qi was bubbling up, both intertwined in the air with human qi.

Heaven, earth and human, the three qi converged together and began fusing.

"First step is breaking the aperture, the second step is taking in the qi." Hei Lou Lan mumbled.

"Breaking the aperture is a point of no return, the only possibility of survival is in success and failure means certain doom. And taking in qi tests the nature of the Gu Master and their ability to control it. This step is extremely crucial and is like walking between cliffs on a tightrope. If the balance is even a little off such that the human qi is slightly in excess, it will lead to self-detonation! If heaven qi is slightly more, the Gu Master will dissolve into the sky! If earth qi is slightly more dense, the Gu Master will turn into a fossil and suffocate to death! Difficult, truly hard, truly difficult!" Ye Lui Sang lamented while shaking his head, even as a spectator, his heart shook at this sight.

One can only move forward when they begin the advancement to a Gu Immortal, there is no going back. The danger is extremely high, thus many rank five peak stage Gu Masters, even if they knew the method to advance to a Gu Immortal, would not choose to take the risk unless as a last resort.

The expert observes the process while the layman simply enjoys the show.

Most people only watched the sight while bustling with noise and excitement.

But the few expert Gu Masters who knew the inside details were dripping with sweat, their hearts palpitating with fear from the sight.

Fang Yuan was the one with the most experience regarding this.

The process of charging to Gu Immortal realm and becoming a blood path Gu Immortal in his previous life had left behind an extremely deep impression on him.

"This second step is extremely difficult, it not only tests the Gu Master's ability to control the balance, what it tests even more than that is the Gu Master's nature." He inwardly sighed.

Heaven qi and earth qi attacked the body, and the three qi converged; this was the process of a mortal blending with heaven and earth.

An ordinary person would never have such a moment where they are this intimately close to heaven and earth.

Heaven and earth were the cornerstones to nurture all living beings, the resonance between heaven qi and earth qi would fill the Gu Master's mind with the wonders of the Great Dao.

Experiencing the Great Dao was an extremely rare opportunity and the Gu Master could easily lose themselves in it, not being able to extricate themselves. This could very easily lead to an imbalance between the three qi.

Even more crucially —

The higher the amount of heaven qi and earth qi taken in, the higher the chance of advancing to a Gu Immortal. At this crucial time, the Gu Master would often get greedy and take in too much heaven qi and earth qi, leading to an imbalance between the three qi and perishing.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not disappoint Fang Yuan, he persevered and stabilized the situation, controlling the three qi perfectly and progressing slowly.

"This Tai Bai Yun Sheng probably received an expert's guidance!"

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng actually accomplished it, the second step could not stump him at all. This man really is not simple..."

"We need to keep on watching. Being able to do it now does not mean he can maintain the state until the end."

Hei Lou Lan and Ye Lui Sang were feeling bewildered.

Rumble!

Right at this time, a change occurred.

As the aurora in the sky shook, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building experienced intense tremors. As its cornerstone, the sacred palace started shaking as well, dust rose and many beautiful courtyards collapsed.

"What is going on?"

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

Everyone shifted their gazes in shock.

"Hmph, it is here." Fang Yuan sneered, but was well aware of this.

Inside the True Yang Building, the land spirit was furious!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng advancing to a Gu Immortal meant he was taking in heaven qi and earth qi. But this world was not the outside world of northern plains, but was Imperial Court blessed land, a small world of its own.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was using up this small world's heaven qi and earth qi which was akin to weakening Imperial Court blessed land and was basically extracting the source of the land spirit's strength.

Could the land spirit not be angry?

It had been imprisoned for countless years and now finally had the hope of obtaining freedom.

Although it was formed from an obsession and did not know how to tell lies, but it had intelligence and understood the strategy of concealing itself.

The land spirit had originally planned to restrain itself, fearing Giant Sun's will. It would wait till Gruel Mud had corroded the shackles on it to a certain degree before it broke out in one violent move.

But now that Tai Bai Yun Sheng was charging into Gu Immortal realm, he was not only extracting the strength of the land spirit, but was sure to awaken Giant Sun's will! The land spirit would then have all its hopes dashed.

Even more likely, it would be forcibly suppressed by Giant Sun's will again.

With no choice, it could only make a quick decision and take advantage of Giant Sun's will still being in hibernation at the moment, to resist and avoid giving Giant Sun's will time to be prepared!

Thus, everyone looked on as the True Yang Building shook, bringing destruction to the fish in the ponds as many structures in the sacred palace collapsed.

In the True Yang Building, the land spirit Frost Jade Peacock let out a loud cry.

Its attack was extremely effective as the green paste covering its body immediately melted until below its neck and five to six black chains on its body also broke!

"Huh?"

A light mumble, as if just waking up from a dream, echoed out from the depths of the True Yang Building.

"Who has such guts to awaken me from my slumber?" From the infinite and eerie darkness, a giant will resembling the sun slowly woke up.

It was originally only a small glimmer, but soon brightened up to the extent that it could pierce through ten layers of the underworld, sweeping past every corner of the True Yang Building.

Fang Yuan's will that had refined the guest halt stele simply could not defend itself and was immediately wiped out. The glass owner token he held also started becoming boiling hot!

Chapter 607: Ambushing Giant Sun’s will

A will blazing like the sun passed through the glass owner token and attacked Fang Yuan's mind.

The will was like a golden flood as it rampaged directly into Fang Yuan's brain!

Will was formed from large numbers of specific thoughts, if Giant Sun's will was allowed to erode his mind, Fang Yuan could very likely turn into a demented amnesiac.

"This is bad! Quickly throw away that damned owner token!!" Mo Yao's will appeared in his mind, and screamed.

She was the will of a Gu Immortal who had reached rank seven before death; her background knowledge of will was much deeper than Fang Yuan's.

Her own gains and losses were linked to Fang Yuan, like two locusts tied with a thread.

The mind was a vital place, Fang Yuan would not want to start a battle in there.

"No need to worry." he sneered. He was already prepared so he was not concerned, soon activating the special will Gu.

The special will Gu received the primeval essence and directly flashed into Fang Yuan's mind, blocking the will of Giant Sun.

The golden-like will came to an abrupt stop, completely halted by special will Gu!

The special will Gu then burst out with a strong absorption force, devouring Giant Sun's will unceasingly. The small will swallowed the big will, as if an ant swallowing an elephant, but Giant Sun's will had no ability to resist.

"This is..." Mo Yao's will was stumped for a while before coming to a realization, "So Giant Sun's will was a special will!"

Wisdom path had developed for a long time since its start at the Remote Antiquity Era, continuing to this day.

Will was classified under wisdom path and naturally the contents regarding it were plentiful. Not only was will divided into many types, there were also all sorts of effects.

Back when Fang Yuan had just ventured into it, he had already bought many wisdom path Gu worms. For example, special will Gu, deliberate will Gu, play will Gu, keep will Gu and new will Gu which were specially used to condense special will, deliberate will, play will, keep will and new will.

These five types of will had their advantages and disadvantages, requiring the Gu Master themselves to choose the appropriate will according to the situation.

Among them, special will could be arranged in advance and automatically trigger under special conditions.

To explain this in a simple fashion, let's take a rat trap as an example. When a rat comes in contact with the trap (fulfilling the special condition), the rat trap will then activate, trapping the rat (the prior setup is triggered, activating the trap).

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable considered dangerous situations occurring in the future, and for the benefit of his descendants, he chose to use the most suitable special will Gu to create a will of himself and placed it in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

As long as the danger reached a certain degree, the special condition would be fulfilled and the special will would trigger Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's prior setup. As for what the activation requirement of this prior setup was, outsiders did not know. Even Fang Yuan who had been reborn was not clear about it.

But from the video clips in his previous life, he knew Giant Sun's will was a special will.

Knowing this made it easier for Fang Yuan.

Giant Sun's will was an Immortal Venerable's will, but it must also follow the laws and Great Dao of the world. The will was condensed by a Gu worm, and similarly could be subdued by the corresponding Gu worm.

Thus, Giant Sun's special will was greatly restrained by special will Gu. Within Fang Yuan's mind, Giant Sun's will had yet to show its might before it was swallowed by Fang Yuan's special will Gu.

After swallowing this will of Giant Sun, special will Gu's belly immediately bulged like a fatty who had stuffed himself to the limit.

"Haha, what a great will." Fang Yuan praised it but was inwardly shocked, 'That was dangerous! Although it was restrained, it was after all an Immortal Venerable's will. Even if it was only a strand, it was really not easy to deal with!"

The glass owner token was a part of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Giant Sun's will attacked Fang Yuan through this owner token. But if the owner token was compared to a passage, this passage was way too small and could only allow a strand of Giant Sun's will to pass.

If the passage was just a bit bigger, the situation would be completely different.

This strand of will that special will Gu had eaten was simply negligible compared to the Giant Sun's will in True Yang Building.

Falling prey to Fang Yuan's small scheme, Giant Sun's will could not contain its anger: "Swindler, you dared profane my, Giant Sun's, honor! I will crush you to pieces!"

Rumble!

True Yang Building started shaking, giving off all kinds of lights which infused the sky, a peerless power seemed to manifest, shaking heaven and earth.

Even though Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already died and was unable to mobilize Eighty-Eight True Yang Building using just his will, but within Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had left behind a large amount of rank nine yellow apricot immortal essence!

Wild Gu could directly absorb the primeval essence in the air, but would lose this ability when they are refined and have to absorb the Gu Master's primeval essence.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was an Immortal Gu House and was under the command of Giant Sun's will, it could activate by absorbing the immortal essence left behind by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable; it was extremely simple and easy, as if it was natural!

"Run!" Looking at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building about to show its power, Mo Yao's will anxiously warned Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was a despicable thief who had refined a part of True Yang Building, and now that Giant Sun's will had awakened, it classified him as an enemy.

Fang Yuan did not have Giant Sun's bloodline, this enmity was too big, Fang Yuan was directly marked down and an unprecedented killing intent was about to befall upon him!

"There's no hurry." Calamity was coming right for him, but Fang Yuan appeared indifferent and relaxed.

He tightly held the glass owner token.

This particular token was not simple!

It was a product created by expending an Immortal Gu using an owner token as the base. It was a crucial key for which central continent's Gu Immortals and several large forces had prepared with meticulous care over thousands of years.

"Still causing trouble after death, hmph, what era are we living in now!" Fang Yuan snorted and with no fear sent a thought through the glass owner token, launching an ambush.

True Yang Building shook intensely, the aurora that filled the sky instantly collapsed by over half. The phantom image that appeared when condensing the floors was like a candle in front of a great wind, as it collapsed and dissipated.

Everything came to an abrupt stop.

In True Yang Building, Giant Sun's will let out a frightening and furious howl as it was besieged and attacked by countless special will Gu.

These special will Gu were the preparation of central continent's Gu Immortals which had been accumulated for thousands of years, a trump card specially arranged to deal with Giant Sun's will.

Giant Sun's will's weakness was thoroughly targeted, like a sheep surrounded by a pack of wolves.

It had immediately wanted to activate Gu worms to massacre these special will Gu.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was an Immortal Gu House, a solidified killer move formed from many Immortal Gu and mortal Gu. Naturally, it had methods to clean up the enemies.

But central continent's Gu Immortals had researched deeply and already calculated this.

Coordinating with special will Gu's attack were other shocking methods, actually sealing all of the yellow apricot immortal essence Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind.

True Yang Building was not able to move without the immortal essence and immediately stopped all actions. Even though Giant Sun's will was seething with rage, it did not have any method to instantly resolve this, thus landing in a predicament.

True Yang Building sank into deathly stillness as Fang Yuan put his mind at rest.

In his previous life, central continent's Gu Immortals relied on this method to slay Giant Sun's will and destroy Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"A pity I am still a mortal and not a Gu Immortal, there is no way for me to reap profits from this." Fang Yuan felt a slight regret.

This was Giant Sun's will, even at its weakest moment, it was not something he could meddle with.

In truth, even if he advanced into a Gu Immortal, with just one Gu Immortal's battle strength, the result would not be good. When the central continent Gu Immortals attacked Imperial Court blessed land, they had altogether eleven Gu Immortals, each of them an elite expert, but even then only three were able to return in triumph.

However, the sacrifices were worth it as they received rich battle spoils.

True Yang Building was a spiritual symbol of northern plains and when it was suddenly destroyed, the whole of northern plains suffered heavy impact, their morale fell to the abyss and they were forced into retreat continually in battles. If not for the Gu Immortal Ma Hong Yun who repeatedly playing a vital role as a pillar during the most crucial times, northern plains would have already been annexed by central continent.

As for the current Fang Yuan, he was safe for at least a period of time.

"What happened to True Yang Building just now?"

"Could it be the influence of Tai Bai Yun Sheng advancing to a Gu Immortal was too big and even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was affected?"

"Imperial Court blessed land prohibits the entry of Gu Immortals, advancing to a Gu Immortal here like Tai Bai Yun Sheng is an extremely rare event. Does this violate the arrangements made by old ancestor Giant Sun back then?"

True Yang Building's abnormal changes caused this crowd of people who did not know the truth to be bewildered and start making guesses.

True Yang Building fell into a deathly stillness and did not show any movement for the moment. Soon, everyone's gazes were attracted towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng again.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was floating in between the sky and the ground, continually taking in heaven qi and earth qi, combining them with his own human qi.

The balanced three qi were pouring into the space where his aperture had once been.

An extremely mysterious transformation was happening to his body.

Whether it was his physical body or soul, they were both being tempered by heaven and earth qi. The essence of his life itself was elevating to a higher level.

There were three steps in advancing to a Gu Immortal; the first was breaking the aperture, the second was taking in the qi.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had an intact Gu Immortal inheritance and thus had a clear understanding of the key concerns in the process. So far, he was able to stabilize with no major hindrances.

But how could advancing to a Gu Immortal only have these obstacles?

Compared to the majestic heaven qi and the vast earth qi, human qi originated from only Tai Bai Yun Sheng himself.

Thus, there were endless amounts of heaven qi and earth qi, but human qi was limited in quantity.

The three qi needed to be in balance, there was no way to take in the surplus heaven qi and earth qi, so they were excluded and left to the side.

As time passed, these heaven and earth qi accumulated in the sky and on the ground, gathering and condensing, the sheer quantity causing a qualitative change.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng had too deep of an accumulation, he was able to draw in so much heaven and earth qi. Now the extra heaven and earth qi are condensing into calamity and tribulation!" Ye Lui Sang's eyes flashed with burning light.

The deeper the accumulation of the Gu Master, the greater the difficulty in advancing to a Gu Immortal. But if they succeeded, their potential future accomplishment would be that much higher.

The risk and profits in this were directly proportional.

Hei Lou Lan watched on tightly without saying a word, putting all his effort in observing and gaining reference.

Heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, how did they form?

The scene in front of them was displaying the whole process before everyone's eyes.

Golden earth qi continued to become denser and the turbid qi condensed into shape, gradually forming a one-horned great tiger. And the green heaven qi condensed into countless giant green willow leaves. Every willow leaf was the size of a boat.

The one-horned great tiger was as large as a hill; it raised its head while crouching down, taking a jumping posture.

The green willow leaves swayed as they spread in the sky, ready to strike.

"This is the earthly calamity lofty tiger and the heavenly tribulation willow wind!" Fang Yuan's gaze flashed with a sharp light.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng stopped his crazed laughter, a grave expression filling his face.

The crowd who were so far from all this could feel the endless power of the earthly calamity and the heavenly tribulation, then what about Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was at the center of this, the target of the earthly calamity and the heavenly tribulation?

The spectating crowd was silent, the atmosphere turning heavy.

Imperial Court land spirit, however, laughed loudly: "The opportunity to break free from my captivity has appeared!"

Chapter 608: Giant Sun’s retaliation

Inside True Yang Building.

The land spirit was using all of its strength to attack the seal on it.

Bang bang bang!

Three soft explosive sounds could be heard consecutively, as three black chains binding it were broken.

The green paste on it had thoroughly melted from its neck and even to the tips of its two wings, revealing the bright and lively feathers.

"Little sparrow, you dare!" Giant Sun's will was bursting with fury.

"Giant Sun, despite being dead, you actually still imprisoned me for hundreds of thousands of years. Today, I will definitely break out of your damn cage!" Frost Jade Peacock let out a shrill scream, similarly furious.

Trapped for so many years, unable to even budge, the suffocation and indignance from being in captivity turned into the strength needed to break its seal.

Giant Sun's will gave a deep shout, the sun like will suddenly flared up, rushing in all directions like a majestic golden flood.

Ten thousand special will Gu were already surrounding him in layers after layers. They were like a dam blocking the flood, which was Giant Sun's will.

Giant Sun's special will was completely restrained by the special will Gu. The whole dam held tight without any cracks, but the situation only lasted for a few breaths of time; the special will Gu had already been swallowing Giant Sun's special will to the limit and started to burst one by one.

Several breaths later, the 'dam' formed by the special will Gu trembled, broke down and shattered apart!

Giant Sun's special will might have been subdued but the size of it was extremely large, having originated from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Even after the wear and tear of over hundreds of thousands of years, this was still not something ten thousand special will Gu could suppress.

Restraint was relative.

Water could extinguish fire, but if the fire was fierce enough, it could directly evaporate the water pouring on it.

Giant Sun's will that was like a sun was extremely grand and large, although there was a lot of consumption when he attacked special will Gu, it was still able to destroy the ten thousand special will Gu in the end.

Without the besiegement of special will Gu, Giant Sun's will was like a tied up prisoner who had broken out of the shackles, and immediately tried to control True Yang Building.

But the next moment, a full fifty thousand special will Gu rushed out and gathered again, forming a new encirclement!

Central continent's Gu Immortals had researched very deeply and would never underestimate Giant Sun's will, thus they had made sufficient preparations. Special will Gu was not an Immortal Gu, its quantity could be piled up.

Giant Sun's will who had just obtained freedom was again sealed off, letting out a furious roar.

He started attacking again, his momentum as vast as a rapidly flowing river, breaking apart the encirclement of special will Gu.

But soon, the third wave of special will Gu surrounded it. The quantity was even more this time, reaching over a hundred thousand!

Central continent's Gu Immortals had spent thousands of years for this; several great super forces had joined hands making large purchases, refining Gu non-stop, and spending an astronomical amount of Gu refinement resources.

They had paid such an astonishing price and now they were all being used by Fang Yuan, displaying extraordinary effects.

Being trapped once again, Giant Sun's will did not shout or roar.

Giant Sun's will was the will of an Immortal Venerable and knew how to think.

When he realized he had fallen into a scheme and the enemy side had made sufficient preparations, he became calm again.

He began to think and soon discovered a flaw in the encirclement!

Although Giant Sun's will was surrounded tightly in all directions by special will Gu with no area neglected, this did not signify there was no flaw in this encirclement.

These special will Gu were refined by Gu Immortals and refined Gu worms were unable to directly absorb the primeval essence from their surroundings, and there was no supply of primeval essence for them in here.

Then, where did the primeval essence used to activate these special will Gu come from?

There were so many special will Gu, and there could even be more, their primeval essence requirement would be gigantic. Giant Sun's will slightly thought over it and realized — what these special will Gu absorbed was not primeval essence but immortal essence!

A bead of the lowest grade rank six green grape immortal essence could convert to what was practically an almost unlimited amount of primeval essence!

Immortal essence was the source of fuel for these special will Gu.

And these immortal essence were concealed very well; clearly, there were other supporting Gu worms coordinating with special will Gu to form an enormous and hidden Gu formation.

"So long as I break their connection with the immortal essence, these special will Gu would not be of much threat." Giant Sun's will soon thought of this method.

However, to break the connection between the special will Gu and the immortal essence, he had to fully grasp this Gu formation first.

Just like how central continent Gu Immortals sealed all the yellow apricot immortal essence left behind by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to suppress Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Giant Sun's will also had a similar idea.

On the spot, Giant Sun's will thought rapidly and soon found over ten clues.

Following these clues and making deductions, the vague structure of the Gu formation began to gradually become clearer.

The land spirit naturally would not sit and wait for its death.

When it had sensed Giant Sun's will being suppressed, it mustered all its strength to break the seals on it.

Gruel Mud had terrifying effectiveness against these seals; the green paste on its body was full of cracks and the edges were rapidly melting down. The black shackles on its wings once again consecutively collapsed and four broke apart.

The land spirit, Frost Jade Peacock, gave a shrill cry, its whole body shook intensely, shaking away most of the green paste on its two wings, shortly afterwards it impatiently unfolded them.

Cold aura permeated out from all over its spotlessly white body as it raised its head high, appearing noble and beautiful. But it had yet to completely unfold its large wings when they were tightly pulled in by the black chains.

Its movement came to a sudden stop, the intense pain making it even more furious.

Although there were only three chains left, they still tightly shackled its freedom.

"Break them!" Frost Jade Peacock suddenly turned around its elegant neck, its sharp brows flickering with terrifying cold light.

"Damn it!" Giant Sun's will who had been thinking intensely, could not help but stop his thoughts as he sensed this situation.

If the land spirit broke his control, then Eighty-Eight True Yang Building could be thrown out from Imperial Court blessed land at any time.

Without Imperial Court blessed land's protection, countless Gu Immortals would start rushing over to loot True Yang Building.

At that time, it would be the case of an army of ants devouring an elephant; even more yellow apricot immortal essence would not be able to stop the consumption from the dauntless advance of countless Gu Immortals.

But Giant Sun's will was powerless to stop the land spirit at this moment.

He had been making several probing attacks while thinking at the same time, and although there were some results and he was able to recover some methods, they were still very limited and were not enough to suppress the situation.

......

At this moment, outside the True Yang Building....

Roar!

Lofty tiger roared and jumped.

The world trembled as the hill sized lofty tiger jumped into the air. Its enormous and malevolent tiger claws slammed towards the insignificant insect-like Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng gave a light shout as he dodged quickly!

The tiger claws could not strike him, but the huge wind force from it was still able to make Tai Bai Yun Sheng feel uncomfortable.

At the same time, the willow winds in the sky fluttered down.

These willow winds were as large as a canoe, and their descent was graceful, resembling falling leaves. But the movement that felt slow was actually fast, and the destructive power contained within them was terrifying.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was bathed with blood, paying close attention to the movements of the willow winds. Previously, he had carelessly come into contact with three willow winds, but just that had already destroyed all the defensive Gu on him.

Right now, when he saw the willow winds falling down, he quickly evaded them.

From the earth, the malevolent tiger pounced up; while from the sky, the willow winds fluttered down one after another. Tai Bai Yun Sheng was already finding it difficult to continue after a while, he was in a sorry state and was facing the danger of losing his life.

"Sigh, it bodes ill for Tai Bai Yun Sheng!"

"His accumulation is very robust, but he has not made sufficient preparations to advance to Gu Immortal."

"Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng, you can do it!"

Even Fang Yuan could not help but feel nervous at this scene: "Is Tai Bai Yun Sheng going to fail in advancing to a Gu Immortal in this life?"

He suddenly had a thought and disregarding the backlash, forcibly activated luck inspection Gu. But the luck on Tai Bai Yun Sheng was still burning and raging like boiling water, and was still blooming.

But the next moment, a quarter of this flaming luck had suddenly dissipated!

"What's going on?" It was the first time Fang Yuan was seeing such a change in luck.

And right at this time, a light pillar suddenly erupted from True Yang Building.

The light pillar that was as thick as an ancient tree, charged straight to the sky.

The willow winds were pierced through by this light pillar, immediately crumbling apart and turning back into clear heaven qi, pure and warm.

The light pillar swept through repeatedly, shattering most of the willow winds in the sky, before shooting towards the lofty tiger. The lofty tiger dodged while howling in grief, but the light pillar followed it like a shadow, impossible to avoid!

The earthly calamity lofty tiger continued to decrease in size the more the light pillar touched it, till it vanished into thin air!

"What's going on?" Everyone was shocked.

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has made a move! Old ancestor protected lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng!!" Many people cheered.

But there were also some who scoffed: "Nonsense, Tai Bai Yun Sheng does not have Giant Sun's bloodline, why would old ancestor protect him?"

"This! Could it be the workings of the rumored divert disaster Gu?" Ye Lui Sang was endlessly shocked.

Hei Lou Lan was even more excited: "The luck path's divert disaster Gu can divert heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, greatly reducing their might, even directly obliterating them! If I can obtain this Immortal Gu..."

Divert disaster Gu was one of the cornerstones of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. It was also one of the limited methods Giant Sun's will could mobilize currently.

Giant Sun's will's actions did not stop at this.

He had forcibly extracted a trace of yellow apricot immortal essence by rampaging multiple times. After activating divert disaster Gu, Giant Sun's will mobilized the human qi Immortal Gu in true inheritance secluded domain.

Right under Fang Yuan's sight, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's burning luck aura suddenly decreased by another quarter.

Human qi Immortal Gu was activated which similarly let out a ray of of white light.

This white light, however, directly shone on Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Human qi Immortal Gu could increase the Gu Master's human qi, raising their future potential after advancing to a Gu Immortal. When Tai Bai Yun Sheng obtained its help, the human qi on him instantly inflated by ten times!

With the increase in human qi, he naturally needed even more heaven qi and earth qi.

However, heaven qi and earth qi were drawn out of Imperial Court blessed land.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed heartily, True Yang Building's help had been out of his expectations, but he still quickly accepted it and absorbed large amounts of heaven qi and earth qi, merging the three elements into one; not only averting danger, his potential had also greatly increased, and his future prospects had turned much better!

The land spirit Frost Jade Peacock gave a shrill, furious cry.

Heaven qi and earth qi were extracted in large amounts, causing an intense feeling of weakness to fill its body.

"Little sparrow, you are still too green." Giant Sun's will snorted, he had used all the immortal essence he was able to extract on the most crucial area, acquiring the greatest results, greatly relieving the dangerous situation.

Giant Sun's will was after all a will that originated from an Immortal Venerable, its wisdom was extremely high.

The situation had turned around quickly now and it was advantageous to Giant Sun's will.

The weakening of the land spirit gave Giant Sun's will plenty of time to grasp the Gu formation of the special will Gu surrounding him. Once Giant Sun's will breaks apart this encirclement, he would regain control of the situation, and it would be extremely easy for him to undo the seal on the immortal essence then.

As long as the seal on the immortal essence was broken, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would be able to display the supreme might of a rank eight Gu House in all its glory!

"This is bad, I still underestimated an Immortal Venerable's will. I have less than half the expected time left." Fang Yuan was able to understand the situation in True Yang Building through the glass owner token.

His heart sank: "Now, I can only put my hopes in Tai Bai Yun Sheng. Hopefully, he can quickly become a Gu Immortal and refine landscape as before Gu..."

Chapter 609: Better to die than not be free

At the center of the scene, the three qi were fusing.

With the help of Giant Sun's will, the thick qi flows had almost formed a cocoon around Tai Bai Yun Sheng!

All his injuries were long gone without any trace, his body, soul and consciousness were all being refined to a higher level.

He looked back on his life, the scenes of the past quickly flashing through his mind.

The mysteries of the Great Dao circulated in his mind, inspirations came to him without pause, he was obtaining perfect solutions for the difficult problems in cultivation that had restrained him in the past.

At this moment, heaven and earth were like selfless teachers, imparting all their knowledge to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

However, the mysteries of heaven and earth were too vast and profound, the more Tai Bai Yun Sheng knew, the more he realized his minuteness.

He had no choice but to focus on his time path, refining and developing his knowledge.

His understanding towards time path reached the peak of his lifetime!

Inspiration from nature!

Man is the spirit of all livings beings, Gu is the essence of heaven and earth. Gu Masters used Gu, refined Gu and raised Gu; this was actually an unending process of learning, exploring and studying the world.

In the process of advancing to a Gu Immortal, a Gu Master need not use Gu worms to indirectly understand the world, instead it was a direct interaction with heaven and earth.

This was probably the only chance in one's whole life before becoming a Gu Immortal to have such a precious opportunity.

Rank five peak stage was the finishing line of mortal Gu Masters. But rank six Gu Immortals were beyond mortal, becoming a Gu Immortal was only a new starting point.

At this crucial starting point, every Gu Immortal's future achievements would be different depending on the potential they accumulated.

"Such a beautiful experience, but my human qi is not sufficient..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng wished to continue immersing himself in this feeling but could not do so, a regretful expression appearing on his face.

His human qi was already nearly exhausted, and this was after obtaining the help of human qi Immortal Gu, otherwise the time would have been even shorter.

The qi cocoon dispersed and Tai Bai Yun Sheng's silhouette was revealed again.

The three qi had merged and shrunk down to a mass of tri-colored primordial qi, condensed into where Tai Bai Yun Sheng's aperture had originally been.

This step signified the completion of the second step in advancing to a Gu Immortal, receiving qi.

Next was the final step of becoming a Gu Immortal -- releasing Gu!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was being extremely serious, as he took out river as before, mountain as before and man as before Gu.

These three Gu were his core Gu worms and he was exceedingly familiar with them. Moreover, man as before Gu was even his vital Gu.

"Finally, the most crucial moment..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng first sent his vital Gu to the mass of tri-colored primordial qi in his body.

BOOM!

All of a sudden, a mystical sound like that of thunder storm echoed in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's ears, causing his whole body to intensely shake.

The tri-colored mass of qi was originally merged together and constantly flowing in circulation. But after Man As Before intruded in, it was like it had ignited an explosive; the primordial qi mass immediately exploded loudly.

There can be no creation without destruction, in death there is new life!

This moment was when a mortal could ascend to a Gu Immortal!

The explosive sound was truly mystical, exploding out the marvels of life, exploding out a whole new world!

The mortal aperture was broken, an immortal aperture was being formed!

The immortal aperture was like a small world; the sky was azure like crystals and the ground was a desolate wilderness filled with yellow stones.

It was like a newborn baby and intensely demanded nourishment, erupting at the outside world with an extremely strong force of suction and absorption.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh....

Heaven qi and earth qi madly poured into Tai Bai Yun Sheng, flowing non-stop into the immortal aperture.

In the immortal aperture, the ground quickly expanded; two thirds of a thousand square kilometres, four thirds of a thousand, two thousand square kilometres...

And time flow also rose from the one to one ratio to one to ten, one to twenty....

The immortal aperture was gradually starting to become unstable from the mad flow of qi.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng then sent in River As Before and Mountain As Before, stabilizing the situation.

The immortal aperture was expanding continually, and a tributary of the river of time flowed in the darkness, causing the time flow to increase steadily.

Time passed, Tai Bai Yun Sheng kept on placing Gu worms to maintain the stability of the immortal aperture.

Three and one third thousand square kilometres, four thousand, four and two thirds of a thousand!

One to thirty, one to thirty-one, one to thirty-two, one to thirty three!

The immortal aperture had reached its extreme at this point, as if it had drunk and eaten to its fill, abruptly stopping its growth.

But the clear heaven qi was still pouring in from the sky, and golden earth qi was still surging up from the ground.

At this moment, the immortal aperture absorbed heaven qi and earth qi much slower than before. At first, it was drinking in big gulps, while now it was taking slow sips.

Heaven and earth qi converged into the immortal aperture, green and golden mists and clouds filled the whole immortal aperture.

The dense qi flow was brewing beads of immortal essence within.

They were precisely the green grape immortal essence of a rank six Gu Immortal, thirty six of them in total.

The tribulation clouds in the sky and the calamity dust in the ground, began to gradually dissipate.

The mist like heaven qi and earth qi in the immortal aperture, however, had yet to dissipate.

They condensed around Man As Before, River As Before, Mountain As Before and other Gu worms, causing a dense qi cocoon to form over these Gu worms.

The two qi mixed; heaven and earth interacted.

Within the qi cocoons, each Gu worm was beginning to ferment mysterious changes.

"It is time." A Gu recipe flashed in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mind.

This Gu recipe was only a theoretical Gu recipe of an Immortal Gu, it was from the old beggar's Gu Immortal inheritance.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not guarantee whether this theoretical Gu recipe could succeed.

But he no longer had another option.

His lifespan was near its end, about to exhaust completely. After advancing to a Gu Immortal, his senses reached a whole new level, especially the sense regarding time had heightened the most, it was precise to within a single breath.

This novel sensation did not put him in a cheerful mood for long before he fell into silence, feeling oppressed and even afraid.

Because he could sense that the time he had was truly not much, just like a small puddle under strong sunshine, with his lifespan being the thin layer of water left in the puddle.

He had planned to get lifespan Gu but it failed because of Fang Yuan's secret manipulations. The bloody road he had experienced in reaching the great hall even became a knot in his heart.

Now, his only hope was in man as before Gu.

According to what the theoretical Gu recipe showed, when man as before Gu was advanced to rank six, it could be used on oneself.

"Refine!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng gave a soft shout, countless thoughts emerging in his mind.

These thoughts formed the theoretical Gu recipe which directly poured into the immortal aperture and then into the thick cocoon covering the man as before Gu.

These heaven and earth qi were the source of all living beings. As the two interacted, they evolved into all things in heaven and earth.

These two qi were the origin of all living beings and could replace any Gu refinement materials.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's thoughts were like keys that directed the heaven and earth qi in the proper direction.

The thoughts entered the cocoon and immediately brought upon a violent change.

Although it could not be compared to the explosion of the three qi in the first step of releasing Gu, its effect was not small either.

The qi cocoon erupted with devouring force, swallowing the remaining heaven and earth qi in the immortal aperture without pause.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh....

The qi flow surged non-stop, forming a screaming gale.

Man as before Gu turned into the eye of the storm, large amounts of heaven and earth qi poured into it, turning into Gu refinement resources.

"This it it, this is it...." Tai Bai Yun Sheng mumbled softly in the air, his tone carried gratification and also expectation.

After so much effort and risk, he was now finally seeing the hope of success.

Although the process had been filled with inconceivable events.

If True Yang Building had not made a move, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was sure to fall in the second step.

As he thought of this, he glanced at the True Yang Building.

He was not of Giant Sun's bloodline, but True Yang Building had actually helped him; this was a fact.

"Did Giant Sun's will wake up?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng inwardly guessed. He had a Gu Immortal inheritance, his experience and knowledge were not lacking compared to people like Hei Lou Lan and Ye Lui Sang.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable prohibits the entry of Gu Immortals, I have already violated this taboo by advancing into a Gu Immortal here. So, why would Giant Sun's will still help me?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was puzzled.

Even with his plentiful experience, he could not anticipate the things occurring in the True Yang Building.

Within the True Yang Building, Frost Jade Peacock gave shrill cries, the green paste on its body kept on shaking and bouncing, the iron chains also shook, producing clanking sounds when they collided with each other.

The powers sealing it were melting down from the corrosion of Gruel Mud.

But Frost Jade Peacock showed no signs of joy, instead it was filled with fear and anxiety.

Giant sun's will, however, laughed brightly: "Little sparrow, your struggle is of no use."

Through Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Giant Sun's will was able to exploit some methods to ingeniously strike the Imperial Court land spirit, weakening its strength at its foundation.

Despite the powers binding Frost Jade Peacock weakening constantly, Giant Sun's will had already bought some time.

He had already seen through most of the special will Gu formation that had besieged him.

How could an Immortal Venerable's arrangement be so simple?

As long as Giant Sun's will was completely free, he naturally had large numbers of methods to choose from like metal path, water path, fire path and so on, to seal the land spirit again.

"I have slept for too long, but it doesn't matter. I will first put this disobedient land spirit in its place, then I shall completely eliminate the minute loopholes in True Yang Building; at that time, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building will once again be like an iron bucket, standing tall for hundreds of thousands of years longer!" Giant Sun's will's tone was deep and profound.

"I won't let you have your way even if I die!!!" After hearing 'standing tall for hundreds of thousands of years', all the hairs on Frost Jade Peacock stood on their ends.

A land spirit was formed from an obsession and the matter of recognizing the master was not a flexible one. Frost Jade Peacock was distinct in this even from other land spirits; it was incomparably proud and would not yield even a little.

But Frost Jade Peacock did not struggle anymore, instead it strangely lay down dispiritedly. However, its gaze was still sharp as a knife, filled with hatred completely.

Giant Sun's will was stupefied before suddenly realizing something as he shouted in rage: "Little sparrow, you dare to do this!"

Outside the True Yang Building.

"The tribulation clouds and calamity dust are gradually dispersing, has Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng succeeded in advancing to a Gu Immortal?" Those who did not know the truth felt excited at this sight.

"I had never expected Tai Bai Yun Sheng to actually reach the third step! Looking at his appearance, the immortal aperture has already formed. I wonder what grade of blessed land he has formed?" Ye Lui Sang mumbled.

In advancing to a Gu Immortal, after passing the second step, the Gu Master could form an immortal aperture.

Immortal apertures of rank six and rank seven Gu Immortals were blessed lands; rank eight and rank nine Gu Immortal apertures were grotto-heavens!

"Blessed lands are divided into three grades, corresponding to large, medium, and small in size; the more heaven, earth and human qi are fused, the higher the grade of the blessed land. Small blessed lands have an area of up to two thousand square kilometres, they can draw in a small tributary of the river of time, and form over ten beads of immortal essence; there are few resources. Medium grade blessed lands can range from two and two thirds to four thousand square kilometres, they can draw in a slightly bigger tributary of the river of time, and form over twenty beads of immortal essence; they have plentiful resources. High grade blessed lands can range from four and two thirds to six thousand square kilometres, and draw in a large tributary of the river of time, the quantity of immortal essence formed surpasses thirty, and there will be plenty of heaven and earth qi remaining which can mutually interact and refine a mortal Gu into an Immortal Gu!"

Hei Lou Lan's gaze was fixed directly ahead, the relevant information flashing in his mind.

His brows slightly furrowed, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was able to pass the second step with True Yang Building's help, reaching the third step. And now, it looked like there was a great chance for him to succeed in becoming a Gu Immortal.

'If Tai Bai Yun Sheng becomes a Gu Immortal, then what stance should I take, how should I treat him?' Hei Lou Lan pondered over this issue.

'If nothing unexpected happens, Tai Bai Yun Sheng will no doubt obtain a high grade blessed land. However, refining an Immortal Gu carries risk, forming calamities and tribulations in the immortal aperture.' Fang Yuan's gaze continuously flickered.

For a mortal to advance to a Gu Immortal, there naturally were special risks.

Gu Masters were like this, it applied to Gu worms too.

Humans took in heaven and earth qi, fusing with human qi, the fusion of the three qi would lead to heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities. Gu worms took in heaven and earth qi, and also would induce calamities and tribulations.

It was hard for outsiders to interfere in the calamities and tribulations within one's own blessed land.

True Yang Building could influence Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but it could not influence the blessed land, the immortal aperture in his body.

In another words, Tai Bai Yun Sheng could only rely on himself.

"Huh?" Fang Yuan suddenly looked at the sky.

Regarding the sky of Imperial Court blessed land, in daytime, golden light glittered, while at night, warm silver radiance shone down.

But right now, pitch-black scars appeared in the golden sky from which specks of starlight shone down.

This was the night sky of the outside world of northern plains.

The whole of Imperial Court blessed land began to tremble.

Everyone started crying out in surprise and shock.

The tribulation clouds and calamity dust which had almost dissipated condensed again. Large amounts of heaven and earth qi poured into Tai Bai Yun Sheng's body non-stop, directly entering his immortal aperture like moths to a fire.

"What's going on?!" Hei Lou Lan was dumbstruck.

"What the hell happened!" Ye Lui Sang held his head, shouting involuntarily.

"Too much heaven and earth qi were absorbed from Imperial Court blessed land, its foundation was injured, thus it is revealing the outside world, in linking up with northern plains!" Fang Yuan's mind shook, his gaze moved from Tai Bai Yun Sheng to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

He had guessed the truth.

Frost Jade Peacock was actually so proud, it would rather die than be suppressed by Giant Sun's will any longer.

It lived up to its words!

Chapter 610: The key to victory and loss

When a Gu Master advances to an immortal, their aperture will transform into an immortal aperture.

The immortal aperture is a qualitative evolution of the aperture, it is like the creation of a whole new small world.

Rank six and seven Gu Immortal apertures were known as 'blessed lands'. Rank eight and nine Gu Immortal apertures were called 'grotto-heavens'.

If a Gu Immortal's lingering obsession was left behind when they died, it would combine with the heavenly power inside the immortal aperture and become the land spirit.

Every immortal aperture is unique, it is a part of the Gu Immortal's body. In some ways, even if a Gu Immortal dies, the land spirit and immortal aperture that they leave behind could still be considered a strange form of life extension for them.

Precisely because the land spirit is formed from obsession, it is rigid and not flexible.

In history, there were many such cases. For example, if a Gu Immortal forcefully takes down a blessed land, but did not meet the requirements to become the owner, the land spirit would reject them, in the end, the land spirit may directly self-detonate, causing the Gu Immortal's efforts to be for nothing.

Giant Sun's will forcefully sealed Imperial Court blessed land's Frost Jade Peacock, this had accumulated hundreds of thousands of years of anger in the latter. Now that he wanted to continue sealing it, Frost Jade Peacock's resolute heart was finally ignited.

"What is going on?"

"Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal ascension caused a loophole to form in the blessed land?"

"Imperial Court blessed land is currently being exposed to the outside world, this is unbelievable, this has never happened in the past!!"

"This is bad, I have a very bad feeling. Do you think the blessed land is going to be destroyed?"

In the blessed land, everyone was shouting in fear, they were panicking and their doubts were spreading.

In the sky, countless cracks were formed. The sky of the blessed land, which was silver and gold, had lots of cracks now, from these cracks, one could see the starry sky of northern plains.

Fang Yuan's gaze was still calm as ever.

"Imperial Court blessed land would not self-destruct so easily." He muttered in his heart, regarding this he was extremely confident.

In history, there were many cases of the land spirit suiciding, destroying the blessed land along with them, but that was not going to happen here.

This was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement, how could it be broken so easily? This was the hard work of a rank nine Gu Immortal, this set-up covered the entire region of northern plains!

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was the biggest obstacle.

"If this was in the past, how could the land spirit cause such trouble? Except that now, Giant Sun's will had just awakened, he was caught off guard and had to waste time to resolve this mess. Meanwhile, the seal that imprisoned the land spirit had weakened drastically because of my gruel mud Immortal Gu, this allowed the land spirit to struggle so violently."

In his analysis, Fang Yuan could not help but internally praise Giant Sun's resolution and methods.

He had used the chess piece Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and with his limited methods, he managed to fight for precious time and allow the scales of victory to tilt towards himself.

"However, even though the land spirit cannot self-destruct, it could still do the most basic thing like absorbing its own heaven and earth qi."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan directed his gaze towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Above Tai Bai Yun Sheng's head, the scattered tribulation cloud formed once again, and the calamity dust on the ground also started spreading.

Large amounts of heaven qi and earth qi gushed out, they were about to form a new heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity!

"This, what is going on? Why are there still heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities?! Wasn't it over already?" Seeing this, Ye Lui Sang's eyes were wide open in shock.

"This is different from what is in the records. There is something strange going on with Tai Bai Yun Sheng, why are there two heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities in a row?" Hei Lou Lan was very confused as well.

Even they had no idea, not to mention the others.

Looking at the imposing heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity forming once again, many people were lost for words as they felt very worried regarding Tai Bai Yun Sheng's situation.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression was ashen.

"Why is there still a heavenly tribulation forming?! My inheritance did not state that this would happen!" He was shocked and furious.

Because not just on the outside, at the same time, the immortal aperture inside his body was also forming another heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity!

When a mortal Gu becomes an Immortal Gu, it is like a Gu Master becoming an immortal, it is a dangerous process to make a qualitative change that defied heaven. When Gu worms were refined into Immortal Gu, they would need to involve heaven and earth qi, this way, the corresponding heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities would form.

Being faced with trouble both internally and externally, Tai Bai Yun Sheng could neither advance nor retreat, he could not attend to one problem while neglecting the other, his situation was very worrying!

Fang Yuan used the gruel mud Immortal Gu to awaken the land spirit.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal ascension became a crucial chess piece in the fight between the land spirit and Giant Sun's will.

This immortal ascension had already gone out of his control.

Other than Fang Yuan, everyone else was kept in the dark, they were unaware of the truth.

Only Fang Yuan knew the land spirit's intention!

In a race against time, the land spirit could not compete with Giant Sun's will, thus it placed its attention on Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

The heaven qi and earth qi were extracted by sacrificing the land spirit's own foundation. Its intention was to form the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity that would destroy Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

What benefits would the land spirit gain from killing him?

This would involve the devouring of the immortal aperture.

Mortal apertures were not easy to devour and combine, but after ascending to immortal, the immortal aperture was a small world. Between worlds, they could be devoured and assimilated, there were great benefits to Gu Immortals.

On Tian Ti mountain back then, Fang Yuan discarded a portion of Hu Immortal blessed land's territory, which were quickly taken by the other Gu Immortals. Swallowing other immortal apertures and strengthening one's own immortal aperture, there was much to gain from this.

If the land spirit destroyed Tai Bai Yun Sheng, after he dies, his immortal aperture would remain. It would then be absorbed and assimilated by Imperial Court blessed land.

After devouring the aperture, the blessed land's foundation would rise, and the land spirit would become much stronger. This would be a great help for it to break through Giant Sun's seal.

In the sky, dark clouds were rumbling as lightning and thunder resounded.

Countless purple lightning bolts formed into balls of lightning.

On the ground, the calamity dust settled down, exposing the bare earth.

A crack formed on the ground, it was hundreds of meters wide, exposing red hot flames from within, it resembled a desolate beast opening its bloodthirsty mouth.

The flames rose up, forming many traces of restraining smoke as they gushed up.

"Chaotic lightning balls, restraining smoke!" Fang Yuan frowned slightly.

The chaotic lightning balls not only had great power, they could even ruin the Gu Master's mind and will, inducing a chaotic effect. Restraining smoke could seal away the environment, as long as the Gu Master was trapped within, they would lose their five senses, like falling into a maze or an abyss, they would not be able to get free.

Chaotic lightning balls were not fast, but together with the suppression from restraining smoke, they were perfect partners and could unleash the greatest effect!

Fang Yuan could not help but feel some worry.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's failure was not what Fang Yuan wanted to see.

Holding the glass owner token in his hand, Fang Yuan tightened his grasp as his gaze turned dark: "Still too weak, too weak! With my current strength, I am very heavily affected by circumstances..."

Howl, howl, howl!

The chaotic lightning balls flew through the air, emitting a strange and shrill noise. They sounded like a woman screaming and crying at the same time, it was very painful to the ears.

At the same time, the restraining smoke was rumbling, surging towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression turned pale.

The chaotic lightning balls changed their directions randomly, sometimes they traveled right, sometimes left, it was hard to dodge them. Furthermore, there were traces of restraining smoke around him, like he was in the middle of an ancient forest.

"If I come into contact with the restraining smoke, I'll be finished! Oh no, the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity in my immortal aperture is also forming, moreover I have already lost my defensive Gu!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng gritted his teeth, his gaze was shining with resolution.

Risk it!

His body gave off a shining light, using several movement Gu, his body flew into the air.

The intense wind blew this old man's hair towards the back, showing an unrestrained demeanour.

Shocked screams could be heard coming from the crowd.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng charged towards the tribulation cloud, above him, there were countless chaotic lightning balls, looking from afar, he was like a moth flying towards a fire.

"Is Tai Bai Yun Sheng seeking death?" Ye Lui Sang frowned deeply.

"Good!" Hei Lou Lan, however, gave high praise.

Fang Yuan's eyes also shone.

Restraining smoke might seem harmless without any attack power and could only trap enemies, but it held much greater threat than the chaotic lightning balls.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng understood the situation and made the best decision.

Only to see that after he charged into the thunder cloud, countless lightning balls shot down like fish swimming in water.

Bam bam bam...

The lightning balls continued to explode, but it did not affect Tai Bai Yun Sheng at all.

He flew left and right, trying to find a survival chance in the barrage of attacks, his movement speed was fast at times and slow at others, he had great control over the situation!

"Amazing! What level of flying attainment is this!"

"To think that Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng is actually a flying master!!"

"He hid himself too deeply, I only found out now..."

Everyone was overjoyed to find out that Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a flying master!

"To think that Tai Bai Yun Sheng was skilled at using cloud path Gu worms." Ye Lui Sang praised, he was not very surprised at the display of flying.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a healing Gu Master, these years when he roamed northern plains, he had encountered many dangers. He had to have a secret ability in order to survive till now.

In truth, most healing Gu Masters were either skilled in defense or movement.

When these Gu Masters were nurtured, they were specially trained in this manner.

That was because in the battlefield, healing Gu Masters were usually the first to be targeted, many times they could not receive protection from their teammates. Thus, healing Gu Masters needed to have certain ways to protect themselves.

"As the number one healing Gu Master in northern plains, Tai Bai Yun Sheng is not skilled in defense, with his age, it is no wonder he has such flying attainment." Hei Lou Lan thought about this and turned his head, looking at the sky far away.

There, Fang Yuan seated on the azure wolf king's back, observing Tai Bai Yun Sheng closely.

Compared to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Chang Shan Yin who was also a flying master was much younger.

"Little sparrow, you are really enjoying yourself." In True Yang Building, Giant Sun's will laughed instead of raging.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was shaking intensely, the aurora was wavering in the sky as a huge pillar of light shot out.

Immortal Gu — Divert Disaster!

The light of Divert Disaster shone around Tai Bai Yun Sheng, piercing through the lightning balls and restraining smoke.

"Old ancestor is really blessing Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he struck once again!" Amidst the shocked screams, there were jealous and envious people too.

"This is too weird, Tai Bai Yun Sheng is not part of Giant Sun's bloodline, to think he could receive such blessings as well!" Someone was suspicious.

"As expected, he struck." Fang Yuan sighed internally, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had already become a crucial factor in the contest between the land spirit and Giant Sun's will, the land spirit wanted to harm him, while Giant Sun's will wanted to protect him!

Chapter 611: Landscape As Before

"Luck inspection Gu!"

Fang Yuan's heart moved, quickly sending his primeval essence into the Gu.

The next moment, his vision changed.

Luck inspection Gu, a rank five luck path investigative Gu, it could allow him to see luck despite its formlessness.

Looking at Tai Bai Yun Sheng's luck now, his previous fiery red luck that was originally burning with a glowing red glow had shrunken by a bit.

"Earlier, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's will was helping him, thus his luck was being expended. Now that he helped once more, Tai Bai Yun Sheng has only a third of his initial luck left." Fang Yuan evaluated.

Looking at his own luck, it was still the black coffin luck, as rich and dense as ink, and even larger than before.

Fang Yuan's heart jumped, but quickly snickered to himself, looking at the people in the blessed land.

The people who were watching Tai Bai Yun Sheng ascend to immortal realm had changes to their luck as well.

The overwhelming majority of the Gu Masters had unwittingly developed a small layer of black coffin luck.

Except for Hei Lou Lan, he still had his unchanged profuse azure luck.

Looking around, Fang Yuan felt his eyes hurting, he quickly stopped using the luck inspection Gu.

When a Gu Master ascends, there would be endless heaven and earth qi, using Gu worms in such an environment would cause a backlash.

If he forcefully continued to use them, both he and his Gu worms would suffer injuries, or even face death.

As his vision returned to normal, Fang Yuan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng again.

He was swimming in the thunderstorm, flying through the crevices of the clouds, showing off his master level flying attainment.

His body had no more defensive Gu, he was relying on his movement to evade the chaotic lightning balls, it was like walking on a tightrope, he was in great danger.

In order to avoid the earthly calamity of restraining smoke, he charged into the thunder clouds, this was a wise decision when weighing the two difficulties, but it was also a helpless choice.

"If not for the fact that I have green grape immortal essence, and can dilute it to form endless primeval essence, such an insane flying speed would have drained my aperture dry long ago." Tai Bai Yun Sheng was breathing roughly, his hair was in a mess and his body was feeling weak, the situation was getting more dangerous.

Swoosh!

Suddenly, a chaotic lightning ball changed directions and charged towards him.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to evade it, but it was too late, he could only stare indignantly with a furious gaze.

In the moment of crisis, a white light pillar shot over, directly hitting this chaotic lightning ball.

The lightning ball quickly melted from the ray of light, turning into pure heaven qi.

Divert disaster Gu!

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's help came once again, saving Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"So close, even though I became a Gu Immortal, I do not have any defenses on me, if I was hit by the chaotic lightning ball, I'd be heavily injured, the consequences are unthinkable!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng swallowed his saliva, feeling some lingering fear.

After becoming a Gu Immortal, the foundation of his life had been elevated. If he was still a mortal, a chaotic lightning ball could easily kill him. Gu Immortals however, were tougher, even without any defensive Gu, they could endure over a dozen lightning balls without any problems.

But the thing was, these lightning balls had special effects.

After being hit, they would cause Tai Bai Yun Sheng's thoughts to be chaotic, once his mind is in chaos he would not be able to think properly.

At this crucial moment, as long as Tai Bai Yun Sheng stops in the air for a moment, he would be attacked by countless lightning balls at once.

If he was hit by these lightning balls consecutively, Tai Bai Yun Sheng would have no chance to gather his thoughts, he would just be drowned under the endless lightning balls.

"Quickly look, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building saved Tai Bai Yun Sheng once again."

"That's right, this has already happened at least ten times."

"With True Yang Building's help, it seems Tai Bai Yun Sheng's tribulation will succeed without fail!"

Outside, everyone saw this with amazed and envious expressions.

"Such intensive assistance, will it really work?" Hei Lou Lan's eyes were shining brilliantly, he saw the situation with a different perspective.

In such an environment, when heaven and earth qi were rampaging, usage of any Gu worm would create a huge backlash.

Divert disaster Gu was no exception.

In the history of Gu Masters, there were many instances of Gu Immortals helping out during the tribulation, and eventually the backlash destroying their Immortal Gu.

Except that most people were ignorant and did not know such secrets.

"Divert disaster Gu is one of the foundational pieces of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it is used for Imperial Court blessed land to divert away disasters. Without it, Imperial Court blessed land would face terrifying earthly calamities and heavenly tributations. Giant Sun's will would not sacrifice such a precious Gu for Tai Bai Yun Sheng, that means the reinforcement of Giant Sun's will is limited... What happens now is most crucial, it will depend on Tai Bai Yun Sheng, whether he can quickly survive the calamity and tribulation in the immortal aperture." Fang Yuan was expressionless as he sat on the azure wolf king's back, watching with growing tension.

After all, landscape as before Gu was one of his main goals in coming to northern plains.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's speed started to slow down.

He was facing troubles both in his aperture and outside of it, the land spirit was causing him harm, while the calamity and tribulation was forming in his own immortal aperture due to his mortal Gu's ascension.

This internal threat especially, it was taking away much of his attention, thus his reactions toward the outside world were getting slower.

Suddenly, his body shook, completely stopping his movements.

Immediately after, countless chaotic lightning balls flew towards him.

Divert disaster light pillar was shining brilliantly, it burst out and surrounded Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Now is the most crucial time!" Fang Yuan, Hei Lou Lan, Ye Lui Sang and others could see clearly that this was it, their eyes were shining.

At this moment, in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture, bright light exploded, engulfing the entire small world.

The aura of the Immortal Gu was spewing out like a fountain.

In that bright light, an Immortal Gu was rising up slowly.

It looked like a ladybug, it was fist sized and had a jade body. On its round back, there were natural markings, half was of rivers and seas, while the other half was of valleys and mountains.

"So this Immortal Gu was created by combining River as Before and Mountain as Before. It seems the effect is also the product of River as Before and Mountain as Before, but elevated." Tai Bai Yun Sheng analyzed.

This was refined during the resonance of heaven and earth, it was not refined by him personally, thus, he was still unclear towards the effect of Landscape as Before.

After looking at it for a few breaths' time, Tai Bai Yun Sheng placed his attention on the most central area of the blessed land.

Immortal Gu Landscape as Before, it was not part of his goal, only an additional surprise.

Now at the center of the blessed land, man as before Gu had turned into a huge cocoon, but cracks were starting to develop on it. Dazzling rainbow light was leaking from the cracks.

Breaking the cocoon and becoming a butterfly!

As the thick cocoon vanished, a colorful butterfly fluttered into the sky. Wherever it went, rainbow light rained down, trailing behind the butterfly's path as a curvy rainbow was formed behind it.

"Success, Immortal Gu Man as Before! Ahahaha..." Seeing this, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was extremely happy, he laughed maniacally.

So many years of accumulation, so many years of anticipation and worry, so many times he had fallen into grave danger, but at this moment, he obtained a perfect result!

But his internal threat still remained.

In the immortal aperture, the azure tribulation cloud was rumbling, forming a huge green scaled snake, the snake had a silver horn on its head, and its body was hundreds of metres long, the snake tail had turned into qi, fusing with the tribulation cloud.

As for the ground, it started shaking, making loud sounds that resembled thunder, causing pain to the eardrums.

The newly formed earth burst out with cracks, as lava spewed out of it, the smoke was thick as trees as the surroundings withered.

"Heavenly tribulation — silver horn green scale python, earthly calamity — molten earth!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart shook, facing both the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity alone at the same time, he felt an immense pressure.

He placed his hopes on the Immortal Gu Landscape as Before.

"Come." He willed, as a bead of green grape immortal essence flew out, fusing into the landscape as before Gu.

The ladybug-like landscape as before Gu immediately flapped its wings, flying away like a flash of lightning.

Everywhere it went, in the surroundings, the land returned to spring as the landscape was restored to normal, back to the moment before the earthly calamity struck.

"Good Gu, good Gu!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart settled, with landscape as before Immortal Gu, he had no fear towards the earthly calamity.

Hisss—!

The silver horn green scale python opened its mouth, making a shrill sound.

It shot out abruptly, its huge body bringing along a draft of wind, as it pounced on the landscape as before Immortal Gu.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was nervous, although Immortal Gu had huge capabilities, those which were not defensive Gu were usually fragile. Landscape as before Gu was the same, if it was destroyed by the silver horn green scale python, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's situation would turn bad.

Thankfully, landscape as before Gu was born from his aperture during the resonance of heaven and earth, he could control it like moving his limbs.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had deep foundations accumulated in his life, he quickly mobilized landscape as before Immortal Gu and escaped. The silver horn green scale python behind him had attacked dozens of times, it destroyed mountains and rivers, the earth was pierced and rocks were sent flying, as savage winds ravaged the land.

"Oh no! At this rate..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng was concentrating intensely, after a few breaths' time, sweat started forming on his forehead.

His eyes were shut tight, his body was still floating in the air, as the chaotic lightning balls crashed towards him.

But thankfully, due to the divert disaster Immortal Gu's light pillar, his body was protected.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was unable to care about the outside world since long ago, but he had not forgotten his external threat.

This terrible situation forced him to cut his losses decisively.

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's reinforcement is limited, it might stop anytime. I can only do this... With man as before Immortal Gu in my possession, as long as I have time, there is hope! Cut, cut it off!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted in his heart.

Abandoning the territories to protect his headquarters, he gave up a portion of his immortal aperture, the sky began to cut apart.

The blessed land was the foundation and base of a Gu Immortal, cutting off the blessed land was like self-mutilation, it reduced their own strength and potential.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng had no other choice.

Just like how Fang Yuan survived the earthly calamity back in Hu Immortal blessed land, in order to get rid of the blue charm lightning shadow, he discarded a portion of the blessed land, Tai Bai Yun Sheng also had to make such a sacrifice!

The blessed land's sky was shaved off layer by layer.

Along with the thick tribulation clouds, they were all sent out of his body.

Outside his body, it was Imperial Court blessed land, Frost Jade Peacock joyfully chirped as it devoured these blessed land fragments, to increase its own strength.

Giant Sun's will shouted in anger.

He was trying to protect Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life, but the latter was now fueling his enemy's strength!

Giant Sun's will had to protect him, because if Tai Bai Yun Sheng died, his entire immortal aperture would be devoured by Imperial Court blessed land.

Most importantly, divert disaster Immortal Gu was already full of cracks, if he reinforced Tai Bai Yun Sheng any more, the Gu might get destroyed from the backlash.

Divert disaster Immortal Gu was one of the foundation pieces of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it could not be lost!

But if Tai Bai Yun Sheng died, it was similarly disadvantageous for Giant Sun's will.

At once, Giant Sun's will fell into a difficult predicament.

Chapter 612: Hoodwinking the Land Spirit

The sky in the immortal aperture started to peel off layer by layer, the dense tribulation clouds thinned out along with it. The devastating silver horn green scale python's body decreased to one-tenth of its original size, its might extremely weakened.

The situation was taking a turn for the better for Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Success is at hand." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes were filled with tears when he opened them. The situation in the immortal aperture was already stabilizing, and he had the room to pay some attention to the external crisis.

The light of Divert Disaster was covering him, preventing the calamity and tribulation from touching him; Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt gratitude from the depths of his heart: "This is all thanks to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building helping me, otherwise I would find it difficult to even have a hope of succeeding... Eh!"

The light of divert disaster suddenly dissipated!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was caught off-guard and was bombarded by the chaotic lightning balls, his mind immediately turning chaotic. He flew around in disorder, knocking into large numbers of chaotic lightning balls as he was unable to act for himself with not even a trace of reason left.

Everyone was shocked but before they could express it, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building burst out with an absolutely powerful absorption force again, directly capturing the hysterical Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Giant Sun's will could not sacrifice divert disaster Gu and also could not let Tai Bai Yun Sheng die.

The best method was, of course, to throw Tai Bai Yun Sheng out of the blessed land. Unfortunately, only Frost Jade Peacock could do that in this situation.

Helplessly, Giant Sun's will could only use this inferior method.

This was indeed an inferior solution.

Under everyone's shocked gazes, the tribulation clouds and calamity dust surged explosively, shrouding Eighty-Eight True Yang Building! Countless chaotic lightning balls crashed down like a violent storm; while restraining smoke coiled around the tower like an immemorial giant python, continually seeping inside.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had brought in Tai Bai Yun Sheng, thus becoming the target for the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity.

To protect Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life, Giant Sun's will chose to forcefully resist the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity!

"How could this happen!"

"Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng was brought into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!!"

"How on earth does he deserve such assistance from old ancestor? This is a heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity we are talking about, they are extremely dangerous to True Yang Building!"

Everyone looked on with stupefied and shocked gazes.

Under the presence of the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, using Gu worms was asking to suffer backlash.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was a rank eight Immortal Gu house; in its essence, it was an integrated body of many Immortal Gu and countless mortal Gu. And now, it was forcefully resisting the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, the pressure on it was already enormous. And because of the force of the backlash, the coordination between the Gu worms had been affected!

It was clear, this was by no means a wise course of action.

However, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had become a crucial key in the fight between Giant Sun's will and Frost Jade Peacock; Giant Sun's will, forced by the situation, could only settle for such a method.

Inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Frost Jade Peacock rapidly moved its wings, continuously dodging in between the gigantic trees.

Five Immortal Gu, with all kinds of flaming tails trailing after them, were pursuing and obstructing it.

Frost Jade Peacock was not willing to be sealed again and used all its strength to run away, gradually it lost its head and was unable to take the exact path, crashing into countless giant trees on the way.

Under Giant Sun's will's control, True Yang Building was a natural cage that could utilize the strength of any round, while Frost Jade Peacock was the bird in the cage. The giant trees turned into treemen, opening their arms to block it.

Caaaw—!

Frost Jade Peacock screamed shrilly as it suffered damage.

It tore apart the defense line of three old treemen, but its speed lowered greatly by this, and was caught up by a metal path Immortal Gu from behind.

A golden stream of light rapidly flowed on its body. The golden light condensed into a thick golden shell wherever it touched, firmly covering Frost Jade Peacock.

Frost Jade Peacock sensed it could not budge in any areas covered by the golden light; it was instantly startled and furious.

It hurriedly flapped its wings to increase its speed again. But the next moment, it was attacked by the second Immortal Gu.

An intense sleepiness invaded its mind, causing its eyes to turn hazy as it felt an intense urge to sleep.

Boom.

It crashed down head-first onto the ground, unable to fly any longer.

It had a premonition that its fate was to be sealed again; two rows of tears filled with grief and indignance involuntarily fell down from its eyes.

"Don't... even... think..." Frost Jade Peacock mumbled to itself, trying to use all its remaining strength to resist.

Although there was still the remaining power of Immortal Gu Gruel Mud on its body, the two Immortal Gu sealing it again were not restrained by Gruel Mud.

"Even if I die, I won't let you prevail!" Frost Jade Peacock gave off an intense suicidal will, and disregarding everything, it drew out the foundation of Imperial Court blessed land — heaven and earth qi, to intensify the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity.

And it was rapidly weakening.

Imperial Court blessed land was born from a space path Gu Immortal, thus the blessed land's territory was vast, far surpassing any at an equivalent level.

Later, it was developed by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, becoming a top-notch blessed land and also obtaining the ability to transit between day and night; it could be said to be at the doorstep of transforming into a grotto-heaven.

If it could swallow the time path Gu Immortal Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture, space and time could converge which was the greatest supplement to Imperial Court blessed land. It was extremely likely for there to be a qualitative change which could allow Imperial Court blessed land to advance to a grotto-heaven!

If that happened, Frost Jade Peacock could break apart most of the arrangements of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Although it could not suppress Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it would have the power to expel it out of the blessed land.

However, Giant Sun's will was truly too resolute and would rather suffer the damage from the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity to protect Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life.

Frost Jade Peacock was only an obsession left behind after a Gu Immortal's death, how could it scheme against Giant Sun's will?

But it was also because of its obsession, it was brave and unyielding!

On the verge of being sealed again, it would rather be exterminated, and disregarding the consequences, it drew out large amounts of heaven and earth qi from Imperial Court blessed land.

These heaven and earth qi were like adding fuel to the fire; as they assimilated into the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, the sky rumbled with lightning, the chaotic lightning balls immediately expanded tenfold in quantity, and the restraining smoke had even more changes, its body inflated and its dark color turned even deeper.

Crack crack crack!

Lightning balls rained down like a storm, fiercely striking Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Bursts of explosions sounded out; Eighty-Eight True Yang Building became filled with scars, the eaves of the tower collapsed piece by piece, and a crack even appeared on the outer wall.

Restraining smoke turned into an even bigger problem, becoming a deadly smoke calamity; it was much more powerful and seeped everywhere on Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's surface, gradually dying it black.

The pitch-black walls of the building seemed to have eroded for a thousand years, as they started to peel off.

"The heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity have become stronger!"

"This is too terrifying, retreat, retreat!"

"What is happening? Even the wind and snow from the outside world are pouring in!!"

Everyone started shouting in shock.

Frost Jade Peacock extracted large amounts of heaven and earth qi, injuring Imperial Court blessed land's foundation. If Imperial Court blessed land was originally a strong house, now the tiles and bricks were taken out, only leaving behind the framework of the house.

This caused countless holes to appear in it, connecting to the outside world.

And the outside world of northern plains was currently experiencing the blizzard of every ten years.

Divert disaster Gu was dormant, causing Imperial Court blessed land to suffer the invasion of the blizzard calamity as well.

Imperial Court blessed land was no longer a refuge; large amounts of wind and snow poured in, the temperature quickly dropped as the heavy snowfall flew inside. Although it had not reached the level of forming snow monsters, it was not too far away.

"Little sparrow, look at what a big mess you have caused." Giant Sun's will shouted in annoyance.

Blessed lands and grotto-heavens would attract all sizes of calamities and tribulations in every set interval of time. The larger their fortune, the stronger the calamities and tribulations.

The great snow disaster that wreaked havoc over the whole of northern plains every ten years was actually the calamity and tribulation of Imperial Court blessed land.

Imperial Court blessed land had Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and was also a peak level blessed land with territory that was at the size of a small world; the fortune it contained was gigantic, thus the calamities and tribulations it attracted were extremely terrifying.

Right now, divert disaster Gu was hibernating, while Imperial Court blessed land had connected outside to northern plains, causing the once in ten years blizzard to return into it.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building could forcibly resist the frenzied attacks of lightning balls, the invasion of the black smoke, but it was unable to contend against the blizzard that could wreak havoc over the whole of northern plains.

If this situation continued, Imperial Court blessed land would erode and crumble apart due to the snow disaster.

Frost Jade Peacock did not need Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, but Eighty-Eight True Yang Building needed Imperial Court blessed land.

There was one way to salvage this situation.

That was to use divert disaster Gu to eliminate heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities and turn them into heaven qi and earth qi. Making Imperial Court blessed land take in these heaven and earth qi to stabilize its foundation, and close the connection with the outside world of northern plains.

Giant Sun's will could take the risk in forcibly activating divert disaster Gu. But to make Imperial Court blessed land take in heaven and earth qi required Frost Jade Peacock's cooperation.

"Asking this little sparrow to cooperate is simply an impossible dream!" Even if it was Giant Sun's will, this was a difficult problem.

He helplessly thought of the only way —"Unless Frost Jade Peacock acknowledges a pair of new owners..."

Giant Sun's will did not know that Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture contained landscape as before Immortal Gu which could conveniently deal with this trouble.

He thought of another Immortal Gu he had — false emotion fake will Gu!

The condition for Frost Jade Peacock to acknowledge its owner was a couple who had true love for each other.

However, nothing was absolute, even the land spirit could be hoodwinked.

Giant Sun's will knew as long as he found two candidates to use false emotion fake will Gu on, he could hoodwink the land spirit and make Frost Jade Peacock recognize new owners.

Once Frost Jade Peacock was controlled, each problem could be easily resolved.

Moreover, this method was very favorable to Giant Sun's will.

If a couple who had true love for each other became the owners of Imperial Court blessed land, what would Giant Sun's will do if this couple did not obey his commands?

Instead of that, he would hold onto the initiative if he found two unconnected people to use false emotion fake will Gu on and satisfy the requirement to become the owners.

Because false emotion fake will Gu contained Giant Sun's will!

False emotion fake will Gu was subjected to Giant Sun's will's control. Even if the two unconnected people were disloyal in the future, as long as Giant Sun's will still held false emotion fake will Gu, at worst, he could once again select two new candidates.

'Little sparrow, you are a long way from being able to fight with me.' Giant Sun's will was shrewd and wise, inheriting some of the main body's intelligence; the seemingly desperate situation could not hold him back. With just some thinking, he thought of a way to resolve it.

He immediately mobilized Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's strength to inspect the candidates.

Right now in Imperial Court blessed land, everyone was running away from danger here and there, with many casualties appearing.

The situation was quickly worsening, it was so cold that one's spit could instantly freeze into a piece of ice. The majestic blizzard was pouring in without any pause, tall and formidable snow monsters started standing up from the depths of the snow, selecting targets to devour.

But this did not pose any difficulty for Giant Sun's will.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building could plunder resources from the whole of northern plains, let alone two people that were right in front of it.

These two people would naturally be those with Giant Sun's bloodline, Giant Sun's will soon selected two candidates who satisfied it.

"Eh?" Hei Lou Lan's vision rapidly changed, he was at rank five peak stage, but he did not even have the strength to resist as he was absorbed into True Yang Building.

"Ahhhhh, save me!" Not far away, Ma Hong Yun was still running frantically and did not realize the changes in his surroundings.

Thud.

He bumped head first into a giant tree in front.

"Don't tell me this kid was running with his eyes closed..." Hei Lou Lan was speechless.

Chapter 613: Identity exposed

"Painful, painful!" Ma Hong Yun rubbed his forehead that had turned red, pouting as he got up from the floor.

"Eh! What is this place?" He discovered that the blizzard had vanished without a trace, he was surrounded by a spring-like warmth; it was not a world of ice and snow, instead it was a vast ancient forest.

Around him were gigantic ancient trees, hundreds of metres tall, so thick that even a dozen adults joining hands could not surround it.

The ancient trees were very tall, and their lush leaves covered the sky; rays of sunlight penetrated through the small gaps, forming a tranquil scene under the shade.

Compared to the outside world, this was practically a paradise.

"You are in the center of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building." A voice suddenly echoed within Ma Hong Yun and Hei Lou Lan's ears.

"Who is this?" Hei Lou Lan's pupils contracted.

Ma Hong Yun cried out in fear: "Ghost!"

He panicked and subconsciously ran to the side of Hei Lou Lan.

"Ghost? I am no ghost, if I could become a ghost, my affairs would be much easier to settle. Unfortunately I am merely a remnant will, inferior to even a ghost."

Giant Sun's will gave a sigh, and suddenly in mid-air, golden speckles of light appeared.

These speckles of light rotated slowly and suddenly condensed, transforming into an imposing body of light and shadow, similar in appearance to Giant Sun.

"Ah, you are!?" Ma Hong Yun stammered, his finger pointing towards the will of Giant Sun in endless shock.

Hei Lou Lan's pupils contracted, as the head of Hei tribe, he knew a lot. His complexion turned solemn and respectful; placing his hands on his chest, he spoke dutifully: "Descendant pays respect to Ancestor Giant Sun!"

Giant Sun sighed once again, and said: "I know the two of you are feeling confusion within your hearts. To make a long story short, this man broke into True Yang Building, undid the seal on the Frost Jade Peacock land spirit, and thus put Imperial Court blessed land on the brink of crisis."

As he said that, the golden speckles condensed into the image of Chang Shan Yin.

"Ah, it's Lord Wolf King!" Ma Hong Yun immediately recognized.

"It was actually him?!" Hei Lou Lan also could not help but cry out.

But Giant Sun's will immediately continued: "What you see is not his genuine appearance."

As he spoke, the image of Chang Shan Yin changed, gradually turning into Fang Yuan's true appearance.

"This is the true face of that person." Giant Sun's will spoke.

Fang Yuan disguised himself as Chang Shan Yin using the human skin Gu. This Gu was a mortal Gu, it was able to deceive people like Hei Lou Lan, but it failed to deceive Giant Sun's will.

Even though when Fang Yuan explored the true inheritance secluded domain in secret, Giant Sun's will was asleep. But within the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there were many Gu worms that had recorded his actions.

Seeing the true face of Fang Yuan, Hei Lou Lan and Ma Hong Yun were unable to recognize him.

"So it turn out that this Chang Shan Yin was merely a fake! To actually infiltrate Imperial Court blessed land, he is extremely daring!" Hei Lou Lan let out a cold snort, sensing such a huge conspiracy, he could not help but be both startled and furious at once.

"He not only has guts, but he had also made ample preparations. Looking at the two methods he used to scheme against me, these are not something that one can accomplish on their own, there surely must be a larger force backing him. You two are my descendants; True Yang Building has been infiltrated by outsiders and is in deep trouble, I now need your strength." Giant Sun's will spoke.

Hei Lou Lan and Ma Hong Yun glanced at each other, both expressing their desire to cooperate with Giant Sun's will.

Giant Sun's will spoke concisely, in a short period of time, he was able to give a clear explanation.

"So it was like this." Hei Lou Lan came to a realization, and was now able to understand why True Yang Building helped Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

His heart jumped, Giant Sun's will's idea was for him to become Imperial Court blessed land's owner, that involved tremendous benefits.

"Imperial Court blessed land's ownership condition is special, the blessed land actually requires two owners. No wonder back then, when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable set up the sacred palace, he made it so that his empress could stay in it. He loved his empress very much, now it seems that the empress also had half the ownership of Imperial Court blessed land."

"Using false emotion fake will Gu to deceive the land spirit, this is quite a good idea. But this kid, how could he be selected to become Imperial Court blessed land's owner alongside me?"

Hei Lou Lan's eyes sparkled, shooting a glance toward Ma Hong Yun, concealing his deep disdain.

"Could it be that Ancestor Giant Sun thinks that he is an easier pawn to control?" Hei Lou Lan's gaze trembled, with Giant Sun's will present, he did not dare to do anything reckless.

Differing from Hei Lou Lan, Ma Hong Yun suddenly remembered something and shouted: "Wait a moment! Lady Xiao Yun and my wife Xiao Li are still outside, I do not want to be the owner of the blessed land, quickly let me out, I need to save them!"

Lady Xiao Yun naturally referred to Zhao Lian Yun.

His wife Xiao Li was Chang Li. Originally, Chang Biao, in order to coax Ma Ying Jie, allowed his adopted daughter Chang Li to be married off to Ma Hong Yun, consequently turning her into Ma Hong Yun's wife.

Giant Sun's will seemed to have taken a fancy to Ma Hong Yun, he laughed heartily: "Hahaha, caring for beautiful women, you are truly my descendant. Boy, once you become the owner of this blessed land, this will become your domain. Then, you will be able to have all the women you desire."

Ma Hong Yun stared blankly, before quickly shouting: "No, it's very dangerous outside, I have to go and save them both. No matter what this affair is, we can discuss it later. Release me outside, quickly let me go!"

"Foolish boy, relying on your own strength, you can barely defend yourself, how can you defend other people?" Giant Sun's will laughed. "Be obedient and stay here, cooperate and become the owner of Imperial Court blessed land. I will be the one to save your women."

Giant Sun's will moved rapidly without delay, starting to act the moment he finished speaking.

Great numbers of Gu Masters were in the True Yang Building, and almost all of them were Giant Sun's descendants.

These were his descendants, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was built for their sake, as an inheritance for his descendants.

Naturally, not all of his descendants had the aptitude to become Gu Masters, Giant Sun's will had not made a move to save those.

Fang Yuan had a panoramic view of this scene.

"Giant Sun's will made a move, this time, many people were taken into the building." Within his mind, Mo Yao's will spoke.

Fang Yuan sat still on the back of an azure wolf king, floating at a high altitude in the sky, gazing at the distant sacred palace.

But it was a huge distance away from his original location.

The power of the calamities and tribulations getting more fearsome, Fang Yuan, in order to avoid the disaster, could only retreat.

In the surroundings of the sacred palace, the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities continued to increase in power, the area was already extremely dangerous. This Frost Jade Peacock was putting in a last ditch attempt, even the once in ten years blizzard of the northern plains was attracted over.

Now the sacred palace had mostly been destroyed, the broken walls scattered in the wind, its former splendor nowhere to be seen.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was in a terrible state, it was wrapped in layers of heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities. Inside it were the chaotic lightning balls and restraining smoke, while outside was the raging blizzard that was getting stronger.

"Giant Sun's will has already awakened, he definitely wants you dead, it's a blessing that he isn't targeting you now; he absolutely won't come and save us. We should retreat and return to Water Pavilion. Within Water Pavilion, there is some immortal essence that I have left behind in the past, you can use them to move the Gu House. You can return to central continent, and when you return Water Pavilion to Spirit Affinity House, you will receive more benefits than you can imagine, there is no need for you to take a risk here." Within his mind, Mo Yao continued to coax him.

Things had already progressed this far, the entire Imperial Court blessed land had been affected, Giant Sun's will had already awakened, Water Pavilion was still hidden; while True Yang Building was suppressed by the heaven tribulations and earthly calamities, it was a great opportunity to retreat.

"Retreat?" Fang Yuan's eyes were cold and detached, his line of sight turning towards the glass owner token in his hands as he sneered softly.

He gripped the glass owner token tightly.

This was a crucial trump card he had not expended yet.

Central continent Gu Immortals left behind three methods to deal with Giant Sun's will.

The first was the Gu formation of special will Gu, effective in dealing with Giant Sun's will. The second method was a sealing Gu formation, which could temporarily seal the yellow apricot immortal essence left behind by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The third method was even more hidden but had greater power, it could temporarily expel Giant Sun's will from the True Yang Building!

The glass owner token was the key to all three of these methods.

Now, both the first and second methods were already used, only the third method was left.

But this third method was much stronger compared with the first two methods, it could be said to be a trump card!

Especially at this moment.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was wrapped in heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, once Giant Sun's will gets temporarily separated from the building, he would definitely suffer the fearsome attack of the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities!

Mo Yao's plan was indeed mature and stable, but great risks come with great rewards.

Meanwhile, in True Yang Building.

Chang Li and Zhao Lian Yun were brought into the building by Giant Sun's will, appearing in front of Ma Hong Yun.

"Lady Xiao Yun, my wife Xiao Li!" Ma Hong Yun was jubilant, and dashed towards them.

"Husband!" Chang Li was happy to have escaped danger, and threw herself into Ma Hong Yun's arms.

Zhao Lian Yun also moved quickly towards Ma Hong Yun's side, her face also full of joy from having returned from death's door, she lightly kicked Ma Hong Yun's leg: "Foolish kid, unexpectedly, you were useful for once."

"Hahaha, it's only natural." Ma Hong Yun loosened his hug and cordially looked towards Giant Sun's will floating in midair, and expressed his gratitude, "Thank you, old ancestor."

Just as he said that, suddenly, a violent tremor occurred.

For a moment, the entire forest shook.

"What's going on?" Chang Li and Zhao Lian Yun both turned pale.

"Alright, enough nonsense, the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities are getting more and more severe, eventually, even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building will no longer be able to resist. You must become Imperial Court blessed land's owners as soon as possible." The complexion of Giant Sun's will's changed as he spoke.

Bam bam bam...

A group of large treemen moved slowly, each footstep they took sounding like thunder.

The treemen lowered their waists, opening their branch-like palms, revealing the giant immobilized peacock.

"This is the land spirit of Imperial Court blessed land, Frost Jade Peacock!" Giant Sun's will introduced, while at the same time, false emotion fake will Gu flew towards the Frost Jade Peacock.

Hei Lou Lan and Ma Hong Yun stood before the Frost Jade Peacock, as the false emotion fake will Gu let out a yellow light that resembled a fog, gradually enshrouding Hei Lou Lan, Ma Hong Yun and the Frost Jade Peacock.

Chapter 614: Otherworldly Demon!

"Listen to my instructions. Hold your breath, be calm, be relaxed, and discard any superfluous thoughts..." Giant Sun's will spoke in a pensive tone.

Hei Lou Lan closed his eyes and slowed his breathing.

Zhao Lian Yun and Chang Li stood to the sides and did not dare to speak.

A light breeze blew, and the tree leaves rustled, creating a tranquil atmosphere.

Ma Hong Yun looked left and right. Suddenly seeing the Frost Jade Peacock, he was amazed, shouting: "Look quickly, the peacock is alive, it actually shed tears!"

The tranquil atmosphere was disrupted, and the voice of Giant Sun's will's stopped. Hei Lou Lan held his irritation, and angrily opened his eyes. He berated: "Nonsense, of course the land spirit is alive. When the land spirit dies, the blessed land will be finished as well. Why do you care if it is shedding tears or not, quickly follow the instructions!"

"Oh, oh. So, it's like this, my bad, my bad." Ma Hong Yun was shocked by the Black Tyrant's anger, he nodded quickly.

"Concentrate, clear your mind, don't think excessively, this is the best way to display false emotion fake will Gu's power to its limit." Giant Sun's will continued to instruct.

Hei Lou Lan closed both of his eyes and breathed gently, a light breeze blew, bringing with it the sweet fragrance of vegetation.

"Wait a moment, wait a moment!" Ma Hong Yun suddenly screamed.

"You despicable fellow, are you courting death!" Hei Lou Lan clenched his fist, an immense rage was building in his heart, he was outraged and anxious.

"Old ancestor, I am a man, he is also a man. Creating feelings between the two of us, I... I am unable to accept it!" Ma Hong Yun was afraid of Hei Lou Lan's terrifying aura, he whispered while being on guard against Hei Lou Lan, pleading with Giant Sun's will.

"You scoundrel..." Hei Lou Lan gnashed his teeth and clenched his fist until they made cracking noises, his eyes revealing an ominous glint.

Were it not for Giant Sun's will being right by his side, according to his brutal nature, he would have already sent a punch over, blowing Ma Hong Yun's brains out.

"Idiot! Saving the blessed land is the most urgent matter right now. So what if you're both men, just be free and relax, there will not be a problem! I will always support you!!" Zhao Lian Yun called out, she was fearful of Hei Lou Lan, yet simultaneously her eyes showed some unexplainable excitement.

"That's right, husband, look at the big picture, I... I do not mind it," Chang Li spoke softly in agreement.

Ma Hong Yun rolled his eyes and shouted: "Hey, this does not involve you so you can talk about it casually! Old Ancestor, I have an idea, how about you let me and my wife do it. Our love is genuine and sincere, you can even save up on using the false emotion fake will Gu."

Ma Hong Yun was straightforward, not giving much thought to the complex circumstances.

As far as Giant Sun's will was concerned, not using false emotion fake will Gu was out of the question.

Hei Lou Lan's killing intent burst out, Ma Hong Yun's proposal greatly encroached on his benefits, his anger was about to explode, almost reaching his limit, but he did not dare to attack in the presence of Giant Sun's will, he did not dare to flare up.

As expected, Giant Sun's will rejected Ma Hong Yun's proposal: "Boy, you are too young, true love, is it so easy to find? When calamity strikes, all the birds fly in different directions, human couples are also the same. Do you think this young lady truly loves you? Hehehe."

The words of Giant Sun's will made Chang Li's complexion pale.

Indeed, Chang Li had never sincerely loved Ma Hong Yun, originally, she was looked upon as a political bargaining chip by Chang Biao and delivered to Ma Tribe, intended to be used to form good bonds with Ma Ying Jie, but in the end, Chang Biao died, and Chang Li lost her backing. She could only accept her fate and stay by Ma Hong Yun's side.

Fortunately, Ma Hong Yun could cultivate to rank three, becoming a Ma Tribe elder, the resources he had available to him were incomparable to before, and as he also had Ma Ying Jie's trust, he could provide Chang Li with a good life.

Ma Hong Yun was to become one of Imperial Court blessed land's owners, and since he was close to Chang Li and Zhao Lian Yun, Giant Sun's will began to investigate them.

His investigative method was simple, direct, and effective.

He separated a portion of his will, and ventured into Chang Li and Zhao Lian Yun's minds, looking over their memories and thoughts.

With True Yang Building's support, along with the method of an Immortal Venerable, Chang Li and Zhao Lian Yun were not even aware that, at this time, each of their secrets were rapidly being learned by Giant Sun's will.

"Old Ancestor, what do you mean?" Ma Hong Yun pursed his eyebrows, he was foolish and brazen, while Hei Lou Lan did not dare to offend Giant Sun's will, he dared to ask a direct question.

Giant Sun's will laughed: "You are indeed a fool, boy. Your mind isn't that sharp, but it is excusable, I will now give you a lesson. This little wife of yours approached you with an ulterior motive, her adoptive father deliberately ordered her to come. Even your heroic action of saving this beauty was merely a show."

Chang Li's complexion immediately turned deathly pale and she trembled from head to toe.

Hei Lou Lan was indifferent, he was already accustomed to these dirty political games.

"How could that be?" Ma Hong Yun's eyes widened, unable to believe this.

Giant Son's will then said: "And there is also your little female companion, called Zhao Lian Yun. Hehe, she had matured young and gained some wisdom, she was forced by circumstances to had no choice but to be with you. From the very beginning she had looked down on you, only wanting to protect herself... Of course, now that you have grown stronger, she has gradually become dependent on you."

Zhao Lian Yun's heart went cold, her thoughts were exposed on the spot, making her feel extremely unpleasant, as if the clothes on her body had been forcibly stripped off by someone.

But facing Giant Sun's will, she did not dare to refute anything. She wasn't a normal child, she was a transmigrator, the suffering she had experienced in this life had made her aware of the mystery and cruelty of this world.

"Eh!?" Suddenly, Giant Sun's will's words came to a stop, and his image in the air showed an expression of shock and fear with his eyes wide open.

"To think, to think that!" Giant Sun's will's tone changed abruptly, he stared at Zhao Lian Yun with a hateful gaze, causing her to take a few steps back in fear.

"To think that you are an otherworldly demon! You are actually lurking by Ma Hong Yun's side! Hehehe, you have such guts, you are really daring. Unfortunately... you met me." Giant Sun's will exuded a strong killing intent.

"Otherworldly demon, what is that?" Hei Lou Lan was astonished, as it was his first time hearing this term despite his status and experience.

He looked at Zhao Lian Yun but could not see anything extraordinary about her.

"Old Ancestor, what are you trying to do!" Ma Hong Yun, no matter how stupid, could recognize something was wrong.

He sprinted to the front of Zhao Lian Yun, spreading both of his arms, protecting her behind his body.

"Boy, you want to protect an otherworldly demon?" Giant Sun's will raised his tone, his expression becoming ice-cold.

"What otherworldly demon! I don't know any otherworldly demon, I only know she is Lady Xiao Yun, without her help, I would likely have been killed already." Ma Hong Yun tried his best to defend Zhao Lian Yun.

Giant Sun's will shook his head and sneered. He had no interest in explaining, yet for some reason, he had to explain: "Killed? Boy, you are a person destined to become a Gu Immortal. Had she not helped you, there would definitely have been others who would have given you assistance. Otherworldly demons are enemies of the entire world, they are a huge menace! If we let them grow, the consequences would be unthinkable. In the past, there was an otherworldly demon who managed to grow successfully, the five regions were almost destroyed as a result!"

Hei Lou Lan's eyes widened.

The words of Giant Sun's will were too sensational. Listening to his words, it seemed as if the otherworldly demons could rival rank nine venerables.

How was it possible?

But the one who said these words was someone Hei Lou Lan had no choice but to believe.

For a moment, Hei Lou Lan looked Zhao Lian Yun in the eyes, killing intent emerging.

"No, Lady Xiao Yun is innocent, you must not harm her!" Ma Hong Yun was extremely determined, he wholeheartedly wanted to protect Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun was stunned.

She looked towards Ma Hong Yun's lonely and powerless back, her eyes glistening with tears.

She did not know what bullshit otherworldly demons were, but could surmise that perhaps it was related to her own transmigration.

She forced herself to wipe her tears, the corners of her lips raising into a determined arc.

Since Ma Hong Yun wholeheartedly defended her, disregarding his own life, she consequently must not implicate Ma Hong Yun!

She took a step forward, stopping in front of Ma Hong Yun, she looked at Giant Sun's will, speaking resoundingly: "You want to take my life, come and take it."

"Good." Giant Sun's will had a ferocious smile, killing intent boiling with no trace of sympathy.

He was a huge will congealed by special will Gu, the difference between special wills and other wills were that: they could be given a special command by the Gu Master that would be triggered if specific circumstances were met.

And Giant Sun's will, during its formation, was given a profound resolve by the main body —— if it discovered an otherworldly demon, no matter the circumstances, killing the otherworldly demon must take priority!

Giant Sun's will had to kill Zhao Lian Yun, to have been able to restrain himself until now was already really remarkable.

"No——! Ma Hong Yun saw the situation going south, he shouted out in a moment of desperation, extending both his arms and hugged Zhao Lian Yun within his bosom.

"Otherworldly demon, you deserve to die without pity!" Giant Sun's will sneered, and started to make his move.

Yet the next moment, his expression became rigid, and shortly after he faced towards the sky and bellowed: "Damn it——!"

The roaring voice suddenly came to a spontaneous end, and the image of the will abruptly disappeared in mid-air.

Giant Sun's will could sense a formidable, hard to resist force, that pulled it outside of the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"What is going on?"

"What happened?!"

No matter if it was Hei Lou Lan or Ma Hong Yun, both stared blankly at the spot, surprised by the turn of events.

Just a moment ago, Giant Sun's will was still brilliant and mighty, how could he suddenly disappear?

Outside the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the golden speckles of the majestic will enveloped the entire True Yang Building.

Rumble!

Large amounts of chaotic lightning balls bombarded in succession, the lightning balls could cause one to sink into confusion and in essence attacked wills.

Giant Sun's will was restrained by the chaotic lightning balls, in no time the explosions put him in a tough spot, a portion of his will was damaged and destroyed.

Meanwhile, the restraining smoke took advantage of the situation, swallowing up the pieces of Giant Sun's will.

Giant Sun's will really was too majestic, though the outer shell suffered the bombardment of the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, the inner layer desperately tried to enter the building.

Eighty-Eight True Yang building, presided over by Giant Sun's will, was now an empty building, although the structure was intact, the Gu worms stopped functioning.

Like an army of soldiers suddenly losing their commander-in-chief, they can only rely on their instincts to act.

At this moment, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had become exceptionally fragile.

Chapter 615: We are fellow apprentice brothers!

"You little pest, I will kill you!"

Giant Sun's will was naturally furious at being subjected to such a scheme once again.

A portion of the majestic will was immediately sent flooding towards the distant Fang Yuan.

However, this torrential portion of will was weathered down by the chaotic lightning balls and restraining smoke in the inner layer, shrinking by thirty percent. And after being ground down by the outer layer's blizzard, it decreased by another twenty percent.

By the time it approached Fang Yuan, it had already been reduced by more than half.

"This can only last for about fifteen minutes." Fang Yuan turned a blind eye to the rapidly approaching attack, his mind was cool as ice, as he silently estimated the duration of this third method.

His thoughts moved while tightly clenching the glass owner token, and the next moment, he teleported inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

This was a feature of the glass owner token.

Fang Yuan had been able to move in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building without anyone knowing of it, because of this.

He appeared on an ice mountain, causing the torrential will to strike empty air.

It was a scene of white, the icy-cold wind brushed past his face.

Grrr!

Three-eyed snow rabbits, at the size of adult men, with bulging muscles, drilled out from the depths of the snowy land, surrounding Fang Yuan in a few moments!

This was the round that Tai Bai Yun Sheng had been transported to in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The snow rabbits kept on appearing endlessly and soon there were tens of thousands of them glaring at Fang Yuan.

Just based on close-quarter combat capability, these snow rabbits did not lose to wind wolves or turtleback wolves. Under the environment of ice and snow, their battle strength even surpassed ordinary wolves.

The large numbers of wild Gu living in their body further increased their ferocity.

One had to spend a lot of time and energy to break through their obstruction.

But Fang Yuan was in control of the glass owner token and did not need to use such a forceful method.

His thoughts moved and the glass owner token gave a faint glimmer.

The crowd of snow rabbits suddenly appeared to be at a loss, their killing intent instantly dissipating.

Fang Yuan waved his hand and they dispersed in confusion, drilling into the thick snowy ground, and before long, they were gone.

Fang Yuan was able to control many floors of True Yang Building with the glass owner token. He had intentionally held back before and did not use up the quota completely, saving several uses for later. Right now, he used it and immediately obtained control over this floor.

Without the obstruction of Giant Sun's will, he was this round's true controller and it was very easy for him to disperse these snow rabbits.

Crack...

A glacier split open, revealing a tunnel.

The tunnel directly extended down the inner part of the ice mountain.

Fang Yuan moved quickly in this tunnel and soon saw Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was sealed inside an ice block, seemingly in a deep sleep.

He had been bombarded by chaotic lightning balls when he tried to pass the tribulations before, his mind sunk into chaos and he was not able to think. Thus, he was easily absorbed into the tower by Giant Sun's will.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was not of Giant Sun's bloodline, and moreover was a Gu Immortal, therefore he could not be easily controlled. To prevent him from causing trouble and to seize the moment to handle the land spirit, Giant Sun's will took advantage of this to seal him here.

With a thought from Fang Yuan, the ice block dissolved and Tai Bai Yun Sheng slowly woke up.

"Chang Shan Yin..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng gradually regained his consciousness, he glanced around and recalled, before gazing at Fang Yuan.

Although he found Fang Yuan's cruel way of doing things very repugnant, he was grateful at this moment: "You saved me?"

Fang Yuan arrogantly smiled: "If not me, who else could it be? Tai Bai Yun Sheng, do you know you are facing imminent catastrophe?"

"Imminent catastrophe?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed, but he was a famed character and was not scared by Fang Yuan's frightening words.

Instead, he slowly stood up and lightly smiled at Fang Yuan: "Please explain."

Fang Yuan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng with indignance and explained: "I was ordered by master to infiltrate into True Yang Building and release the seals on the land spirit, to overturn True Yang Building and take control of Imperial Court blessed land! Master gave me a glass owner token which can use three methods to deal with Giant Sun's will. But something unexpected happened midway, you suddenly advanced to a Gu Immortal and it was used by Giant Sun's will to weaken the land spirit, leading to the current peril. Did you think you were favored by Giant Sun's will? Hmph, he was only using you to protect True Yang Building! Now that you have lost your value, you were sealed up, and if not for me saving you, you would definitely fall into the control of Giant Sun's will, and end up in extreme misery!"

"What?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's brows furrowed as he revealed a bewildered expression. Fang Yuan's words not only contained a lot of information but also were very impactful.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng stared at Fang Yuan, his gaze flashing with a bright light as his brows furrowed deeper: "I had been doubting why I suddenly received the help of Giant Sun's will, but later absorbed into True Yang Building and sealed up for no reason. Your words explain everything. But if so, who are you? Why did you save me? You might have released me from imprisonment, but it doesn't mean I will believe you unconditionally!"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Who am I? Look carefully!"

He then took a step back and right in front of Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he used a knife to slowly cut his skin starting from his forehead.

A bloodstain extended down to his stomach, following the tip of the knife.

"What are you...?!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was shocked.

Fang Yuan chuckled, he then held the knife behind his head and cut downwards. Using his hands in turn, he cut down a long wound smoothly.

The two long wounds soon exuded scarlet blood.

An intense pain attacked him, but Fang Yuan's expression did not change.

Next, he started slicing at his arms, thighs and other crucial areas.

His hand was steady as a rock during the whole process, his expression was indifferent as if the one being cut was not him but someone else, not expressing even a trace of pain.

"What are you doing?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt a chill down his spine and took a step back, doubts forming in his mind.

But the next moment, his pupils shrunk and his shock could not be concealed on his face.

He saw Fang Yuan clenching his teeth and peeling his skin off like stripping clothes.

His movement was neat and efficient, there was almost not even an inch of skin remaining on his whole body. Like a blood monster, there was only a terrifying human shape with scarlet muscles and snow white teeth left behind.

Next, Fang Yuan activated healing Gu.

Under the emerald light, new tender skin started to grow over his body.

The skin gradually covered all his body and after the emerald light dispersed, the one before Tai Bai Yun Sheng was Fang Yuan with his real appearance.

"Ahh! So you were not Chang Shan Yin, but were just disguised as him. You, who are you?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng might have a benevolent character, but he was not foolish; he immediately realized the truth when he saw this scene.

His heart was filled with extreme trepidation.

Looking at Fang Yuan in front of him, he saw the appearance of an ordinary youth, but the presence he emitted was beyond ordinary, especially that pair of dark eyes, like an ancient lake with unfathomable depths.

He was giving off the intense aura of rank five peak stage, his gaze as chilling as a knife's edge; Tai Bai Yun Sheng had seen countless people and one look at Fang Yuan told him, the latter was a genius character who was lofty, resolute and did not fear any challenges.

Even in all his life, the number of such people Tai Bai Yun Sheng had seen could be counted with his fingers.

"Who am I?" Fang Yuan chuckled, the corners of his lips curled up to reveal a smile, his expression was proud and vivid.

His burning gaze looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng, his tone serious, containing an earnestness that made people want to subconsciously believe in them: "My true name is Fang Yuan, I came to northern plains from central continent because of an important assignment from master, we are fellow disciples."

"Fang Yuan? Fellow disciple?" Shocked and astonished feelings attacked Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mind: "What do you mean?"

"Hmph, you don't even understand the meaning of fellow disciple? It means my master and your benefactor is the same person, our relation is of fellow apprentices!" Fang Yuan's brows furrowed and his tone revealed some impatience.

There was no language barrier between Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Fang Yuan, he naturally understood the term, but he was not able to accept the great significance of it at this moment.

After he heard Fang Yuan's explanation, an image appeared in his mind.

It was an image of an old beggar.

With disheveled purple-red hair, occasionally he was insane, occasionally he was in a stupor, but when he was clear-headed, his gaze revealed one who had experienced vicissitudes over time and an awe-inspiring aura manifested in him.

When he was young, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had given the old beggar a bowl of water out of kindness.

When the old beggar became clear-headed, he gave Tai Bai Yun Sheng three Gu Immortal inheritances to choose from. The young Tai Bai Yun Sheng chose the third inheritance in the end.

This was the most profound memory in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life and he had never forgotten it in all his life.

Many times, he had recalled the old beggar's image.

It was him who saved the lost Tai Bai Yun Sheng, pulling Tai Bai Yun Sheng from his lowest point. It could even be said the old beggar created Tai Bai Yun Sheng. Without the old beggar's help, there would not have been the current Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Master..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng mumbled, he had always regarded the old beggar as his supreme benefactor!

His whole body involuntarily trembled.

He had tried to scout out the traces of the old beggar, and had never given up on this. But so many years had gone by and he had almost roamed the whole of northern plains without making any progress in his search.

The old beggar was mysterious; suddenly appearing before disappearing again.

Now when Tai Bai Yun Sheng suddenly heard of the news of his benefactor, his heart was filled with excitement, joy and naturally was even more in disbelief.

"Listen well." Fang Yuan pointed at Tai Bai Yun Sheng and spoke bluntly, "Benefactor's name is Purple Mountain True Monarch, master has six great disciples. I, Fang Yuan, am ranked at fifth, I cultivate strength and enslavement path, both are from Gu Immortal inheritances."

"Purple Mountain True Monarch, Purple Mountain True Monarch..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng pondered over Fang Yuan's fabricated name like a treasure, his mind involuntarily thinking of the old beggar's disheveled purple hair.

"Master doesn't care about his appearance and likes to wander around, exploring the unknown. Before I came to northern plains, I heard him mention you and how he gave you three choices but you chose the most useless time path inheritance. Hmph, if it had been me, I would definitely choose the first inheritance, that fire path inheritance that could burn seas and mountains, it has such extreme power." Fang Yuan's tone was filled with anger, yearning and regret, his expression was sincere and vivid as if this had really happened.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mind shook. He had never mentioned this experience to outsiders. Fang Yuan, however, described the situation back then so accurately!

He naturally did not know Fang Yuan had once searched his soul to confirm if he had landscape as before Immortal Gu recipe.

"Then, you, you are my apprentice brother?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze towards Fang Yuan was a whole lot different now.

"Hmph!" Fang Yuan twitched his mouth in dissatisfaction, "At most, you can only barely qualify as a disciple in name, benefactor has actually taken in many disciples, but they cannot be compared to legacy disciples like me. But according to master's rule, as long as a disciple in name can advance to a Gu Immortal, they can become his legacy disciple. According to ranking, you are my... uhh... that... fifth senior brother."

"Huh?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's brows slightly furrowed.

"Hmph, what are you being proud for! It is only because of your Gu Immortal identity, that you are ranked ahead of me." Fang Yuan coldly looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng, "Wait till I become a Gu Immortal, with my enslavement and strength path dual cultivation, I will push you down and I will be your fifth senior brother! But looking at your elderly appearance, you clearly don't have much lifespan. I might not even need to become a Gu Immortal, I just have to wait for you to die of old age."

Fang Yuan's attitude was extremely rude, even revealing obvious resentment.

This was where the brilliance of his plan lied.

If he just spoke eloquent words and made a vow, that might not make Tai Bai Yun Sheng believe him too much. But it was because his words contained an attitude of rejection and also deep emotions, that made Tai Bai Yun Sheng quietly put down his guard and gradually choose to believe him.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng might be quite old, but his experience paled in comparison to Fang Yuan who had five hundred years of experience in his previous life.

Fang Yuan did not openly explain but using just a few words, he made Tai Bai Yun Sheng interpret the whole story himself and see a glance of his master's origin.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng muttered: "Then, sixth junior brother..."

Fang Yuan immediately put out his hand: "Don't call me that, I am not close to you! My task had been going smoothly but it was destroyed by you. Do you know how much time master had spent to make all the arrangements in Imperial Court blessed land? Now, the situation has changed like this, how do I explain it to master? You can just call me Fang Yuan!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was not angry at Fang Yuan's interruption, instead a guilty feeling emerged in his heart; he chuckled and cupped his fists towards Fang Yuan, asking sincerely: "Then... Fang Yuan, things have already reached this point, how should I help you to recoup the losses for master as much as possible?"

Success.

"Hehehe, spectacular, this is too spectacular, kid! You are truly insidious, tsk tsk, swindling a Gu Immortal to your side using just a few words!" Mo Yao had all along been observing this, and at this moment, she could not help revealing herself in Fang Yuan's mind to praise him.

Fang Yuan sneered inwardly, on the surface however, he showed an unhappy expression: "Heh, after such a long time, you have finally spoken sense! Master has a discerning eye, he did not nurture a thankless wretch. Knowing to repay kindness is a trait we should have. Hmm... the situation right now is very bad, the crucial thing is there is not much time left. I have already used the third method master left behind, you must cooperate with me now. It will all depend on the two of us!"

"Please instruct me." Tai Bai Yun Sheng bowed.

"First use this." Fang Yuan grinned and tossed out a fifteen year lifespan Gu.

"This!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed, an astonished expression appearing on his face at the sight of this lifespan Gu.

"Use it, you may have Immortal Gu Man as Before, but that thing expends a lot of immortal essence. I don't want you to suddenly end up dead at the crucial moment." Fang Yuan spoke viciously, with an indifferent expression.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng instead felt a warm feeling in his heart. In his previous five hundred years of life, Fang Yuan's grasp of the human heart was able to reach to pinnacle after experiencing many trials and hardships..

"This lifespan Gu..."

"My glass owner token can control only a small number of the rounds. True Yang Building only has a single lifespan Gu, quickly use it, stop wasting time!"

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not use it, he kept it in his pocket.

He thought of Gao Yang and Zhu Zai.

Until now, he was still feeling guilty.

The lifespan Gu in his hand had a scent of blood that was very familiar to him.

"What is going on with you?" Fang Yuan acted furious, pretending not to know.

"There are reasons..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyelids drooped, he raised his gaze, looking at Fang Yuan with a determined look: "All in all, don't worry, I can provide you the greatest assistance!"

Fang Yuan grabbed onto Tai Bai Yun Sheng, gritting his teeth: "Bastard, do you know that I disregarded the consequences in using the glass owner token just to obtain this lifespan Gu?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was silent, his expression was gentle as jade, but he was very determined.

Fang Yuan's words made his heart feel great warmth, his last lingering trace of suspicion vanished like smoke.

After looking at each other for a while, Fang Yuan seemed to have felt Tai Bai Yun Sheng's determination as he retracted his gaze: "Hmph, if you did not become a Gu Immortal and are also a legacy disciple, I would not care if you died. Alright, according to the details of your inheritance and your tribulation performance, you should have the Immortal Gu Landscape as Before now, right?"

"Mm." Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded: "Yes, that is correct."

Fang Yuan's eyes shone, his mouth cracked open to show his snow-white teeth, he did not conceal his joy: "Very good, come with me!"

Saying so, a large number of starlight firefly Gu flew out of his aperture.

"Oh, that's right, hold these two for me, put it on your aperture, I cannot bring them along." Fang Yuan tossed casually.

"Immortal Gu!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's pupils shrunk.

A moment later, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Fang Yuan entered Hu Immortal blessed land using the stargate.

Chapter 616: Repairing Dang Hun mountain

"Master, you are finally back!" Little Hu Immortal was already waiting before the stargate and when Fang Yuan appeared, she immediately jumped towards him and hugged his leg, rubbing it with her cute rosy cheeks.

"Hehe, you have worked hard during these days when I was not here." Fang Yuan smiled warmly and lightly stroked Little Hu Immortal's head.

Little Hu Immortal's fox ears shivered slightly, a blissful expression appeared on her face and her snow-white tail started shaking lightly behind her.

"This is... a land spirit? So this is a blessed land!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng stepped out of the stargate closely after Fang Yuan, and was startled at seeing Little Hu Immortal.

He had heard Little Hu Immortal addressing Fang Yuan as 'master'.

Fang Yuan was only a mortal, but he already possessed a blessed land! In history, there were some people who had such fortune. The most famous one was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. He had luckily inherited Imperial Court blessed land when he was still just a mortal. And in his later cultivation journey, Imperial Court blessed land was of huge assistance.

"Haha, this blessed land's name is Hu Immortal blessed land. I seized it forcibly from several sects of central continent, under master's order." Fang Yuan proudly replied.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze immediately changed.

There was a difference between immortal and mortal, but right now, he was looking at Fang Yuan as an equal, asking: "I would assume that the process of snatching this blessed land was very dangerous, right?"

"Naturally, even now when I think of it, I still have some lingering fear." Fang Yuan laughed heartily, "But in the end, winner takes all, everything is just that simple. I obtained the blessed land, becoming the final winner. The greater the risk, the greater the profits!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded, sighing inwardly: this profit is simply too immense!

A blessed land with a land spirit was the immortal aperture of a fallen Gu Immortal. Possessing such a blessed land was akin to inheriting the Gu Immortal's immortal aperture and cultivation resources!

Simultaneously, the impression of Fang Yuan's audacious nature deepened by another level in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mind.

"Master, who is he? His aura is strong." Little Hu Immortal sensed Tai Bai Yun Sheng brimming with Gu Immortal aura. She could not help but be tense, gripping on Fang Yuan's pants, appearing somewhat nervous and on guard.

"Relax, he is on our side, and is here to help us save Dang Hun mountain." Fang Yuan comforted Little Hu Immortal, "Take us to Dang Hun mountain."

Little Hu Immortal's eyes brightened upon hearing this. She trusted her master's words unconditionally.

She immediately let down her guard and disappeared on the spot, taking Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng with her.

The next moment, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were teleported to the center of the blessed land, the location of Dang Hun mountain.

Dang Hun mountain had already been deformed completely from the corrosion of Gruel Mud. Only a small mound remained of the lofty Dang Hun mountain.

Dang Hun Palace, which was on Dang Hun mountain previously, had naturally been destroyed.

"Master, if you arrived any later, you would not have been able to see Dang Hun mountain." Little Hu Immortal said with a sorrowful voice.

Fang Yuan lightly petted her head, then looked towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a smart man and from this scene along with Fang Yuan's previous words, he could guess Fang Yuan's intention in bringing him here.

He nodded towards Fang Yuan, before taking out landscape as before Gu from his aperture.

Immediately, the surging aura of an Immortal Gu filled the surroundings.

"This is?" Little Hu Immortal's bright eyes opened wide upon this first encounter with landscape as before Gu.

Landscape as before Gu was like a ladybug, it was the size of a fist and had the color of green jade.

Its round shell was engraved with natural patterns; half of the patterns portrayed rivers and lakes that twisted and turned, flowing continuously, while the other half was of mountains and hills, precipitous and overlaid upon one another.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng gave a soft shout; a bead of green grape immortal essence turned into a stream of light that instantly poured into landscape as before Gu.

The Immortal Gu suddenly burst out with green jade light that soared to an extreme height, giving off a radiance that people could not look at intently.

The light radiance covered the remaining Dang Hun mountain.

The corrosion of Gruel Mud on Dang Hun mountain immediately paused under the illumination of the green light. Immortal Gu Gruel Mud's power was quickly neutralized and then vanquished.

The green light gradually dimmed; Tai Bai Yun Sheng then threw in another bead of green grape immortal essence.

The green light brightened again, covering the devastated Dang Hun mountain and continually cleansing it.

The small mound sized Dang Hun mountain started to grow and strengthen at a visible speed under the radiance.

"Dang Hun mountain is changing back!" Little Hu Immortal clapped her little hands, prancing around happily.

But the good scene did not last long, Dang Hun mountain only recovered by twenty percent when the green light weakened again.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed slightly: "What kind of mountain is this? It actually exhausted a green grape immortal essence!"

He was able to create thirty-six green grape immortal essence beads in his ascension to Gu Immortal. But later, using movement Gu crazily to dodge chaotic lightning balls expended one bead of immortal essence. Then in his own immortal aperture, to resist the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity after the formation of Immortal Gu, he had continuously activated landscape as before Gu to restore his aperture to its previous condition, spending three whole beads on it.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a clear understanding of how precious immortal essence was; now he had just started to restore Dang Hun mountain but had used up two beads of immortal essence.

At this rate, he would have to at least expend five to six beads of green grape immortal essence!

Fang Yuan smiled: "Dang Hun mountain."

"Dang Hun mountain?" When Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard the name, his expression underwent a great change, his eyes opened wide and he spoke with a shocked tone, "Could it be?"

"It is indeed the one in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, how could there be another Dang Hun mountain?" Fang Yuan laughed.

"To think, to think I would actually be able to see the legendary Dang Hun mountain! This is the sacred land of soul path cultivators that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had praised endlessly." Tai Bai Yun Sheng was extremely moved as he kept on exclaiming in admiration.

It was the first time even for him to witness a thing of such legend.

When he glanced at Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze had another subtle change.

He did not say anything else but quietly used a third bead of immortal essence to maintain the activation of landscape as before Gu.

This time, Dang Hun mountain was restored to forty percent before the green light dimmed.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng used a fourth bead, then a fifth bead and finally a sixth bead before Dang Hun mountain fully recovered.

"It is truly Dang Hun mountain, requiring six whole beads of green grape immortal essence to recover completely." Tai Bai Yun Sheng mumbled while looking at the tall mountain in front of him.

Dang Hun mountain was magnificently beautiful; ordinary mountains could not even compare to it.

It was a pink crystal mountain, emitting an unforgettably dreamy radiance.

"Mast... Master, Dang Hun mountain's disease has been treated." Little Hu Immortal's eyes had turned red, "Sob sob sob...."

She cried tears of joy, before lowering her head and using her delicate little hands to wipe the tears.

Fang Yuan also let out a breath of turbid air when he gazed at Dang Hun mountain.

Now, the objective for infiltrating into northern plains was finally achieved!

So many days and nights of effort, taking risks in the battlefields, disguising, racking his brains to scheme; they were all not in vain.

At this moment, a soaring fire burned in Fang Yuan's heart.

This burning fire had a name — ambition!

Restoring Dang Hun mountain could no longer satisfy his appetite. There were still opportunities left in Imperial Court blessed land!

Especially now, Giant Sun's will was expelled out of the tower; Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had become akin to an ownerless object.

Even if false emotion fake will Gu was an Immortal Gu and was difficult to capture, Fang Yuan had used his silver tongue to obtain Tai Bai Yun Sheng's trust, succeeding in roping in the crucial battle power that could influence the situation.

When the time comes, using a Gu Immortal's will, forcefully refining false emotion fake will Gu was not an impossible matter.

"Let's go, back to northern plains." Fang Yuan came and left just as quickly, with Tai Bai Yun Sheng in tow.

Before leaving, he handed burial soul toad to Little Hu Immortal.

Burial soul toad was a storage Gu used to store souls. There were souls of humans and beasts, and they had mostly been gathered by Fang Yuan from the battlefields.

These would turn into large numbers of guts Gu through Dang Hun mountain.

When they returned to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the starlight firefly Gu supporting the stargate were already spent by over half; Fang Yuan quickly stored what remained into his aperture.

It was extremely difficult to accumulate starlight firefly Gu. The current amount could only support one more activation of the stargate.

"We are back again." Tai Bai Yun Sheng was deeply moved.

In this trip, he had directly gone from northern plains to central continent and back to northern plains from central continent. It was truly a travel disregarding distance, he felt like he was free to go anywhere in the world!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had only heard of hole earth Gu and connecting heaven Gu in methods that could allow one to connect between blessed lands and grotto-heavens; he had never heard of the method Fang Yuan used.

"Probably only people like sixth junior brother are worthy of such mystical methods. Maybe this was imparted to him by master." Tai Bai Yun Sheng trusted Fang Yuan even more after the trip to Hu Immortal blessed land.

Fang Yuan was only a mortal at the moment, but he possessed a blessed land, this by itself was sufficient to prove many issues.

Dang Hun mountain's magnificent scene was even more deeply imprinted in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mind.

Seeing is believing!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had no choice but to believe it.

Fang Yuan first revealed his true appearance, then used lifespan Gu, revealing secret information to obtain Tai Bai Yun Sheng's trust. Fang Yuan had also resolved the doubt in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart — why True Yang Building had helped him endure the tribulation for no rhyme or reason.

Fang Yuan's words and the evidence he showed to Tai Bai Yun Sheng were almost all true, except the lies at the crucial points.

Nine truths and one lie; the lie would eventually become the truth. Especially when this lie involved the deepest secret of Tai Bai Yun Sheng. Tai Bai Yun Sheng had never revealed it to outsiders while Fang Yuan knew it by soul searching.

Among all these, the true marvel lied in Fang Yuan grasping Tai Bai Yun Sheng's psychology completely.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had been feeling extreme guilt after betraying Gao Yang and Zhu Zai; he denied the value of his own existence. Under stimulation, he went through Gu Immortal ascension and even charged towards tribulation, thinking of ending it all.

But when he successfully passed the tribulation and became a Gu Immortal, he stood at a whole new height, looking at a different scene.

His mind came back to life, and after passing the tribulation with much difficulty as well as getting his immortal aperture blessed land, he did not want to die anymore.

He wanted to make a fresh start.

But he had an unresolved matter tugging his heart.

He needed hope, he needed acknowledgement!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng himself was not aware of this psychological need. But Fang Yuan was aware and gave him this acknowledgement.

Fang Yuan's acknowledgement, in a certain way, represented his master's acknowledgement.

And Tai Bai Yun Sheng respected his benefactor deeply. His master's acknowledgement made him feel there was value in him being alive. A mysterious force and a completely new environment attracted his interest.

He had been at the peak of mortals and had experienced all that the mortal world could provide, but in the journey of immortals, he was a child that had just begun to move.

The fifteen year lifespan Gu was in his pocket. He was no longer worried and guilty. He chose to believe Fang Yuan, not only because Fang Yuan explained everything and there were not many pieces of evidence he could contest, but even more importantly —

In the very depths of his heart, he wanted to believe in Fang Yuan!

Every single person who was cheated, was it because they were stupid?

No, it was only because they wanted to believe in it from the depths of their heart.

"Here, your Immortal Gu." Tai Bai Yun Sheng tossed Fixed Immortal Travel and flying bear phantom Gu to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan nonchalantly accepted them; this casual attitude towards Immortal Gu caused another ripple in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart and trust.

But he received a great shock when Fang Yuan brought out the glass owner token, as at the next moment, he appeared in another round.

Tall and ancient trees were everywhere. Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were within a dense forest.

Roars and howls interlinked together, giant trees pulled out their roots and stood up, turning into tall treemen.

Within a few moments, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were surrounded by treemen one after another.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a grim expression; one treeman was nothing to him, but the number of treemen here was extremely astonishing, and to completely exterminate them would require him to pay a significant price.

But the next moment, Fang Yuan lightly waved his glass owner token, and this round immediately became under his control.

The treemen stopped moving forward, their killing intent gone as if it was never there.

While Tai Bai Yun Sheng was wearing a stupefied expression, Fang Yuan grabbed his arm and directly teleported in front of Hei Lou Lan and Ma Hong Yun.

There was already an enormous change in the situation here.

Frost Jade Peacock was half-lying on the ground, with Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun turtling up under its wings. Surrounding it were layers after layers of treemen unfolding mad attacks.

Hei Lou Lan was fighting nearby with false emotion fake will Gu resting on his shoulder.

He blocked the attacks of the treemen while also launching attacks at Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun at the same time.

But these attacks were blocked by the light barrier from Frost Jade Peacock before they could even reach their targets.

"Lord Hei Lou Lan, you are also being attacked by the treemen, your situation is the same as ours! We have neither hatred nor grievance between us, why must you try to kill us?" Ma Hong Yun shouted.

Hei Lou Lan snorted: "Didn't you hear what old ancestor said? Your girl is an otherworldly demon with a mysterious background and will be a cause of endless disasters, she must be eliminated! Who knows if she and the Chang Shan Yin impersonator are on the same side! Old ancestor was about to attack her just earlier, but suddenly disappeared due to some mishap. You have Giant Sun's bloodline, you are a person of northern plains; you are actually not able to distinguish right and wrong, you dare to shield an otherworldly demon!"

Ma Hong Yun was furious and immediately retorted: "She is not an otherworldly demon that you all claim, she is innocent! Lord Hei Lou Lan, don't waste your strength in vain, we have already received the land spirit's recognition; with the land spirit with us, you can't kill us!"

When Giant Sun's will was thrown out of the tower, this round did not have any controller and operated by itself; the treemen treated the land spirit, Ma Hong Yun and others as challengers challenging the round.

Hei Lou Lan wanted to kill Zhao Lian Yun in place of Giant Sun's will. Ma Hong Yun was ready to give up his life to save her, which strongly shook Zhao Lian Yun's heart and she started feeling true love for him.

Ma Hong Yun had already treated Zhao Lian Yun with earnest feelings; the two loved each other, and the land spirit acknowledged them as its masters by its own accord.

In this dangerous situation, the land spirit raised a defensive barrier around them, protecting them from the fatal attacks of the treemen and Hei Lou Lan.

As for Chang Li, she had already died miserably under the attacks of the treemen.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng appeared on the crown of a treeman, observing the battle situation.

"Ma Hong Yun... he actually obtained the land spirit's recognition. Hmph, this kid's dogshit luck is truly powerful." Fang Yuan mumbled with a complex expression.

"You know him?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was somewhat astonished as he had not thought the grand Fang Yuan would actually recognize this rank three initial stage minor character.

"It is you!" Hei Lou Lan quickly sensed the distant Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng; his eyes opened wide as he swiftly jumped back like he was facing a great enemy.

His eyes twitched and his heart had already sunk.

Giant Sun's will had suddenly disappeared, and the mysterious man impersonating Chang Shan Yin appeared with Gu Immortal Tai Bai Yun Sheng standing beside him, and the two seemed to have a very close relation at that! This was extremely unfavorable to Hei Lou Lan.

Ma Hong Yun, however, did not sense anything. The defensive barrier raised by the land spirit was shrinking constantly as it was attacked by the innumerable treemen. His and Zhao Lian Yun's sight were blocked by the dense amount of trees and leaves.

"What do we do now?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng asked calmly while casting a glance towards the gloomy Hei Lou Lan.

Fang Yuan sneered: "We need Imperial Court blessed land's land spirit, Frost Jade Peacock's strength to topple True Yang Building! Frost Jade Peacock might have already recognized its masters, but because Giant Sun's will is not present, the seals on it are not being manipulated and it is barely surviving. Most of its strength had already been sealed again. The defensive barrier is also on the brink of collapse and simply won't be able to block me. I will go kill Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun. You go deal with Hei Lou Lan and seize the false emotion fake will Gu, I trust that it won't be a problem with your Gu Immortal battle strength. Let's move, we don't have much time!"

"Immortal and mortal are vastly different, it is just like a wide chasm separates them. You don't need to worry." Tai Bai Yun Sheng lightly smiled, moving elegantly towards Hei Lou Lan.

Fang Yuan directly shot forward towards Ma Hong Yun.

The surrounding treemen followed him under his control.

"Such a pity... Ma Hong Yun, I originally wanted to use you as a key to control the events of the future. But who told you to block my way? No matter how good your luck is, your death is certain today!" The brimming killing intent in his heart surfaced as a malevolent smile on Fang Yuan's face.

Chapter 617: The reason for overwhelming fortune

Bam bam bam!

Three ten meter tall treemen raised their hammer-like fists as they attacked time and time again, crashing on the light barrier.

Frost Jade Peacock cried out sorrowfully.

Its huge wings were sealed by gold, only the land spirit's head was still exposed.

"My masters, I cannot hold on anymore." The land spirit sighed, its long eyelashes trembling slightly. The light barrier was getting weaker, and under the treemen's endless attacks, it was on the brink of collapsing.

What was more scary was, Fang Yuan was closing in!

Imperial Court blessed land was already in bad shape, and the land spirit, Frost Jade Peacock, was sealed, the remaining strength of the barrier was not a problem for Fang Yuan, he could break through it any moment.

The fatal threat had already arrived, but Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun still had no idea.

Even though they could not sense Fang Yuan, the thick aura of death was suffocating them.

Zhao Lian Yun was silent and did not speak, she hid in Ma Hong Yun's arms as she shut her eyes.

After all, she was an ordinary woman.

Ma Hong Yun continually comforted her in a soft voice, even though he felt no hope himself.

"It's over." Fang Yuan shot out like lightning, stepping on twigs and branches as he entered the innermost layer of the treeman encirclement.

But just when he was about to execute the finishing blow, as he was charging, Mo Yao shouted in his head: "Eh? This aura! Wait... stop quickly!"

"What is it?" Fang Yuan's momentum was lost, he stopped at a high area on a tree as he asked in suspicion.

Ever since Mo Yao's will entered his head, he had never felt such intense emotions from her before!

At this moment, Mo Yao showed herself in Fang Yuan's mind.

She had tears all over her face as her slim body was shivering, she was muttering: "This aura, this aura... there's no mistake, there's absolutely no mistake! This is the aura of fortune rivalling heaven Gu!"

"Fortune rivalling heaven Gu?!" Fang Yuan's heart jumped, as he immediately recalled.

Mo Yao had researched deeply about Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in her lifetime, taking a huge risk to enter the true inheritance secluded domain for her lover Bo Qing.

Her original motive was to obtain the supreme true inheritance of luck path, she wanted to steal the fortune rivalling heaven Gu in it.

But in the end, she only succeeded partially.

As she spent a lot of effort and exerted all her strength, she was able to create a crack in the luck path true inheritance.

However, fortune rivalling heaven Gu flew into this crack and vanished into thin air.

But Mo Yao did not return empty handed, she obtained a portion of the luck path inheritance's details. Combined with her refinement path grandmaster foundation, she eventually refined calamity beckoning Gu.

But calamity beckoning Gu was inferior to fortune rivalling heaven Gu, Mo Yao used it to help Bo Qing with his tribulation, and in the end both of them died.

Eventually, Fang Yuan found Mo Yao's inheritance and refined calamity beckoning Gu once again, accepting Mo Yao's request to return the rank seven Gu House Water Pavilion to Spirit Affinity House.

Now, Mo Yao felt the aura of fortune rivalling heaven Gu, this was a crucial Immortal Gu that she had failed to obtain after spending her entire life and putting in immeasurable effort.

It was understandable that she had become so agitated and emotional.

"Fortune rivalling heaven Gu's aura is on this lad! I can't believe it, I, Mo Yao, spent my entire life and nearly died in the secluded domain, but eventually the fortune rivalling heaven Gu escaped and this mortal lad got it by chance. Hehehe, is this life?" Mo Yao raised her head and sighed, as she laughed and cried, her tone was extremely dejected.

Fang Yuan squinted, his eyes glowing with cold light.

He asked in his heart: "That means fortune rivalling heaven Gu is currently on Ma Hong Yun? Can you confirm that?!"

"Of course, I can never forget the aura of fortune rivalling heaven Gu!" Mo Yao replied unhesitatingly.

She continued and said: "Fortune rivalling heaven Gu is a one time expenditure rank eight Gu. It is formless and ethereal, being in essence a lump of luck, it is extremely difficult to capture with ordinary methods. Back then, my main body could not capture it, thus it managed to fly away from the scene and vanish without a trace. Even True Yang Building could not trap it. It must've escaped to northern plains, roaming until it landed on that lad!"

"So it is a one time expenditure Gu..." Fang Yuan was extremely disappointed.

Fortune rivalling heaven Gu was the greatest treasure in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path inheritance, it had extremely great value.

Fang Yuan was unable to gain benefits in the true inheritance secluded domain, but if he could take fortune rivalling heaven Gu away from Ma Hong Yun, that would be the best.

But unfortunately, fortune rivalling heaven could only be used once before it vanished.

"Fang Yuan, you have to be careful! Fortune rivalling heaven Gu is extremely special, back then Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had fortuitous encounters endlessly, time after time he would turn disasters into blessings, he unceasingly had great luck, and he relied on this Gu to a great extent. Ma Hong Yun is affected by fortune rivalling heaven Gu, he is a true child of luck! His luck could be said to be ranked at number one in the five regions!! The luck that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had back then would very possibly be replicated in him. Although luck is formless and ethereal, it is a part of strength and cannot be underestimated!" Mo Yao quickly said anxiously.

"I know what to do." Fang Yuan held in his killing intent, his expression turning cold as he stopped on the tree branch, not attacking abruptly.

He looked down from above, at Ma Hong Yun and others, allowing the treemen below him to attack.

Actually, the two were not too far from each other, but even Frost Jade Peacock did not discover him.

This showed how weak the land spirit was right now.

It was obvious at one glance that the two sides had great difference in strength, it seemed that victory was in sight, and killing Ma Hong Yun was extremely easy.

But Fang Yuan did not think so, he was once a Gu Immortal, his vision surpassed mortals.

He understood: These so called paths — wisdom path, refinement path, metal path, time path and others, they looked like they were combinations of complex series of Gu worms gathered together, but in actuality, they were the deciphering of one's understanding towards heaven and earth, towards the mysteries of the universe.

Luck path was the same.

Based on Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's example, one could see that luck path, even compared to other paths, could more deeply explain the mysteries of heaven and earth in some aspect.

Fang Yuan had never looked down on Ma Hong Yun, he had always been vigilant towards him.

Because his previous life's memories made him understand how high Ma Hong Yun's future achievements would be.

In his previous life, Ma Hong Yun became the pillar of northern plains, the leader that resisted the attack of central continent Gu Immortals! When Fang Yuan was killed by the barrage of Gu Immortals, he was still growing and developing.

Fang Yuan knew about Ma Hong Yun's growth, and now he finally understood the origin of Ma Hong Yun's heaven defying luck.

That was, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's greatest achievement in luck path — fortune rivalling heaven Gu!

And the cause of all this was Mo Yao who was residing in his mind!

Luck did not have any physical form, and it could not be touched, but Fang Yuan knew the ability of this mystical power.

"No wonder Giant Sun's will purposely chose Hei Lou Lan and Ma Hong Yun as the people to become the land spirit's master. Hei Lou Lan is the strongest person among his bloodline descendants, while Ma Hong Yun had fortune rivalling heaven Gu."

Fang Yuan felt that this situation was troublesome.

Although Ma Hong Yun was a tiny rank three Gu Master, he had the power of a rank eight Immortal Gu protecting him!

A rank eight Immortal Gu, only inferior to rank nine, such as the wisdom Gu and strength Gu of legends. It had absurd and unimaginable strength, anyone who underestimated it would face a pitiful end.

Fang Yuan was only a mortal, back then in the true inheritance secluded domain, he could not even get close to the rank seven human qi Gu, not to mention the rank eight fortune rivalling heaven Gu.

Ma Hong Yun looked harmless, but in all his experiences, when did he ever suffer a true loss? Every time, he benefited from difficulties and had endless fortuitous encounters, all those who wished to harm or kill him faced a terrible end.

Although every time he did not personally take action, but there would always be an external force or accident, along with a series of small coincidences, all of these added together to form a shocking power!

Fang Yuan suddenly thought of Giant Sun's will.

Earlier, Giant Sun's will wanted to exterminate Zhao Lian Yun, but Ma Hong Yun protected her with his life. This was as if Giant Sun's will had become an enemy of Ma Hong Yun.

Just as Giant Sun's will was about to strike, Fang Yuan appeared, pulling out True Yang Building and causing the heavenly tribulation to strike him.

"Even Giant Sun's will fell prey huh..." Fang Yuan looked at this from another angle and was shocked.

"I have the glass owner token, I can check the situation inside the entire Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Why did I not strike earlier? Actually, it was completely unintentional! Or maybe... I heard that Zhao Lian Yun was an otherworldly demon and wanted to protect her, I was curious and wanted to investigate this?" Fang Yuan recalled the scene.

Giant Sun's will's was expelled from True Yang Building, he could be said to be the culprit. But the timing was too coincidental, it allowed Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun to escape death.

"If I suddenly attack Ma Hong Yun, would I be like Giant Sun's will, will an outside force intervene, or will an accident occur?"

Fang Yuan grabbed his glass owner token, considering his plans again.

"Wait!" Fang Yuan thought about it again: "What I've heard on this matter was only Mo Yao's statement. It seems to be credible, but what if she lied to me due to some special reason?"

Fang Yuan suddenly thought of this.

Thus, he asked Mo Yao in his heart: "Strange, earlier when I used luck inspection Gu, I observed the luck of everyone in the sacred palace. If Ma Hong Yun had the fortune rivalling heaven Gu, why did I not discover it? I could only see that the two with the highest luck were Hei Lou Lan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng."

Mo Yao seemed to have predicted this question, she immediately answered: "What's so strange about this? Fortune rivalling heaven Gu is a rank eight Immortal Gu, your luck inspection Gu is only a rank five mortal Gu, an investigative Gu that can allow a Gu Master to see luck despite its formlessness. How can a rank five investigative Gu discover the luck created by a rank eight Immortal Gu?"

"If I cannot see it, how can I be sure that Ma Hong Yun has fortune rivalling heaven Gu's influence on him?" Fang Yuan did not relent, he continued asking.

"Oh Fang Yuan, you are too suspicious." Mo Yao sighed, immediately answering: "There is a method to make sure. That is to use investigative Gu and check your own luck. Every time you act against the child of luck, because of the mutual influence between luck, your luck will become bad, or even worse. If you do not believe me, you can check it that way."

Time was limited, Fang Yuan immediately used luck inspection Gu.

His vision changed abruptly.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun's luck were rather tiny, they were the same as ordinary people.

Meanwhile, there was a massive black luck, almost three hundred meters tall, high enough to pierce heaven and earth!

Chapter 618: Great Strength True Martial Physique

This black luck aura was so dark that it reached the point of being extremely oppressive. The coffin shaped aura was tightly covering Fang Yuan.

Since an unknown time ago, the black aura on Fang Yuan had become much larger and much deeper.

Far away, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Hei Lou Lan were engaged in an intense battle.

The luck aura of the two were exceptionally clear.

Above Hei Lou Lan was still the azure luck aura that gave a lasting feeling like a towering tree. The luck on Tai Bai Yun Sheng, however, was smaller than before, not even one-sixth of the original amount; it was no longer the brightly burning red cloud, instead it was a shade of heavy evening mist that almost looked like a dark cloud.

Fang Yuan looked back above himself and started testing as Mo Yao had mentioned.

Just like Mo Yao said, whenever he thought of attacking Ma Hong Yun, the black coffin luck on him enlarged a little and its dark shade seemed to become even gloomier.

"Fang Yuan, you should leave this troubled place as quickly as possible. The black coffin luck on you right now is too dense and too frightening. Your life is under great threat now! Don't underestimate luck just because it is ethereal, just think of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's unrivalled powers. You are in deep danger right now, the black coffin luck has yet to erupt itself, but the consequences will hit you eventually, it is only that the time is not ripe."

Mo Yao continued to persuade Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan coldly snorted and replied with a resolute will: "Asking me to retreat? Being scared off by merely bad luck? Hehe, how could that be possible!"

He narrowed his eyes, his lips slightly curled up, revealing his snow-white teeth as he looked down from the cover of the treetop: "No matter how bad the luck becomes, it cannot attack me directly. It will need to rely on external influences to kill me. Right now, at this moment, at this place, I want to see who can obstruct me!"

Killing intent surged and bubbled in Fang Yuan's heart.

He believed in the power of luck path, but he believed in himself even more!

He needed to kill Ma Hong Yun!!

He had to try!!!

If Fang Yuan cowered just because of luck, would it conform to his style?

Ordinary people would feel regret after facing the consequences, but he, Fang Yuan, would not feel any!

"Have you gone crazy? That is a rank eight Immortal Gu!" Mo Yao screamed when she felt the dense killing intent in Fang Yuan.

"Hehehe, precisely because the enemy is this strong, the battle would be even more interesting, wouldn't it?" Fang Yuan instead laughed freely. Right now, he no longer had short hair of Chang Shan Yin, but had long black hair that fluttered freely with the wind and his countenance revealed a crazed recklessness.

He was never against bullying the weak, but even more than that, he had the bravery to fight the strong.

How could one obtain a tiger cub without entering the tiger's den?

If he did not stake it all at this moment, then when should he?!

"Fate teases the turbulent sea, cowardly insects avoid waves and flow along the current. A brave man does not need much wisdom, there is not regret or pain even if his body crumbles." Fang Yuan mumbled before restraining his crazed mood, his expression turning tranquil.

"Lunatic, you have gone mad..." Mo Yao continued to mutter.

Right now, Fang Yuan's killing intent had accumulated to the peak.

The black coffin luck aura above him subsequently inflated, expanding by three times within moments!

"Let me see who will save you! Fortune rivalling heaven Gu, let me look at your might."

Fang Yuan made a motion to attack.

BOOOM!

An explosion occurred; the majestic wind current it created formed into a strong gale that pressed on from a distance.

Hei Lou Lan was standing unstably; while Tai Bai Yun Sheng got up from the crater, fresh blood flowing from his mouth.

He looked at Hei Lou Lan who was floating in the air, shock apparent on his face: "You are actually..."

Before he finished his words, Hei Lou Lan charged at him again.

BOOM!

Ground shook and dust surged everywhere.

"Ten extreme physiques." Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk as he muttered the answer in place of Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

He had never imagined Hei Lou Lan to actually have one of the ten extreme physiques. And from the looks of it, it was extremely likely to be the Great Strength True Martial Physique of the ten extreme physiques!

Several breaths later, a shadow flew out from the dust.

It was Tai Bai Yun Sheng!

His hair was a mess, dust covered his face; his chest was caved in till it revealed the deathly white bones.

Blood sprayed out like a spring.

But a green light soon covered his body and the flow of blood immediately stopped; the heavy injuries on his body also quickly recovered.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng had exchanged intel back at Hu Immortal blessed land. And he knew Tai Bai Yun Sheng possessed two Immortal Gu, landscape as before Gu and man as before Gu.

However, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was clearly not using the Immortal Gu Man as Before, but instead ordinary healing Gu.

Immortal Gu Man as Before required immortal essence to be activated, and had extremely great effects, but it was not easy to gather immortal essence. Thus, unless as a final resort, Gu Immortals would not easily use Immortal Gu.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng, you are a grand Gu Immortal but are afraid of me, a mortal?" A roar shook the sky and earth.

Hei Lou Lan flew to the sky and started hunting down Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Such an intense aura of the ten extremes... terrifying! Hei Lou Lan not only has one of the ten extreme physiques, he is also already on the verge of self-detonation!" Fang Yuan was able to decipher many details right now.

Back then at Qing Mao mountain, Fang Yuan had relied on Bai Ning Bing's Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique to cross realms in fighting a strong enemy, and overturn the situation.

Bai Ning Bing was only rank three back then!

As one of the ten extreme physiques' cultivation increased, the power of their self-detonation would increase sharply by many times.

The self-detonation of the rank five peak stage Hei Lou Lan would be beyond compare, so terrifying that even killing Gu Immortals would not be a problem!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a bitter expression on his face, with not even the slightest battle intent.

Previously, Hei Lou Lan had been under the seal of Immortal Gu Dark Limit, not leaking out even a trace of its aura.

Now that he had torn off the seal, his majestic aura would cause terror to emerge in one's heart.

He was now a large human shaped bomb, who would dare to approach him? What if he exploded!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had just advanced to a Gu Immortal, wouldn't it be injustice if he was killed by the desperate Hei Lou Lan in his impending death?

"I had never thought Hei Lou Lan would actually have Great Strength True Martial Physique of the ten extreme physiques. And he has actually managed to grow to this extent!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng fled with astonishing speed.

He was a flying master and his cloud path Gu was also one of the better movement Gu.

Hei Lou Lan was hunting him down from behind but could only look helplessly as the distance between them increased further and further.

Rumble!

Hei Lou Lan was furious, suddenly throwing a punch.

This punch had terrifying momentum as it directly broke the sound barrier and burst the surrounding air!

Following this punch, a fist qi suddenly flew out, forming into a strength path phantom figure.

Fang Yuan had also attacked with many beast strength phantoms back in southern border, but the phantom that Hei Lou Lan summoned was not beast shaped, instead it was human shaped.

And this human strength phantom was a vivid image of Hei Lou Lan.

The obese body like that of a bear, the jagged snow-white teeth that were like daggers. A pair of triangular eyes which flashed with malevolent glint. It was truly a second Hei Lou Lan!

"Even if I combine all the beast strength phantoms I used back at southern border, they might not be the human strength phantom's match!" Fang Yuan's eyelids twitched.

He had extraordinary appraisal ability and immediately saw the extremely high battle strength that this human strength phantom possessed. It was full of spirituality; once it was summoned, it could chase the enemy of its own will.

This was the strength of rank five peak stage Great Strength True Martial Physique!

Simply terrifying!

But how powerful this strength was, Fang Yuan could not estimate it easily. Unless he personally went to battle and experienced it for himself.

But he was sure this terrifying battle strength had already surpassed the mortal realm.

It could even be said that Hei Lou Lan was currently at a state that was half a step to Gu Immortal realm.

The ten extreme physiques broke conventions, they were existences that could shatter opponents at the same realm!

Back at Qing Mao mountain, Fang Yuan used one of the ten extreme physiques to survive an ordeal. But this time, one of the ten extreme physiques was his enemy.

"If not for the fact that Gu Masters obtain a qualitative improvement in their body's defense when they advance to Gu Immortal, Tai Bai Yun Sheng would be in greater danger!"

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng had advanced to Gu Immortal just now, he has yet to accumulate the foundation of a Gu Immortal. Moreover, he is a healing Gu Master, but has to face against this tyrannical and battle-hungry enemy like Hei Lou Lan..."

For a moment, thoughts shone in Fang Yuan's mind like sparks.

"The strongest advantage of a Gu Immortal over mortals lies in their unlimited primeval essence. But Hei Lou Lan's main cultivation path is strength path which relies on primeval essence the least among all paths and has the lowest primeval essence consumption. This advantage is thus almost non-existent."

"There is also Hei Lou Lan's killer move, it actually went in an innovative new direction, creating such a sentient human strength phantom. In just a short period, he has already created five to six human strength phantoms. These phantoms are anything but ordinary, filled with spirituality, they actually flanked and blocked Tai Bai Yun Sheng's retreat paths; this is truly unimaginable!"

Unleashing human shaped phantoms was not a surprising thing.

The crucial point was that he could create such intelligent human shaped phantoms!

Moreover, all of these human shaped phantoms had astonishing strength. The might of their strength and wisdom made even Fang Yuan feel apprehensive.

"No wonder Hei Lou Lan died suddenly in my previous life. So it was because he had one of the ten extreme physiques!" Fang Yuan suddenly realized.

Although he had been reborn, it did not mean he knew everything.

Right now, this unexpected twist disrupted his plans.

"Damn it..." Fang Yuan subconsciously tightened his grip on the glass owner token.

According to his original plan, he would have gone with Giant Sun's will's train of thought, using false emotion fake will Gu to subdue the land spirit and become Imperial Court blessed land's owner.

He needed to subdue false emotion fake will Gu first to accomplish this.

However, false emotion fake will Gu was one of the ordinary true inheritances and it contained a portion of Giant Sun's will in it. How could a mere mortal like Fang Yuan refine an Immortal Venerable's will?

Only a Gu Immortal's will had such a possibility.

Therefore, Fang Yuan used his eloquence to dupe Tai Bai Yun Sheng into becoming his ally; it was to make use of his will to refine false emotion fake will Gu.

But when he returned to True Yang Building, the situation had already changed beyond his expectations.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun obtained Frost Jade Peacock's recognition, becoming Imperial Court blessed land's owners.

Frost Jade Peacock's condition for recognizing its masters was a Gu Master couple who had to have true love for each other.

Ma Hong Yun was a rank three Gu Master, but Zhao Lian Yun was still a young girl and had not begun her cultivation journey yet.

However, she was still recognized as a master!

This showed the condition of 'Gu Master' was only speaking of aptitude. As long as the person had the possibility of becoming a Gu Master, they could receive recognition. In Fang Yuan's previous life, Zhao Lian Yun was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, she naturally had strong cultivation aptitude.

These small details were not worth bickering over. In Fang Yuan's opinion, what he needed to do were two things.

First was seizing false emotion fake will Gu. It was on Hei Lou Lan, and Fang Yuan had given this task to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Second was killing Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun. As long as he killed them, Imperial Court blessed land would return to an ownerless state.

After completing these two matters, Tai Bai Yun Sheng could help Fang Yuan to refine false emotion fake will Gu and take control of the land spirit. Even if Giant Sun's will returns then, Fang Yuan had the capital to contend against him.

However, right now, neither of these two goals were achieved.

Chapter 619: The might of overwhelming fortune

Hei Lou Lan revealed his true trump card, displaying he had one of the ten extreme physiques and was close to self-detonation, it had shocking battle strength, with him managing to suppress the Gu Immortal Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and he was chasing after him.

This was quite a shock, but after some consideration, it was nothing strange.

"If he doesn't defeat Hei Lou Lan, he would not get false emotion fake will Gu. Without false emotion fake will Gu, how will I subdue the land spirit? Damn it..." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth.

His plan was ruined.

"Is this the power of fortune rivalling heaven? The moment I wanted to strike, such an accident occurred!" Fang Yuan took a look at Ma Hong Yun, his expression turning grim.

For some reason, the killing intent in his heart intensified.

He crossed his arms, standing high up in the tree as his mouth showed a cold smile: "It is getting more interesting, fortune rivalling heaven... hmph, now that Hei Lou Lan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng are fighting, if I really want to kill you, what can you do to resist me?"

This time, Fang Yuan did not go personally, but instead manipulated the treemen.

The treemen at the most inner layer raised their hammer-like fists highly in the air.

Under Fang Yuan's manipulation, they slammed down at the same time.

Bam!

With a loud bang, Frost Jade Peacock cried out pitifully as its raised head fell onto the ground.

The defensive barrier that it had erected with all its effort was smashed, it turned into golden dust as it quickly vanished into nothingness.

Even the last obstacle was removed.

The closest treeman took a huge step forward, it stretched out its huge arm as it rapidly grabbed at Ma and Zhao.

Zhao Lian Yun shouted shrilly, while Ma Hong Yun held her in his arms, his back facing the treeman's palm.

"Die." Fang Yuan muttered, completely ignoring the black coffin luck above his head that was rapidly growing.

The treeman's palm was towering over Ma and Zhou, it only needed to squeeze lightly and Ma and Zhao would turn into meat paste.

But at this moment!

A huge tremor occurred in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The entire place was shaking!

"Scoundrel, you dare to chase me out, quickly accept your death!!" A loud voice could be heard, piercing heaven and earth, and causing Fang Yuan's eardrums to feel slight pain.

Hearing this familiar voice, Ma Hong Yun raised his head in joy, saying: "It's old ancestor, old ancestor did not die, he is back again!"

Hei Lou Lan expressed joy similarly on his face.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression was pale, if Giant Sun's will returned, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would display the might of a rank eight Immortal Gu House, it could definitely trap a Gu Immortal, this was no joke!

"How can this be! Even though I spent some time inside Hu Immortal blessed land, but fifteen minutes was far from over." Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk to the size of a pin, he was very stunned.

He quickly used the glass owner token and checked the situation.

Outside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there were layers and layers of golden sand-like light particles.

That was the colossal Giant Sun's will.

He was still growling furiously, as he resisted the assault of the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, he constantly exerted pressure and attempted to barge into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"The Giant Sun's will that is outside did not come in. Then who is this Giant Sun's will here? Where did he come from?!"

Fang Yuan was very perplexed.

But this Giant Sun's will that just appeared did not want to give him time to think.

Heaven and earth shook, those which were running, those which were helping Tai Bai Yun Sheng, those which were standing in place, those which were trapping Ma Hong Yun, all the treemen stopped their actions, standing still like statues.

Fang Yuan's face was red, the glass owner token in his hand was hot like fire!

Cracks started appearing on the owner token, in just a moment, the glass owner token was on the brink of collapsing!

"Damn it!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, this mysterious Giant Sun's will was getting rid of the central continent Gu Immortals' arrangements rapidly.

The third arrangement that central continent Gu Immortals made was extremely hidden, it was not easy for Giant Sun's will to find it.

But right now, Fang Yuan had completely unleashed it, there was no way to hide it, this mysterious Giant Sun's will found it easily.

Once the glass owner token breaks, the third arrangement would lose effect, and the Giant Sun's will outside would be free to enter and exit True Yang Building!

By that time, even if Giant Sun's will did not use Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he could easily kill Fang Yuan using his own ability.

An unprecedented danger had descended upon Fang Yuan!

"Don't tell me I need to use Spring Autumn Cicada? No! The risk of using Spring Autumn Cicada is too high, I am not at that stage yet! I have to persevere, I can still go on!" Fang Yuan growled angrily, he sent his will into the glass owner token.

Bam.

The next moment, through the glass owner token, his will clashed with the Giant Sun's will that had appeared out of nowhere.

Ugh.

Fang Yuan's body shuddered, he spurted out a mouthful of blood as the will he injected was completely obliterated!

His head hurt intensely, like it was going to break apart. His mind suffered a huge blow, as Mo Yao's will screamed continually.

Fang Yuan's body shook, he felt dizzy and could not stand, after enduring for a few breaths, he fell from the tall tree branch.

Swoosh!

Wind blew, as the three closest treemen suddenly stretched out their tree vine hands, grabbing at Fang Yuan with ill intent.

Fang Yuan lost the contest, Giant Sun's will had regained control of this round, thus, the treemen also became Fang Yuan's enemies, they would not rest until they killed Fang Yuan!

Because of this sudden event, Ma and Zhou escaped death, under the influence of their will to live, they started escaping blindly among the chaotic tree roots.

At the moment of danger, Fang Yuan was barely able to regain awareness.

He shouted lightly, injecting his primeval essence into his Gu worms, mustering his strength and punching and kicking the large tree hand that was coming for him.

Bam bam bam!

After three explosive sounds, the fists were shattered as Fang Yuan adjusted his balance in the air, landing hastily.

The aftermath of competing against Giant Sun's will remained, his ears were buzzing and his hearing was nearly completely gone.

But Fang Yuan had no regret.

In fact, he opened his mouth, laughing loudly: "Excellent!"

The earlier clash of wills was not elegant in the least, but it not only allowed Fang Yuan to keep his glass owner token, he even found out the truth about Giant Sun's will.

This newly appeared and mysterious will was not as powerful as expected.

He did not expect Fang Yuan to make such a choice either.

This will was split into three, the largest portion of it was dealing with the third arrangement, a small portion was busy fighting for the control rights of this round, while the last portion was victorious in the contest against Fang Yuan through the glass owner token.

In the end, Fang Yuan's injected will exterminated the victorious Giant Sun's will, and combined with the third arrangement, although his will was wiped out, he successfully caused harm to that large portion of Giant Sun's will.

Thus, Giant Sun's will was only left with a small portion that was controlling this round.

Giant Sun's will fell into extreme anger, he did not expect this tiny mortal to have the guts to challenge his will directly.

He did not expect that this mortal had stored so many wills in his mind either.

This was all thanks to Mo Yao honestly.

In order to deal with Mo Yao, Fang Yuan stored large amounts of wills in his mind as a back up.

He had special will, play will, deliberate will, keep will, heart will and others, he had a variety of many wills.

Giant Sun's will greatly underestimated Fang Yuan's capacity, and as he was anxious to save the situation, he was counterattacked by Fang Yuan and in the end, was caught off guard and suffered a great loss.

"Scoundrel, I will decimate your corpse!" Giant Sun's will was angered to his boiling point, he continued to manipulate the treemen to attack.

Fang Yuan dodged left and right, using all his effort to heal his injuries.

These treemen had thick skin and flesh, even if their branches, arms and legs were broken, they would not die, they had very strong vitality. It was not a good idea to fight them head on.

While he dodged, Fang Yuan's injuries recovered rapidly.

He quickly realized that the treemen were not only attacking him, but also Tai Bai Yun Sheng and even Ma Hong Yun.

More accurately, they were attacking Zhao Lian Yun who was beside Ma Hong Yun.

Ma and Zhao escaped under the pursuit of the treemen, they were in a dangerous situation.

They frantically escaped without a goal, but they actually got near to Fang Yuan.

"Please save us!" Ma Hong Yun finally saw Fang Yuan, shouting loudly for help.

"So naive." Fang Yuan laughed sinisterly, immediately going closer to him.

As the two sides got closer, Fang Yuan shouted loudly: "Giant Sun's will is trying to kill you, we have a common enemy, come here!"

"Be careful!" Zhao Lian Yun who was running showed hesitation and worry.

But the current situation was, only Fang Yuan could protect them.

They were unable to hold on much longer.

If they stayed, they would definitely get killed by the treemen, if they went to Fang Yuan, they at least had a chance of survival.

"Save, of course we'll save them! Quickly save them!!" In his mind, Mo Yao's will suddenly shouted.

"What?" Fang Yuan thought he heard wrongly.

Mo Yao spoke quickly: "Do you still not understand? Giant Sun's will is a huge special will, he knows the power of fortune rivalling heaven Gu, his intention is not to deal with Ma Hong Yun. But when he was first formed, his main body had placed a rule on him, that was to exterminate any otherworldly demon he sees!"

"She's an otherworldly demon, don't tell me you are not interested! But the most important thing is — if you save that Zhao Lian Yun, it will be the best weapon against Giant Sun's will. Since Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun are truly in love, they will definitely be enemies with Giant Sun's will. By then, Giant Sun's will would be dealt with using the power of fortune rivalling heaven Gu."

Mo Yao's words were very moving.

At once, the hidden killing intent that he had towards Ma Hong Yun shrunk.

"Wait! Ma and Zhao are in grave danger now, they might get squashed or trampled by the treemen at any moment! If I appear now, wouldn't I be saving them?" Fang Yuan suddenly thought of this, becoming stunned!

Although Ma Hong Yun was rank three, he was too hard to kill!

The first time Fang Yuan's killing intent appeared, Hei Lou Lan showed his trump card, he unleashed his extreme physique and chased after Tai Bai Yun Sheng!

The second time he had killing intent, Giant Sun's will came out of nowhere and gravely injured Fang Yuan.

And now, his ears were buzzing and his mind was weakened by at least thirty percent. Even though he protected the glass owner token and caused harm to Giant Sun's will, he lost control over this round.

Now, Fang Yuan had his third wave of killing intent, and Mo Yao was the one who stopped him! But the problem was, she made perfect sense! Even Fang Yuan himself was convinced!

The reason Fang Yuan wanted to kill Ma Hong Yun earlier was to change the land spirit's ownership.

But now that Hei Lou Lan showed his true battle strength and protected the false emotion fake will Gu, thus Fang Yuan did not have it. What use was there in killing the two?

"Don't tell me that this third time, the one stopping me is actually myself?" As he was struck by reality, Fang Yuan was tongue-tied!

Chapter 620: Stopped by himself?

Fang Yuan truly experienced the might of fortune rivalling heaven Gu now.

This was a form of helplessness, like being played by destiny, where one would not know whether to laugh or cry, and the more they struggled, the deeper they would fall into despair!

Forced by the situation and in order to avoid calamity, it seemed Fang Yuan could only choose to maximize his benefits.

The distance between the two sides rapidly shortened.

To save them, or not to save them?

Mo Yao repeatedly screamed in Fang Yuan's mind: "Save, save them!"

Reason also told Fang Yuan that saving Ma Hong Yun would make him stand on the same side as Fortune Rivalling Heaven and he could borrow its strength to deal with Giant Sun's will.

However!

There was a voice in Fang Yuan's heart. This voice growled, shouted and roared!

"Save!? Am I going to surrender? Am I going to lower my head? I can kill him with one slap! What am I afraid of? Afraid of these two trash? Even Fortune Rivalling Heaven cannot obstruct me!!"

Fang Yuan's ears were buzzing non-stop, but this voice kept on getting louder, gradually suppressing every other sound.

He felt bursts of intense headaches.

He felt his mouth go dry in front of these choices.

That voice in his heart, however, was getting louder and clearer till his heart started to tremor!

Every howl, every roar, every shout, seemed to throw a bundle of firewood into the fury in Fang Yuan's heart.

The burning flames surged!

That was the fire of ambition, his fighting spirit, his unyielding, obstinate spirit of challenging the strong!

The flames soared; Fang Yuan's eyes turned bloodshot, his blood boiled and surged like the surging waves!

"Come, let me send you off personally!" Fang Yuan spoke, his voice hoarse like sand gritting on iron.

He did what he would normally not do, going against his style of prioritizing benefits.

With a malevolent expression and eyes shining with sharp killing intent, he smashed apart the giant treemen in front of him, tearing the countless twisting and coiling vines.

He reached Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

Then...

He lifted his fist!

Before his punch even struck out, the terrifying fist aura already condensed into solid. The brutal killing intent almost solidified even the air!

"Ahhh!" Ma Hong Yun's eyes opened wide, never having expected Fang Yuan to have such resolute killing intent. He turned pale with fright, and in his panic, he unexpectedly stumbled and fell to the ground.

"Ouch!" Zhao Lian Yun had been holding hands with Ma Hong Yun, and was thus also pulled down to the ground.

This unforeseen event shocked Fang Yuan.

He was already extremely vigilant because of the repeated accidents. But he soon found that this small accident only prolonged the time he struck them by a little.

At the same time, two giant treemen also reached Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

No matter which treeman it was, it would only need one foot to crush these two to pieces. But Giant Sun's will truly did not want to harm Ma Hong Yun, and could only mobilize vines to scuttle to Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, to separate them and then kill Zhao Lian Yun!

Five treemen suddenly pierced out of the ground at this moment and coincidentally blocked Fang Yuan's way.

This strong defense required Fang Yuan to waste at least a dozen breath of time.

Giant Sun's will was using his previous tactics again.

At present, the extremely weak land spirit was already booted from the playing field.

False emotion fake will Gu was safe as it was being protected by Hei Lou Lan.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun might have become the owners of the blessed land, but as long as Zhao Lian Yun was killed, this connection would be cancelled.

At that time, it would not be too late to salvage the situation by using false emotion fake will Gu to make Hei Lou Lan and Ma Hong Yun the owners of Imperial Court blessed land.

Thus, Giant Sun's will was obstructing Fang Yuan from killing Ma Hong Yun.

"Damn it! This kind of feeling again, always at the crucial place and at the crucial time..." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, and used all his strength to forcibly break through the defensive line.

Thud thud thud...

Thunder-like collisions occurred one after another. Fang Yuan was like a tiger let loose, his fierce offense directly breaking the treemen's defense.

The whole process only lasted less than ten breaths!

However, Fang Yuan also had to pay a heavy price. Three enormous wounds were added to Fang Yuan's body; one ran through his chest, another pierced his back, and another formed a bloody hole on his stomach with the size of a baby's fist.

His right forearm was severely fractured, his left leg was twisted grotesquely to the side.

"Hahaha!" Fang Yuan, however, howled with laughter!

He could not use his hand and leg for a while, but he still had movement Gu, he could still fly!

He rapidly chased after Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun through the air.

Ma Hong Yun hunched over, protecting Zhao Lian Yun tightly under him. Vines were coiling around them from outside.

These vines wanted to separate the two without harming Ma Hong Yun.

Ma Hong Yun faced off against the vines. But naturally, he was weaker and looked on as he and Zhao Lian Yun were forcibly separated. He bit his lips and glared with furious eyes, but he was powerless!

"No—!" He roared with bloodshot eyes. Despair and pain filled him as he saw his lover about to die in front of him, appearing like a beast forced into a corner.

"Save him quickly, now is the best time to save him! As long as you save them, Ma Hong Yun will definitely feel grateful to you, you can then borrow the strength of his fortune that rivals heaven! Just think, why is Giant Sun's will not killing Ma Hong Yun - it is to use his luck!!" Mo Yao shouted again, persuading Fang Yuan.

"You really speak a lot of nonsense." Fang Yuan replied with ruthless coldness.

Success was in front of him, but he instead calmed down, he had no expression on his face, not even the previous malevolent look.

"Die!"

When Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun was in his range, Fang Yuan immediately struck out with a fatal attack.

This attack had earth-shattering power, bursting all the air in front of it.

The incomparably violent power was like an evil dragon rising to heaven, as it shrouded over Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

"No!" This time, it was Giant Sun's will who let out a helpless and desperate shout.

He immediately mobilized the surrounding treemen to use their own bodies to protect Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

The tree vines no longer separated the two, instead they attempted to rapidly evacuate them.

But Giant Sun's will was still feeling dejected.

He knew all these would be of no use. This strike filled with Fang Yuan's pent-up wrath, how could it be so easily blocked and avoided?

The treemen's trunks were smashed apart, the vines also did not have enough time to evacuate Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun. In the end, the attack that still had its peak offensive power was about to directly smash them into pieces.

Even though there were countless treemen filling the vast forest, it was all too late!

Fang Yuan was resolute, erupting with all his strength to break through the defensive line and succeeded in grabbing the crucial moment.

The treemen's movement was slow and they were not good at providing swift reinforcement.

Ma Hong Yun was definitely dead meat!

At this moment, not only Fang Yuan, even Giant Sun's will also thought this so.

Not only did they think so, even Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun did not have any hope of surviving the attack.

Any factors that could influence the situation had seemingly already played their part.

Hei Lou Lan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Giant Sun's will, Frost Jade Peacock, Fang Yuan, Mo Yao...

All these people or things had shown all their strength by this point.

Time seemed to slow down, Fang Yuan's lips curled up to reveal a smile: "Now, is there anything left that can save Ma Hong Yun?"

However, at the next moment!

Rumble—!

A loud sound rang out, causing huge tremors and making countless trees creak.

Dazzling golden rays of light shone over the whole round.

"Has Giant Sun's will entered True Yang Building?!" Fang Yuan turned grave, but soon discovered that was not the case.

Giant Sun's will was still taking a beating outside the building. Central continent's Gu Immortals had planned for countless years to create the third method; it could never be underestimated.

If not for this, central continent's Gu Immortals would not have been able to overthrow Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and return victorious in Fang Yuan's previous life.

The enormous golden light lump moved like a meteor and before the sound even registered in one's ears, it crashed onto the ground, instantly destroying the surrounding treemen and protecting Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun within it.

"This, isn't this — that luck path supreme true inheritance!" Mo Yao was so shocked she involuntarily screamed out.

"What's going on? Shouldn't this supreme true inheritance be in true inheritance secluded domain, how did it suddenly crash into this round and throw itself towards Ma Hong Yun's body?!" With no choice, Fang Yuan could only stop his footsteps.

He had already experienced the might of a supreme true inheritance in true inheritance secluded domain.

This was not something he could touch.

'But why, Ma Hong Yun is covered by this light, but why has nothing happened to him?'

For a moment, Fang Yuan could not help but feel extremely dejected.

He had used all his strength in his third attempt to kill Ma Hong Yun; he had even seen hope a moment ago, the success had seemingly been right in front of him, but he still failed in the end.

"Why did the supreme true inheritance move to Ma Hong Yun? Impossible, this is impossible!" Mo Yao completely lost self-control as she scratched at her head, causing her long hair to become messy, resembling a crazed woman.

This was not surprising.

She had suffered untold hardships, expended all her energy and effort but was only able to open a crack in the luck path true inheritance from which fortune rivalling heaven Gu escaped. Finally, she had no choice but to refine calamity beckoning Gu.

But this calamity beckoning Gu was not able to assist her husband, Bo Qing, causing her and Bo Qing to perish.

But at this moment, she was watching this luck path supreme true inheritance throwing itself at a rank three mortal!

Even if you had fortune that rivalled heaven, isn't this going overboard?!

'Why was it not me, I put in so much effort, paid such a huge price, why was it not me?'

'Why was it this mere mortal, a fool, a kid!'

It is a comparison that could make one die from anger!

Fang Yuan forcibly calmed down and tried hard to remove the unneeded emotions, reflecting on this event.

A bright flash of inspiration seemed to roam around in his mind, but was extremely hard to get a grasp on.

"I understand!" Suddenly, Fang Yuan's body shook as he grasped this flash of inspiration, and understood this seemingly impossible event.

This supreme true inheritance recognized Ma Hong Yun and not others as its master of its own accord. This was because, Ma Hong Yun had the power of fortune rivalling heaven Gu on him.

Fortune rivalling heaven Gu was the true essence of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path, the quintessential crystallization of luck path. To the supreme true inheritance, it was the leader and the emperor.

But why did the supreme true inheritance not come earlier or later, but chose this exact moment?

Luck path supreme true inheritance was located in true inheritance secluded domain, how could it come here for no rhyme or reason?

These two questions actually pointed to the same factor — Giant Sun's will!

Chapter 621: Fighting Hei Lou Lan

In the true inheritance secluded domain, all of the true inheritances had Giant Sun's will in them. Otherwise, how could all these fated individuals succeed in taking these inheritances, especially those Immortal Gu?

It was just like charging through rounds in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

In every one of the rounds that had Gu worms as rewards, these Gu worms were all refined by Giant Sun's will in advance.

When these Gu Masters succeed and obtain the Gu worms, they are able to refine these Gu worms instantly and keep them in their aperture because Giant Sun's will was purposely letting them have the Gu.

Because of this reason, as long as a Gu Master is willing to give his Gu worm away to someone else, they can always create a phenomenon of 'instant refinement'.

Earlier, when Giant Sun's will was slumbering, the refinement of wild Gu worms was extremely slow. When Fang Yuan first ventured into True Yang Building, he made use of this loophole.

Every true inheritance was governed by Giant Sun's will.

The reason why the luck path supreme true inheritance did not fly towards Ma Hong Yun earlier was due to this.

But now the true inheritance flew into Ma Hong Yun's arms and made him its master, this was not Giant Sun's will's intention.

What Giant Sun's will wanted was to control Ma Hong Yun, why would he allow him to grow stronger and become more uncontrollable?

Thus, the truth was revealed!

Within the luck path supreme true inheritance, there was no Giant Sun's will.

Giant Sun's will retreated on his own, this allowed the supreme true inheritance to act on its own.

Thereafter, the newly created wild Gu will went towards Ma Hong Yun.

This created another question.

Why would Giant Sun's will retreat for no reason?

Fang Yuan thought about the second time he struck and was about to kill Ma Hong Yun, but out of nowhere Giant Sun's will appeared!

At this point, it was no longer a mystery.

Fang Yuan used the third method, temporarily expelling Giant Sun's will out of True Yang Building.

Afterwards, he entered True Yang Building and successfully convinced Tai Bai Yun Sheng to revive Dang Hun mountain.

After that he came back, attempting to control Imperial Court blessed land. During the second attempt when he tried to kill Ma Hong Yun, he was obstructed by a sudden burst of Giant Sun's will.

At that point, Fang Yuan was very confused.

But now, he understood.

This mysterious Giant Sun's will was pulled out of those true inheritances.

Giant Sun's will was anxious at that time, in order to salvage the situation, he took this step.

He almost succeeded by doing this, but unfortunately, Fang Yuan was too resolute, he directly faced off against him.

Eventually, this forcefully extracted Giant Sun's will was left with a final small portion that controlled this round.

"This means, the luck path supreme true inheritance was able to save Ma Hong Yun because of me? If I did not expel Giant Sun's will out of the tower, if I did not face off against Giant Sun's will, why would this happen now?"

"To think that this third attempt was thwarted by myself after all!"

Thinking so, Fang Yuan sighed deeply as his killing intent towards Ma Hong Yun vanished without a trace.

The current Ma Hong Yun was protected by the luck path true inheritance. As a mortal, it was impossible for Fang Yuan to break through this defense.

"Sigh, I told you to save him earlier, you refused to listen!" In his mind, Mo Yao calmed down and sighed in pity.

Her tone carried some grievance: "If you had saved them, you would gain Ma Hong Yun's recognition and become protected by the luck path true inheritance just like Zhao Lian Yun. The current luck path true inheritance is a newborn wild will, it is like a baby without any internal defenses. If you are inside the luck path inheritance, you will be able to learn about the details of this true inheritance! This is an immense opportunity, but you gave it up..."

Helping Ma Hong Yun would result in benefits. Dealing with Ma Hong Yun would result in Fang Yuan's current heavy injuries.

Fang Yuan snickered.

He already did it, there was not a bit of regret in his heart.

He quickly retreated while healing his injuries, meanwhile replying to Mo Yao: "Even if I cannot do anything to this luck path true inheritance, do you think Giant Sun's will would do nothing?"

This luck path true inheritance is one of the three supreme true inheritances inside the true inheritance secluded domain. Why would Giant Sun's will allow it to acknowledge a new master like this?

In Giant Sun's will's heart, it was not unacceptable to pass this luck path true inheritance to Ma Hong Yun.

But Ma Hong Yun's heart was with an otherworldly demon, that was a huge taboo!

Giant Sun's will was a special will, when the main body first created it, he assigned a special meaning for it to 'do its best to slaughter any otherworldly demon it comes into contact with'.

Now that Zhao Lian Yun was protected by the luck path true inheritance, if Giant Sun's will wanted to kill this otherworldly demon, he would need to remove the luck path true inheritance's hindrance.

Thus, the entire forest flew into a rage.

Countless treemen were uprooted, encircling the luck path true inheritance.

Large numbers of treemen were entangling with each other, all of their roots and vines were coiling around each other to form huge treemen, each were at least three hundred meters tall, their aura was shocking to Fang Yuan.

Giant Sun's will put in all its effort in order to kill Zhao Lian Yun!

Fang Yuan managed to retreat successfully.

Exterminating the otherworldly demon was Giant Sun's will's most important mission. With the appearance of the luck path true inheritance, his attention was drawn over.

Fang Yuan was a threat that ranked much lower than them.

Giant Sun's will also knew that he could do nothing to Fang Yuan now. Weighing the two sides, and because Giant Sun's will had limited strength, he decided to focus solely on dealing with the luck path true inheritance.

Very soon, Fang Yuan got close to the place Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Hei Lou Lan were fighting at.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was suppressed, but Hei Lou Lan had no ability to claim victory either.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a healing Gu Master and a flying master, the former allowed him to specialize in drawn out battles, while the latter allowed him to escape like a slippery eel, he was hard to pin down.

The two's battle had turned into a stalemate.

The two fought from the sky to the ground, their attacks were fierce and the battle brought disaster to the nearby trees, causing the surroundings to be full of fallen trees and debris.

"Senior brother Tai Bai, let me help you!" Fang Yuan shouted.

'Senior brother', these two words triggered Hei Lou Lan as he immediately thought of central continent. That was because in the five regions, the other four regions were overwhelmingly family based inheritances, only central continent was dominated by a sect based system.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes were staring wide, as he screamed like a bear: "You are a scoundrel that had planned for a long time indeed! You two sect brothers have hidden yourselves deeply! Right now, since you are seeking your own death, I will grant you your wish!"

Saying this, he aimed at Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng and sent four punches at them.

The fist qi burst out, transforming into a human strength phantom in midair, having Hei Lou Lan's appearance.

The four fist shadows split up, one of them charged towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng, while the other three went towards Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan was a mortal, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a Gu Immortal, targeting the weakest link was a common strategy.

Three human strength phantoms attacked Fang Yuan, and the last one was to prevent Tai Bai Yun Sheng from reinforcing him.

"Quickly retreat!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was shocked, he gave a quick warning.

He was very familiar with this strength path killer move's power.

He had obtained a lot of defensive Gu worms in Hu Immortal blessed land thanks to Fang Yuan's gift.

But after battling for so long, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's defensive Gu worms were mostly dead, he even suffered heavy injuries several times, it showed the power of Hei Lou Lan's strength path killer move!

Three human strength phantoms flew over with an imposing aura, whipping up a fierce wind.

"What a strong killer move!" Even Mo Yao's will in his mind praised upon seeing this: "Be careful, Hei Lou Lan's strength path killer move definitely surpasses your four arm earth king killer move!"

Fang Yuan snickered, he showed no fear but instead, oozed with battle intent, ready to fight.

"Of course I won't use four arm earth king, because I have an even stronger strength path killer move." Saying this, he paused for a while, before shouting: "Come, six arm heavenly zombie king!"

Bam!

A formless aura burst out.

The horrifying pressure flooded the surrounding area.

Intense pain could be felt, like surging waves, they attacked one's heart!

Fang Yuan however, felt immeasurable pleasure, his body expanded rapidly, his skin lost its gloss and moisture, becoming dark and hard.

His defense rose rapidly!

In just a moment, he transformed into a six metre tall giant.

On his back, six huge monstrous arms grew out, the fingers were thick and scary, each having their own distinctive appearance, it made people feel fear upon seeing them.

Three human strength phantoms arrived before Fang Yuan.

"Good timing." Fang Yuan muttered, facing them head on with no fear!

As fists and legs clashed, they fought directly!

Bam bam bam...

Thunderous explosions occurred endlessly.

Be it Fang Yuan, or Hei Lou Lan's three human strength phantoms, they had great power and each of their blows tore through the air.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a worried expression, but after watching for a few breaths' time, his eyes expanded.

Fang Yuan was a mere mortal, but he could face off against three human strength phantoms at once.

The two were evenly matched!

But the three human strength phantoms had sentience, after failing to take him down, they started cooperating, pincer attacking Fang Yuan from his front, upper left corner, and lower right corner.

"Be careful!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted to warn him, he had previously suffered greatly due to this.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, displaying his grand demeanour.

He had previously activated his killer move, growing six monstrous arms, with his own two arms, he had eight arms.

The eight arms moved in a circular motion, the punches were executed like a fierce rain, it defended him tightly. He managed to completely block the three human strength phantoms attacking from all directions without a single weak point.

"He actually blocked it, this killer move..." Hei Lou Lan's heart jumped, his expression turned grim.

"Sigh, half an immortal's battle strength, this guy is a monster..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng saw this and sighed. He was surprised, and yet not surprised.

Thinking of his master, everything could be explained.

Thus, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart was at ease, he could concentrate on dealing with the human strength phantom fighting against him.

He waved his sleeve, and countless lights flew out from it.

Chainsaw wind blade, flame sword flash, azure blue water python, golden silk net...

Up to a hundred Gu worms were activated at once, they gave off a dazzling rainbow light, resembling fireworks.

The human strength phantom was covered by the smoke, its speed became slower, thus it immediately changed directions and shot out like lightning.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng's attacks followed after it, it was unceasing.

A fireworks-like display of attacks were unleashed endlessly.

The human strength phantom had the ability to think, it knew how to fly in an arc, attempting to get close to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng also retreated at the same time, while his attacks showed no signs of slowing down.

He was a Gu Immortal with near limitless primeval essence. If not for the fact that he had just become a Gu Immortal and had not made any accumulations, resulting in a low quantity of Gu worms, he would have hundreds and thousands of Gu worms, once used together, they would create a terrifying attack.

Human strength phantom could block most of the attacks, but under the flurry of attacks, it continued to be weakened, and the phantom was turning lighter and more transparent.

But Hei Lou Lan's motive had been achieved.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not have a strong attacking method, he could only weaken the human strength phantom slowly.

He was old and wise, but because he was vigilant and had never charged ahead courageous, it was difficult for him to be an effective reinforcement for Fang Yuan.

This was because of his nature, otherwise, back then, he would not have chosen the 'as before' time path inheritance from the three immortal inheritances.

However, even though Hei Lou Lan achieved his goals in this battle, he was unable to be happy.

That was because he realized — Fang Yuan did not need reinforcements!

Over there, Fang Yuan was fighting three human strength phantoms at once, both sides used attacks to counter attacks, the six arm heavenly zombie king's defense was truly astounding.

"Hahaha!" Fang Yuan got more ferocious as he fought, his punches and kicks were lively and their speed was increasing. In the end, his fist shadows turned into a black afterimage from his sheer speed!

The three human strength phantoms were expended greatly in the battle.

Bam, bam, bam.

Three explosions occurred, the three human strength phantoms could not sustain themselves anymore and were smashed to bits, turning into fist qi and vanishing.

Hei Lou Lan's pupils shrunk, but the battle intent in his heart surged like raging tides.

"Interesting, this killer move is very powerful, it is almost on par with my killer move. But most importantly, he has such rich battle experience, his physical combat skills can be said to be at a master's level! If it were others, they might not be able to unleash the power of this killer move to such an extent!"

Hei Lou Lan licked his lips, his eyes were shining with ruthlessness and excitement.

The earlier attack was not his full strength, he was only probing.

The battle with Tai Bai Yun Sheng was very annoying, because Tai Bai Yun Sheng was escaping most of the time, while Hei Lou Lan could not catch up to him, thus he could not use any of his strength.

Now that this Fang Yuan who was a tough opponent appeared, his battle intent naturally surged.

After destroying three human strength phantoms, Fang Yuan did not attack rashly, but instead floated in the same spot.

The two were about a thousand steps away, and their vicious gazes were colliding.

"Stop fighting, come over here and help!" At this time, Hei Lou Lan heard Giant Sun's will's instructions.

"But, old ancestor..." Hei Lou Lan hesitated, his battle intent was wavering.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's status in his heart was still very high.

This was not about personality, but because he had been influenced to feel the pride of his bloodline since he was young. This was a significant element in Hei Lou Lan's self worth.

"Forget about them. Killing the otherworldly demon and taking back the luck path true inheritance is most important!" Giant Sun's will replied quickly: "This is the only record of this luck path true inheritance that I left behind in the entire world. Even in Longevity Heaven, I did not leave behind any details regarding it. I am about to open the entrance to the true inheritance secluded domain, you will go and help push this luck path true inheritance into the secluded domain."

This round was already controlled by Giant Sun's will, the treemen filled the area like a sea. However, even though Giant Sun's will had the ability to break apart the luck path true inheritance by force, he could not do so.

Firstly, it took too much time, that could lead to unexpected consequences.

Secondly, breaking apart the luck path true inheritance was the same as destroying the supreme true inheritance.

Chapter 622: Grasping the biggest flaw!

The situation in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building twisted and turned with no end in sight.

Once the invincible being dominating the entire world, the ruler of an era, the rank nine Immortal Venerable Giant Sun; the terrifying will that he had specially left behind to take charge of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building....

The winner of the last Imperial Court contest, the current tribe leader of a super force, Hei tribe, possessing the Great Strength True Martial Physique of the ten extreme physiques, Hei Lou Lan....

Standing tall above the centre of northern plains as countless years of change were experienced, and yet imprisoned for hundreds of thousands of years - the land spirit Frost Jade Peacock...

A living legend, helping the injured for almost all his life, his benevolence and his name renowned far and wide, owning a Gu Immortal inheritance, advancing to a rank six Gu Immortal, possessing two mysterious Immortal Gu, Tai Bai Yun Sheng...

As well as.

The owner of Spring Autumn Cicada, ranked seventh amongst the top ten mystical Gu, the owner of Hu Immortal blessed land, a mortal who has possession of multiple Immortal Gu, a reborn five hundred year old demon, Gu Yue Fang Yuan...

Favored by rank eight fortune rivalling heaven Gu, a Gu Immortal in Fang Yuan's previous life who had successively inherited Giant Sun's inheritance and an opportunity left behind by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, becoming a great hero of northern plains who resisted the invasion of central continent, Ma Hong Yun...

Viewed as an 'otherworldly demon' by Giant Sun's will, Ma Hong Yun's wife in Fang Yuan's previous life who became a wisdom path Gu Immortal and provided an innumerable amount of assistance to her husband, the legendary woman Zhao Lian Yun...

And also.

The former rank seven Gu Immortal, a refinement path grandmaster, the thirty-sixth generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House - Mo Yao who had schemed against Eighty-Eight True Yang Building; the mysterious will she left behind following her death...

All these existences had their own thoughts with their respective goals. And on this platform of the collapsing Imperial Court blessed land, they collided and contended with each other.

They had their own advantages, abilities and also had their respective weaknesses and flaws.

These were all individuals overflowing with talents, they were elites or heroes of their generations. They were either proficient in scheming and strategizing, being master tacticians, or had immense strength or absurd luck.

The intense stimulation of life and death, the enticement of enormous benefits, caused these existences to perform to their full strength, using all their abilities and trump cards, perhaps betting it all and risking everything in a single moment, or strategizing to control the situation.

Thus, the state of affairs became clear from time to time, while turning indistinct at the next moment.

They had contended till now, but the situation was still chaotic. Only Frost Jade Peacock was pulled out of the game, while the others could tilt the whole set of circumstances with their every move and were not existences that could be underestimated in their influence to the final outcome.

Now —

The main part of Giant Sun's will had been forced out of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building for the moment by Fang Yuan's trump card, suffering the intense assaults of the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity.

Giant Sun's will was the most powerful existence among those present. On one hand, his main portion tried to return to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and on the other, he took the risk of drawing out the sub-wills from true inheritances to seize back the control of the round, and then wholeheartedly tried to eliminate the otherworldly demon Zhao Lian Yun.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun had become the masters of Imperial Court blessed land by some twist of fate; they were also being protected by the luck path true inheritance and were safe for the moment.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng had made a temporary alliance, engaging in a round of probing confrontation with Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan's battle intent soared violently and he was just about to fight Fang Yuan head-on, when Giant Sun's will asked him to leave and deal with Ma Hong Yun to take back the luck path true inheritance.

Hei Lou Lan hesitated, but chose to listen to Giant Sun's will in the end.

"I will let you guys off for the moment!" He glared at Fang Yuan before turning around and leaving quickly.

Fang Yuan looked on as Hei Lou Lan left, floating in the sky without giving chase.

"Huff huff..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng let out a breath of turbid air, flying towards Fang Yuan.

He might be a Gu Immortal, but he only specialized in healing and lacked large numbers of mortal Gu; his battle strength compared to ordinary Gu Immortals still had a great discrepancy. Through a prolonged battle, he had slowly worn down that human strength phantom to death.

"Hei Lou Lan is going to deal with Ma Hong Yun to retrieve the luck path true inheritance! Should we intervene in this?" Mo Yao's will immediately suggested.

This luck path true inheritance was a supreme hidden treasure left behind by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used it as part of his journey in becoming the ruler of an era, invincible within the world.

This luck path true inheritance held extremely large temptation to any Gu Master!

Fang Yuan's gaze slightly flickered, but he did not move, instead turning his sight to look at his left.

Not far from him, a whirlwind was forming.

"Careful, Hei Lou Lan's fist qi can still condense back even after being destroyed!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng warned.

Fang Yuan snorted, and with one step, appeared before the hurricane, punching it.

Boom.

A muffled sound rang out and the fist qi was scattered again.

The first aura was mostly dissipated, but the remaining fist qi still persisted in condensing back. But this quantity was rather small and was not able to condense into form.

"This strength path killer move..." Fang Yuan's expression was heavy.

Strength path phantoms were the long range attacking method of strength path, however this was the first time Fang Yuan had seen human strength phantoms possessing such spirituality.

This seemed to be an innovation of which no records existed in all the Gu Master history Fang Yuan knew of.

It could be even called as 'Hei Lou Lan's strength path phantom'.

More importantly, this 'Hei Lou Lan's strength path phantom' could condense back even after being destroyed.

This gave the feeling of a 'never-ending source of harassment'!

"Hei Lou Lan has certainly not used his full strength, if he can attack with twenty human strength phantoms at the same time, and the remaining fist qi can condense again, that power would be terrifying. If he can send out thirty human strength phantoms, then this strength path killer move can absolutely contend with your six arm heavenly zombie king!" Mo Yao's will evaluated with a grave tone.

"What killer move is this, do you have any impressions of it?" Fang Yuan asked.

Mo Yao's will slowly shook her head: "I am not a strength path Gu Immortal, this killer move also greatly involves soul path and qi path, in addition it has other pivotal mechanics. It should be a modern innovation as it is greatly different from ancient styles, I am guessing that this is an innovation of the current generation."

Six arm heavenly zombie king was researched by Fang Yuan and perfected by Mo Yao.

But there were no lack of geniuses in this world, it was not just Fang Yuan alone who could innovate a strength path killer move.

Of course, Fang Yuan specialized in blood path in his previous life, and had only cultivated strength path on the side.

Treemen flocked one after the other, forming a majestic green wave that attempted to drown Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

However, Giant Sun's luck path true inheritance was like a giant golden egg that firmly protected the two.

Giant Sun's will was concerned about the consequences of his actions; he truly wanted to kill the otherworldly demon Zhao Lian Yun, but also wanted to protect this unique existence that was Giant Sun's luck path true inheritance.

When he saw Hei Lou Lan near, he hurriedly transmitted his voice: "I will open the passage to true inheritance secluded domain, help me push the luck path true inheritance into it!"

Hei Lou Lan nodded. His whole body shook as he punched out with both his fists; fist qi surged out violently!

Boom boom boom...

Muffled explosions rang out in the air non-stop, the fist qi condensing one after another into Hei Lou Lan's strength path phantoms.

Ten, twenty, thirty... forty!

Fang Yuan's pupils could not help but shrink upon seeing this.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression turned pale, revealing intense fear in his eyes.

Forty of Hei Lou Lan's strength path phantoms moved down together and surrounded the luck path true inheritance in just a moment.

A dark crack slowly appeared in the air above the luck path true inheritance. The crack enlarged till it formed a large and round passage.

This deep, dark passage was directly linked to true inheritance secluded domain.

Strength path phantoms shouted together before actually lifting Giant Sun's true inheritance slightly!

The surrounding treemen also moved their large hands to help. The python-like green vines coiled around together to assist in this.

Giant Sun's True Inheritance erupted with an intense and dazzling light; the treemen melted like snow, the coiling vines could not even last for two breaths before being destroyed completely.

Strength path phantoms also continued to crumble but condensed back a short while after.

Hei Lou Lan stood at the outer periphery; he was like an endless source of strength, striking out with large numbers of strength path phantoms one after another.

Under his effort, Giant Sun's true inheritance slowly left the ground.

At the same time, the round passage in the air also erupted with an intense force of suction, like a giant mouth attempting to take back Giant Sun's true inheritance into its belly.

"He can actually form so many strength path phantoms simultaneously! What kind of killer move is this?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng cried out involuntarily at this astonishing sight.

Mo Yao's will also said to Fang Yuan: "Your strength path killer move is specialized for close combat. Hei Lou Lan's killer move, however, is the exact opposite of yours, specializing in long range combat! This killer move is equally matched with your six arm heavenly zombie king. But in Hei Lou Lan's hands, the strength it can erupt with far surpassess yours by several times."

Hei Lou Lan was the possessor of Great Strength True Martial Physique of the ten extreme physiques, and Fang Yuan was not.

In the legends, Gu Masters who had Great Strength True Martial Physique not only had immense strength, their stamina would also never run out. At the same time, their self recovery ability was also extremely astonishing!

Any strength path killer move would erupt with strength that far surpassed their usual strength under the hands of Great Strength True Martial Physique.

"What should we do now?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng stood beside Fang Yuan, fixing his gaze at the contest of strength between Hei Lou Lan and Giant Sun's true inheritance.

He continued with a regretful tone: "This is a supreme true inheritance! Giant Sun's will is taking it back to true inheritance secluded domain, unfortunately Hei Lou Lan is there, so we cannot get a share of the action."

His tone contained the meaning of not being able to contend with Hei Lou Lan.

This was not surprising, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a passive nature; a wise man looks after his own hide, he would not take extreme measures unless forced into a corner.

Fang Yuan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng and smiled.

"What to do?" He asked and answered himself, "Of course we go to true inheritance secluded domain!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was surprised: "True inheritance secluded domain?"

Mo Yao's will shook before reacting, almost slapping her own thigh at the sudden realization: "Right, there is no more of Giant Sun's will remaining in true inheritance secluded domain. Those true inheritances have become masterless objects!"

Previously, these true inheritances contained Giant Sun's will, thus one could only obtain the qualifications for the true inheritances by using an owner token.

But it was different now, Giant Sun's will had moved away all the sub-wills. Young wild will grew soon after in the true inheritances, and they only needed to be manipulated appropriately to refine them easily.

"But you don't have much time, Giant Sun's main will outside the tower is going to return soon. You will only be able to choose one true inheritance in this time." Mo Yao's will reminded, "Fang Yuan, you must quickly consider which inheritance you are going to choose!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng also realized this and asked another crucial question: "This round is already controlled by Giant Sun's will, how do we enter true inheritance secluded domain?"

He had not even finished speaking when Fang Yuan took out Fixed Immortal Travel Immortal Gu.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had held this Immortal Gu for safekeeping before, thus he was not surprised; but his gaze turned serious as he looked at Fang Yuan: "If I am not wrong, Fixed Immortal Travel can only carry one person, right?"

"You are right." Fang Yuan nodded, "So open up your immortal aperture and let me in. I will send you the image of true inheritance secluded domain through thoughts transmission."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng suddenly realized: "I almost forgot that I am a Gu Immortal!"

The immortal aperture of rank six and rank seven Gu Immortals was called a 'blessed land'.

Imperial Court blessed land, Lang Ya blessed land and Hu Immortal blessed land were immortal apertures; they had vast space and were akin to a small world. Tai Bai Yun Sheng's Tai Bai blessed land was naturally not an exception.

Fang Yuan lent Fixed Immortal Travel to Tai Bai Yun Sheng and entered his immortal aperture, then sent his thoughts that recorded the image of true inheritance secluded domain.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng activated Fixed Immortal Travel, Giant Sun's will had no spare energy to stop him and could only let him go to true inheritance secluded domain one step earlier.

Within the true inheritance secluded domain was a scene of chaos.

The dozens of true inheritances were ruled by new wild wills and were like headless chickens, flying around chaotically. From time to time, they collided with each other, letting out sparks and causing unceasing wear and tear.

Mo Yao felt great heartache at this scene: "Make your choice quickly. These true inheritances are destroying each other, if the situation gets worse, even if you can get an inheritance, it might have already lost its essence."

Fang Yuan did not have much time left and could only pick one true inheritance. He had already made a plan for this.

He said in a deep voice: "Mo Yao, I need your help."

"Speak quickly."

"Point me the location of the final supreme true inheritance!"

Mo Yao was stumped at Fang Yuan's words.

Soon, her eyes and mouth opened wide, her mind was greatly shaken!

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building contained three supreme true inheritances. Mo Yao was extremely clear about them and she had introduced them to Fang Yuan when he had charged into true inheritance secluded domain before.

The first supreme true inheritance was rank nine wisdom Gu.

The second supreme true inheritance was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path inheritance.

The third supreme true inheritance was Eighty-Eight True Yang Building itself!

That is to say the one who obtains this true inheritance could control Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!!

"Why did I not think of it?" Mo Yao mumbled in a daze, "Giant Sun's will had transferred all the sub-wills away, now is the best time to seize the authority over Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

"Right! Giant Sun's will had neglected this in fulfilling his desire to deal with Zhao Lian Yun, thus exposing his greatest flaw, and giving us the opportunity to turn around this crisis!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with a sharp brilliance.

He looked at his surroundings, the fire of ambition soaring ever so high in his heart.

He acutely grasped the flaw in the enemy!

Win or lose, it all depended on this move; as long as he could take Eighty-Eight True Yang Building for himself, he would have the territorial advantage!

By that time, even if Giant Sun's main will were to be more formidable, he would only be a despondent dog locked out of the house, standing at the door and barking helplessly!

Chapter 623: Refining Eighty-Eight True Yang Building

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng moved forward in the true inheritance secluded domain.

In the dark true inheritance secluded domain, there was no more of the order and serenity from before.

Because Giant Sun's will had been extracted fully, the dozens of true inheritances here were ownerless inheritances, wild wills formed in them within a short time.

These true inheritances were like shooting stars of all colors, flying extremely quickly in this dark space, they weaved a beautiful huge net with their trails.

Swoosh!

Another true inheritance flew quickly past Fang Yuan's left side.

This true inheritance was only the size of a bowl, it was giving off a silvery light and was very dazzling.

It almost touched Fang Yuan's body as it flew past, the silvery light shone on Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng's faces.

Their expressions were quite ugly, their gazes were full of anxiety and nervousness.

These true inheritances were powerful and had special abilities, most of them had Immortal Gu among the Gu worms in them. Be it Fang Yuan or Tai Bai Yun Sheng, they could not endure an attack from them.

Especially now, when the true inheritances were guided by the newly birthed wills, who knew when they would display their Immortal Gu abilities?

This could not be predicted!

Moving around this place was like walking on a tightrope above death.

"These true inheritances are getting faster, have you found the target yet?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted at Fang Yuan, his voice was trembling.

"Soon." Fang Yuan answered.

He also felt the pressure intensifying, even though he was a flying master and had exceptional skill, the pressure now was tremendous.

Bam!

Just at this moment, there was a loud explosion.

"Oh no, quickly dodge!" In Fang Yuan's mind, Mo Yao reminded.

Not far away, two true inheritances collided, from the intense sounds produced by them, several Gu worms were destroyed on the spot.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had yet to feel pity at this, when his expression paled.

The collision changed the two true inheritances' directions, one of them which was bright yellow flew towards them.

During the moment of crisis, Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly activated all of his defensive Gu, setting up a hundred lines of defense around him and Fang Yuan.

The incoming true inheritance came with a strong force, destroying all of the defensive lines without any difficulty.

But during this period, Tai Bai Yun Sheng managed to earn some precious time for him and Fang Yuan to escape.

The shrill sound almost burst their eardrums, as the meteor-like true inheritance flew away with a blazing tail.

In the blink of an eye, it was more than ten thousand steps away from the two of them.

"My defense Gu were almost all destroyed!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression was pale: "Where there is life, there is hope, we should retreat."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had the intention of leaving already.

Fang Yuan frowned, he was very clear on Tai Bai Yun Sheng's nature.

The older one was, the more cowardly they become.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng lacked the enthusiasm and spirit to take risks now, it was fine to ask him to heal others, but he was not an expert at putting himself into life and death situations.

Just as Fang Yuan was thinking of what to say to spur Tai Bai Yun Sheng's fighting spirit, Mo Yao screamed in his mind: "Quickly look, just above you guys, we found it!"

Fang Yuan's mind became sharp, he quickly looked up.

Indeed, a supreme true inheritance was flying slowly, the speed of the light lump was not fast, it was a stark contrast to the other ordinary true inheritances.

It was the size of an adult person, glowing with an orange and red light, giving off the feeling of warmth.

The surrounding true inheritances, when they got close to it, took detours and changed their directions.

Between Gu worms, there was absolute authority when they had a difference of two ranks.

The authority of a supreme true inheritance was not something ordinary or unparalleled true inheritances could offend.

"Go!" Fang Yuan was overjoyed, he shouted at Tai Bai Yun Sheng before flying over.

　　...

"Hold on! All of you hold on!" Ye Lui Sang's eyes were red, he shouted loudly as he activated his Gu worms, emitting fierce flames.

The flames burned, quickly spreading.

The golden horn leopard group that was attacking them had good resistance to high temperature. But Ye Lui Sang's flames used the power of an Immortal Gu, the golden horn leopard group quickly melted in the flames, turning into puddles of golden mud.

Seeing this, the surrounding Gu Masters cheered loudly.

"Lord Ye Lui Sang is incredible!"

"Thankfully lord is here, otherwise we would be dead meat."

Ye Lui Sang breathed roughly, he was exasperated, helpless and angry.

"Damn it, what is going on? First, Tai Bai Yun Sheng became an immortal, next Imperial Court blessed land was facing destruction, ravaged by the once in ten years blizzard. Now even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has come into the picture. I thought we could leave the trap, but the building's rounds suddenly triggered! If I knew this, I would not have entered the last Imperial Court contest!"

Ye Lui Sang was scolding in his heart.

Not just him, Ma Ying Jie, Luo Bo Jun, Gu Guo Long and the other survivors were all kept in the dark, they did not know the truth.

These people were all northern plains Gu Masters who had entered Imperial Court blessed land.

After Imperial Court blessed land was torn with several holes, the once in ten years blizzard entered and wreaked havoc, killing almost all the mortals. Large numbers of low rank Gu Masters were injured or dead.

But later, Giant Sun's will's found some time, despite being busy, to save some of the blood related descendants.

Ye Lui Sang and the others were placed into the golden leopard round.

When Fang Yuan activated the final trump card and sent Giant Sun's will out of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building temporarily, without Giant Sun's will controlling the round, the large golden horn leopard group started attacking Ye Lui Sang and the others fiercely.

　　...

Outside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The golden sand-like Giant Sun's will was covered the building like a thick layer of armor.

Meanwhile, the terrifying heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity had combined into one, fusing to connect heaven and earth, it was pure white like snow, like a giant cocoon, enveloping the entire Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and Giant Sun's will in it.

Outside the cocoon, wild winds blew, sharp blades made of ice were flying around everywhere. Inside the cocoon, lightning flashed and the snow poured like a storm.

Crack!

A snow-white lightning flash was formed abruptly, in the shape of a trident.

The strange lightning descended from heaven, stabbing into Giant Sun's will.

"Snow war tribulation lightning!"

Giant Sun's will howled, this attack destroyed a large portion of Giant Sun's will. There was a huge injury appearing on the golden sand-like armor.

This snow war tribulation lightning had amazing strength, it was extraordinary. Even Gu Immortals would be moved when they see it, because it was one of the publicly recognised top ten catastrophes!

Just this hit alone destroyed countless numbers of Giant Sun's thoughts.

But Giant Sun's will was left behind by an Immortal Venerable, its foundation was immensely thick. The will that was like a golden sand armor quickly repaired itself.

But other than the snow war tribulation lightning, there were also flying needle rain, explosive thunder hail, cruel wind scythe and others.

These did not exist earlier, they were formed from Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heavenly tribulation chaotic lightning balls and earthly calamity restraining smoke, fusing with the once in ten years blizzard.

Heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities continued to rain down carrying the intense rage of heaven and earth.

Giant Sun's will resisted them desperately, his losses were great.

"Soon, very soon! In just several minutes, I will be able to break free of this obstacle and enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building again... You actually dared to expel me from the building, and keep me outside! I will tear your tendons and bones out, I will grind you to ashes, I will make you suffer a fate worse than death!" Giant Sun's will had already transcended anger when he thought of Fang Yuan.

　　...

Inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there was still a small portion of Giant Sun's will.

Right now, he was controlling the treemen round, manipulating them in trying to push Giant Sun's inheritance back to the true inheritance secluded domain.

"Softly, don't be too rough, this is the only one in the world!" Giant Sun's will paid close attention to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was extremely irritated, but he could only reduce his strength.

This was the one and only record of this luck path true inheritance that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had left behind, once it was destroyed, it would be irrecoverable.

Precisely because of this consideration, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun who were inside the luck path true inheritance were able to survive.

The two of them were hugging each other closely, they had no choice but to watch the giant light ball that was the luck path true inheritance slowly pushed towards the round tunnel.

Even though they were famous and powerful characters in Fang Yuan's previous life, both Gu Immortals, right now, they were still too weak.

One was a newly advanced rank three Gu Master, while the other was a mortal who had not even started her cultivation journey.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng and that Chang Shan Yin have gone missing." Success was at hand, as Hei Lou Lan could not control it anymore, saying.

Ever since Fang Yuan vanished, he had felt a vague sense of unease.

"Forget about them, in just a moment my main will is going to return. By then, even if two or three more Gu Immortals come, they cannot do anything. The important thing now is to get this luck path true inheritance into the true inheritance secluded domain! Most luck path Gu worms are formless and ethereal. Only that place can contain these Gu worms." Giant Sun's will's voice resounded in Hei Lou Lan's ears.

Hei Lou Lan nodded, shouting lowly as he mustered his strength.

At once, he unleashed fifty strength path phantoms.

These strength path phantoms had superior wisdom, they quickly rushed towards the luck path true inheritance. Enduring the blazing light, they pushed.

The luck path true inheritance was finally completely pushed into the true inheritance secluded domain by this force.

The tunnel closed.

"Success." Giant Sun's will breathed out a deep sigh.

Almost at the same time, the giant main will charged into the building.

Giant Sun's will which was controlling the treemen round fused with the main will, sharing their memories together.

"Fang Yuan, where are you?!" The main will screamed loudly with deep hatred.

"Greetings to old ancestor." Hei Lou Lan bowed deeply, showing great joy.

The main will was like a small sun, it shone brightly and was very domineering.

It could be said that Hei Lou Lan had helped Giant Sun's will in many ways.

Giant Sun's will was just about to praise him, but suddenly shouted in anger: " You are all courting death! You dare to refine my Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

Inside Giant Sun's secluded domain, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng stretched out their palms, pressing the true inheritance light lump forcefully, their expressions were pale and their bodies were shivering.

"Quickly! Just one last bit and we would succeed!!" In his mind, Mo Yao's will shouted anxiously.

Chapter 624: Shameless and devious scoundrel!

In true inheritance secluded domain, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were firmly holding a supreme true inheritance from its left and right.

Thanks to the guidance of Mo Yao's will along with Giant Sun's will being emptied out, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were able to get close to the true inheritance.

The most crucial point was there was no primeval energy in true inheritance secluded domain.

Wild Gu worms could absorb primeval energy directly from the surrounding air for their use. Without primeval energy, most Gu worms would lose their threat. This was also one of the reasons Giant Sun's will was trying to push Giant Sun's Luck Path True Inheritance back into true inheritance secluded domain.

The supreme true inheritance had been letting out a warm orange light before, but in Fang Yuan's and Tai Bai Yun Sheng's hands, it let out three colors.

Silver-white light occupied the bulk of it; caused by the refinement from Tai Bai Yun Sheng's Gu Immortal will. The second color was grey from Fang Yuan. The third was black light from Mo Yao.

Silver-white light was the most abundant, grey came second and black was in the least amount.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was a rank eight Immortal Gu House, formed from extremely large numbers of Gu worms. Fang Yuan's group had to use all their strength to quickly refine Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

It could be said, whether it was Fang Yuan or Tai Bai Yun Sheng, they had both spent all their strength.

"Just a little left, just a little more effort!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng anxiously yelled.

The main portion of Giant Sun's will had returned to True Yang Building, the three had heard its furious roar.

The round light lump with the size of an adult had only a final trace of orange left on it. As long as this light was eroded, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would completely change its master and the situation would greatly incline towards Fang Yuan's side!

However, Giant Sun's will furiously made his move at this final moment.

The will left by an Immortal Venerable could not be looked down upon!

And this will was the original master of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building! Thus, in just an instant, the final trace of orange was replaced by dazzling golden light.

Fang Yuan's group immediately felt gloomy at this color.

This color meant that Giant Sun's will had refined the final remaining trace of the supreme true inheritance's will!

"Juniors, you are really audacious, you dare to go after my Eighty-Eight True Yang Building! I will make you pay the most terrible price in the world!" From within the light lump, a roar from Giant Sun's will sounded out.

"Quick! There is only a meagre trace of Giant Sun's will, we need to move together and destroy it, spare no energy!!" Fang Yuan shouted.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's forehead was filled with sweat; he did not need any reminder to be aware of the utmost importance of this matter.

The two gave a deep shout and moved together, mobilising their wills to form a huge army of thoughts that unfolded a fierce assault towards the last trace of will.

Giant Sun's will's roar stopped abruptly as he poured all his energy in defending against the assault.

Its main body was enormous, but it had only refined a trace of the true inheritance and controlled the smallest portion. Even if it possessed majestic strength that far surpassed the allied thoughts army of Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, it did not have the room to display its might, and the power it could let out was an insignificant fraction compared to that of the main body.

The newborn wild will that had been born just recently in the supreme true inheritance had already been thoroughly extinguished.

The tranquil true inheritance light lump became an unconventional battlefield that pitted Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Giant Sun's will.

Contest between wills involved profound techniques and skill.

But be it Fang Yuan or Tai Bai Yun Sheng, they were not truly soul path Gu Masters. Fang Yuan could be considered to have started it just recently while Tai Bai Yun Sheng was truly a novice, relying on nothing more than the instinct to move his thoughts.

As for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, his soul path attainment was definitely out of this world. Unfortunately, the one confronting the enemy was only the special will he had left behind.

Thus, in this battle of wills, there were no fancy skills; it was only a head-on collision, a bloody fight.

After a dozen or so breaths later, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng's wills suffered disastrous losses.

The quantity of Giant Sun's will might be small, not even filling one percent of the true inheritance light lump, but it stood lofty and majestic.

The main Giant Sun's will was vast, its power flowed without pause. Every bit of loss it suffered was immediately replenished.

By contrast, Fang Yuan's group might have occupied the advantage of vast quantity, but they did not have high battle strength and were soon lacking the fuel to continue.

"Damn it! We can't expel Giant Sun's will, the situation has gone south!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was deathly pale, the combined attack earlier was their most powerful method, but it showed no effect.

Giant Sun's will was laughing heartily.

Fang Yuan and the group lacked the energy to continue the attack, and after Giant Sun's will had resisted their most intense attacks, he began to expand his territory.

In the true inheritance light lump, the part occupied by golden light began to expand bit by bit.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked on with wide eyes; they staked all their energy, but were only able to slow down Giant Sun's will's speed of expansion.

Giant Sun's will was truly terrifying.

Even when it was schemed against repeatedly before, and most of its will was outside, suffering the deathly attacks from the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, the remaining part was still a tall, mountain-like barrier to Fang Yuan's group.

This enormous difference in their strengths was like a gulf between heaven and earth.

"We are going to lose!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's tone was grave, "This is just a will Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind, I really can't imagine how powerful he was when alive!"

"Damn it, only one last step was remaining!!" Mo Yao's will grabbed her head, her voice mixed with a tone of sobbing and extreme regret, "If only we were a step earlier, as long as we had three breaths of time, we would have succeeded."

"Never mind!" Fang Yuan gnashed his teeth, his expression heavy.

He had not given up yet, speaking with ruthless intent: "In this situation, we are unable to get our hands on Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. We cannot exterminate Giant Sun's will, sooner or later it will swallow the space we occupy. But we have yet to lose! Don't forget, there are still the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities outside True Yang Building!"

"Are you saying?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed, blurting out.

His nature was benevolent and passive, but he was not stupid, and immediately realized when Fang Yuan mentioned it.

"That's right, if I can't obtain it, no one else should think about getting it. Since I can't get Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, I would rather destroy it!" A ruthless glint shone in Fang Yuan's eyes, his tone was so cold it could make the listener shiver.

"But this is Eighty-Eight True Yang Building..." Mo Yao resounded, but her tone was wavering.

She had no choice but to accept this was the best method to escape their predicament.

Giant Sun's will finally stormed into true inheritance secluded domain.

"You two tiny ants, you actually forced me to this extent! You scheming scoundrels, your good days have come to an end, your sins are so great that even death would be letting you off cheaply. I will give you a punishment worse than death! I will peel off your skin, pull your tendons and let blood flow! I will burn your souls in flames and let you taste incomparable suffering for all eternity!"

The golden will roared like a furious sea, and whipped up huge waves with it!

Schemed upon time and time again by Fang Yuan, suffering the unrestrained bombardment of the calamities; Giant Sun's will's fury had already reached the summit, swearing to kill Fang Yuan, the main culprit.

Compared to the golden wave, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were as small as ants.

The flying true inheritances were swallowed by the golden wave, resulting in splashes but they stopped moving soon after.

Giant Sun's will had once again taken control of these inheritances.

However, most of the Gu worms required primeval essence or immortal essence to be activated, and just Giant Sun's will could not activate them.

At present, most of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was controlled by Fang Yuan's group.

As long as they did not let Giant Sun's will obtain Giant Sun's immortal essence, these Gu worms could not be used.

"Start." Fang Yuan gave a soft shout, his gaze flashing with sharp intent.

Giant Sun's will's powerful approach also dispelled Tai Bai Yun Sheng's hesitation. He was already completely tied to Fang Yuan's side and could only choose to forcibly advance together.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building originally shone with an aurora, but with the actions of Fang Yuan's group, the aurora rapidly dimmed until it dissipated.

The furious golden sea suddenly stilled.

The next moment, Giant Sun's will's furious roar reverberated: "Bastards! You dared to make Eighty-Eight True Yang Building stop its operation, you, you damned scoundrels, you damned devious, shameless scoundrels!"

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building might have had wild will before, but it had just been born, thus it had still automatically operated as normal.

However, Fang Yuan's group had refined most of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and they forcibly made it stop its operations.

Even the strongest fort would find it hard to resist an internal collapse.

Although Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had not collapsed, its operations had stopped and just its shell had no might.

Without any might, how could it resist the terrifying heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities?

Fang Yuan's group could neglect Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, in any case, they would not be able to obtain Eighty-Eight True Yang Building if this situation progressed.

However, Giant Sun's will could not neglect it.

This was an inheritance from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, left behind for the benefits of his descendants; it must not be destroyed.

Giant Sun's will was left behind by the Immortal Venerable to manage Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, how could it just watch as the True Yang Building was destroyed?

"Just you wait!" The golden sea of will swiftly retreated.

The vast will of Giant Sun surged out of the tower like water, forming a golden armor as a defense around it.

Giant Sun's will had no choice but to suffer the ravaging bombardment of the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities to protect the weak Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. However, it still left behind a portion of will which surged towards Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng like a furious river.

Fang Yuan, however, let out a breath of turbid air.

Compared to the majestic furious sea from before, this will might be strong but they could deal with it, albeit with difficulty.

Fang Yuan reluctantly took out a Gu from his pocket.

It was flying bear phantom Gu.

Fang Yuan's will moved and threw the Gu casually; the flying bear phantom Gu flew forward, blossoming with beautiful white light.

The white light dissipated and a giant flying bear protected Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, obstructing the river of will.

"Damn it, flying bear phantom Gu!" Giant Sun's will cursed.

Flying bear phantom Gu was rather special; it was an Immortal Gu but it could be activated with just one's mind, without requiring immortal essence.

Refining it was difficult and feeding it was not easy, requiring the fresh flesh of the desolate beast flying bear.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan possessed Hu Immortal blessed land and could feed this Immortal Gu with the help of treasure yellow heaven.

Even so, he had to pay an enormous price.

Train an army for a thousand days to use it in one fight. Now, it was time for flying bear phantom Gu to show its worth!

Chapter 625: Remaining trump card

The flying bear phantom's battle strength, although not at the level of the desolate beast flying bear, it had at least half immortal battle strength. Most importantly, it might look bulky and slow, but it was very agile.

The river of Giant Sun's will swirled to its left and right, attempting to get past the flying bear phantom, to directly attack Fang Yuan and the others, obtaining victory.

But he was still obstructed by the flying bear phantom.

The flying bear phantom, even without Fang Yuan's manipulation, had some intelligence and was quite crafty, it could battle entirely alone.

Swoosh.

The fat and large bear paw slammed down, carrying the sound of the wind with it.

Bam!

The golden sand-like Giant Sun's will was smashed into bits by the bear paw, turning into golden dust as it dissolved in the air.

But this was just a portion.

The golden river that was Giant Sun's will was like a huge python coiling around the flying bear phantom tightly.

At the same time, countless streams of will were formed, attacking many areas of the flying bear phantom.

The two were fighting closely, at a stalemate, neither could do anything to the other party.

Giant Sun's will could fuse and split freely, it had the freedom to change forms, flying bear phantom could not take it down. But Giant Sun's will was entangled by the flying bear phantom and could not deal with the most crucial person — Fang Yuan.

Giant Sun's will had inherited a portion of the Immortal Venerable's wisdom, he knew from the situation after some thinking: To kill Fang Yuan, he needed to use at least half of the river's will.

But the remaining half was not the flying bear phantom's match.

If he attacked forcefully, it was like he was handing the initiative over.

If Fang Yuan retreated with the true inheritance light lump and stalled for time, after the flying bear phantom destroys the portion of Giant Sun's will that was left fighting it, the situation would become dangerous.

He had already suffered a loss from splitting up earlier when he drew his will out of the true inheritance secluded domain.

At that time, Fang Yuan had used the glass owner token to challenge a small portion of Giant Sun's will resolutely. The result was that both suffered injuries and in the end led to Giant Sun's will taking a huge risk and paying a huge price, but only managing to regain control of the treeman round.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim.

He sustained the true inheritance light lump, slowing the progress of Giant Sun's will's expansion while observing the situation and current battle state.

"If Giant Sun's will would split up again, that would be great. Unfortunately, it will not make the same mistake twice." Fang Yuan observed for a while, seeing Giant Sun's will fighting the flying bear phantom so intensely, but yet showing no signs of splitting up, Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

The opponent was not making a mistake, thus Fang Yuan's predicament was getting more dangerous.

Right now, most of Giant Sun's will was outside the building enduring the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities to protect Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, only two other portions were left behind.

A portion was fighting with the flying bear phantom. The other was competing with Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, trying to refine Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The supreme true inheritance that represented Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's ownership only had a trace of golden color originally, but now this trace had grown to size of a palm.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng had already squeezed out their full potential, they were shivering and their expressions were pale, they were sweating profusely but could not resist the expansion of Giant Sun's will's refinement.

Giant Sun's will was simply too great.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt like he was stuck between a towering mountain and a precipitous ridge during the resistance, he was helpless and felt hopelessness.

Even Fang Yuan, a demonic head with an iron will, felt a strong sense of dejection growing in his heart at this point.

If he allowed the situation to develop like this, eventually, when Giant Sun's will successfully expands, he would regain control of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. By then, Fang Yuan and the others would be dead meat.

He had to do something!

Despite this, Fang Yuan had already been too deeply involved in this supreme true inheritance, he could not do anything else.

His greatest battle strength now was the flying bear phantom Gu, but it was already in use.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a temporary ally that he obtained through swindling, but similarly to Fang Yuan, he was already here engaging with Giant Sun's will, he could not do anything else.

It could be said that other than the Spring Autumn Cicada, Fang Yuan had used all of his trump cards.

"Don't tell me, I really have to use the Spring Autumn Cicada this time?" A thought flashed in Fang Yuan's mind.

But immediately after, he rejected it.

"Spring Autumn Cicada is not an Immortal Gu that has a guaranteed success rate, I could fail. The black death bad luck on me right now is so thick. Once I self-detonate, my remaining consciousness would enter the Spring Autumn Cicada and travel upstream in the river of time, everything points to disaster! The chances of survival are extremely slim."

How could he resolve this situation?

"Sigh... Fang Yuan, we have no hope of success, let's retreat! Using Fixed Immortal Travel, we can return to your blessed land." Tai Bai Yun Sheng suggested.

Should he really retreat?

At this point, if he gave in, Giant Sun's will would immediately regain control of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. By then, through his obstruction, would fixed immortal travel Gu still activate successfully?

Even if he succeeded, would this satisfy him?

Fang Yuan was not satisfied!

He had planned this for so long, he racked his brains in scheming, victory was almost in sight, an immense fortune and benefit was right before him, he was just one step away!

Just one tiny step!!

"I am really unresigned ... Wait!" Fang Yuan's expression changed, he thought of Ma Hong Yun.

"I have no trump cards, but I can make use of this chess piece." Inspiration flashed in his mind, Fang Yuan was no longer hesitant, he flapped his wings and flew up with the supreme true inheritance.

"Where are we going?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng asked quickly.

"Just follow me." Fang Yuan replied curtly.

Fixed immortal travel Gu was in his possession and was refined by him, even if Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to retreat, without Fang Yuan's cooperation, he could not escape.

"Don't think of running away!" The river-like Giant Sun's will growled, splitting up and then forming back into one entity again, while passing the flying bear phantom and charging towards Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Flying bear phantom reacted quickly, it followed after them.

Fang Yuan snickered, changing his direction. After moving in many directions, the flying bear phantom returned to Fang Yuan's side.

Fang Yuan fled while battling, as the two sides fought and stopped many times. Sometimes, the river-like Giant Sun's will was in front, sometimes, Fang Yuan took detours, using the flying bear phantom to fight back.

The road was filled with shocks but no real danger.

Although there were true inheritances of all sizes flying around chaotically, because of the supreme true inheritance's aura, none got close.

Using the flying bear phantom as a shield, the river-like Giant Sun's will could not stop Fang Yuan's movement, he could only slow him down.

But Fang Yuan's circumstances were the same.

He and Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not do anything to the portion of Giant Sun's will that was refining Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. In the contest of wills, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were heavily suppressed, the golden light was expanding steadily, the two were bound to lose eventually.

"So you are here!" When Fang Yuan saw the luck path true inheritance in his vision, he laughed loudly.

"What are you trying to do?" The river-like Giant Sun's will felt something amiss, he screamed out in panic.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at Fang Yuan with similar confusion.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Tell me, what will happen when two supreme true inheritances collide?"

The color on Tai Bai Yun Sheng's face changed, Fang Yuan's insanity made his heart jump.

But thinking about it, he realized: This was an amazing and brilliant plan!

He and Fang Yuan were unable to turn back now. The true inheritance light lump in their hands was extremely troublesome, if they let go of it, they would die, but if they did not, they would die sooner or later.

But if the two supreme true inheritances collided, the results would be unthinkable.

The consequences were so severe even Giant Sun's will lost his composure!

"You, don't come over!" Ma Hong Yun shouted.

Zhao Lian Yun was tightly held in his arms.

But on this stage, the two of them were simply the weakest. If not for their extreme luck, they would have been ground to dust long ago during the intense battles.

Under the influence of luck and coincidences, the luck path supreme true inheritance became their guardian angel, but it had been pushed into the true inheritance secluded domain.

After entering the true inheritance secluded domain, the threat of the luck path true inheritance hit rock bottom, it was almost a guaranteed success for Giant Sun's will to deal with the otherworldly demon.

If not for Giant Sun's will being careful about protecting the luck path true inheritance, and being forced to deal with Fang Yuan at every step, thus unable to leave, he would have dealt with Ma and Zhao long ago.

Ma Hong Yun was safe and sound here, in a way, it was all thanks to Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

But now, Fang Yuan was dragging the supreme true inheritance and rushed here on his own.

"He, what is he trying to do?!" Zhao Lian Yun's body was shuddering, through the translucent barrier, she was frantic and could see Fang Yuan's cold smile.

"No, you cannot do this! Quickly stop, stop it!!" The river-like Giant Sun's will was shouting insanely from behind him.

He was anxious!

Once these two supreme true inheritances collide, they would definitely suffer great damage together.

By that time, not only would the last remaining luck path true inheritance get damaged or even destroyed, even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would suffer immense damage that would be hard to imagine.

The river-like Giant Sun's will underwent intense thoughts, all of the thoughts that formed its will started self-detonating.

The golden sand-like will in the shape of a river burst out with an eye piercing light, his battle strength surged by at least half.

The flying bear phantom growled angrily, but was suppressed thoroughly.

Fang Yuan's brows were tightly locked, the situation was very dangerous, he had to put a portion of his concentration on the flying bear phantom, manipulating it to battle personally.

Five hundred years of battle experience was nothing to be scoffed at!

Under his manipulation, the flying bear phantom moved more agilely, it ignored the injuries on it and blocked the river-like Giant Sun's will completely in the end.

"Fang Yuan, you are courting death! You want to deal with Ma Hong Yun, but do not forget the overwhelming power of fortune rivaling heaven Gu that he has! As long as you carry ill intent towards him, your luck will decrease drastically, even if you have half immortal battle strength, and are able to resist it temporarily, how long can you last?" The river-like Giant Sun's will saw that he could not break through and started shouting.

"Fang Yuan, Giant Sun's will is absolutely right, you need to be very careful!" Mo Yao's will also said.

Fang Yuan snorted, without a bit of hesitation in his heart.

Seeking fortune amidst danger, to Fang Yuan, only by emerging victorious amidst chaos could he have a chance of survival.

Seeing that the two supreme true inheritances were less than a thousand steps away from each other, at this moment, there were ripples in the air, as dozens of figures were transported into the true inheritance secluded domain.

They appeared ahead of Fang Yuan's flying route, they were almost all familiar faces.

Ye Lui Sang, Gu Guo Long, Bian Si Xuan...

The leader was a brawny and muscular man, with hammer-like fists, he laughed ruthlessly towards Fang Yuan: "So you are called Fang Yuan! Old Ancestor Giant Sun has already exposed both of your crimes. Your schemes have been exposed, it is all over, your lives will be finished here!"

Who else was it but Hei Lou Lan?

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed abruptly, he could not free himself now as he was using all his strength to resist Giant Sun's will who was refining the supreme true inheritance.

The appearance of Hei Lou Lan and the others was simply too devastating.

At the final juncture, this was akin to a fatal blow!

"Hahaha!" The river-like Giant Sun's will laughed loudly behind them: "You are all just in time!"

He praised Hei Lou Lan and the others fervently.

This was definitely the act of the main will who took some time to inform and mobilize this bunch of reinforcements.

If this was during normal times, Hei Lou Lan and the others contained battle strength that was insignificant in Giant Sun's will's eyes. But at this time and place, they became a life-saving chess piece, they were the best bet in toppling the balance between the two sides!

"Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, you are all dead meat!" The river-like Giant Sun's will growled, slowing down and attacking.

The initiative was grasped by Giant Sun's will's side once again.

"We lost!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng heaved a long sigh, turning over to look at Fang Yuan, mustering his spirit: "Junior brother, enter my aperture, we will retreat! I have immortal essence, and you have Fixed Immortal Travel, now that Giant Sun's will is being troubled by the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, we have to retreat now before it is too late!"

Fang Yuan however, shook his head: "It is already too late! Once we let go, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building will fall into the control of Giant Sun's will. This building has the ability to suck in Immortal Gu, and the range extends to the whole of northern plains, even if we use Fixed Immortal Travel, there is a high chance of failing in the end."

"Of course I know this." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's tone was anxious: "But we can only take a risk, in order to fight for that slim chance of success. If we delay any longer and lose this last opportunity, we would not even have this slim chance of success left!"

Fang Yuan's gaze was flickering in hesitation, he looked at the supreme true inheritance in his hand once again.

In the true inheritance light lump, the golden dazzling light had occupied a third of the light lump's capacity, and was expanding at an increasing speed.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply: "I did not think that we will still get to this point. Sigh, if not for the circumstances, I would not want to do this!"

"Junior brother, you still have a method left?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard this and was shocked, overjoyed, and suspicious.

Chapter 626: Immortal Ascension!

At this moment.

In true inheritance secluded domain.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, who were mutually dependent on each other and under luck path supreme true inheritance's protection, looked with panicked expressions.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were in control of the supreme true inheritance that represented Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The two sides were cut off by Hei Lou Lan and the others, forming a firm defensive line.

Behind Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, the river-like Giant Sun's will and the flying bear phantom were fighting.

Going even farther outside, the main Giant Sun's will covered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, forcibly resisting the terrifying heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, protecting the inheritance treasure of Giant Sun.

Hearing Fang Yuan still had a method left, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was naturally overjoyed and immediately urged: "Junior brother! What method do you have left, quickly use it."

Fang Yuan gave a bitter smile: "Senior brother, honestly, because of this desperate situation, I have no other ways but to use this method. I hope you will ensure my safety at the crucial moment."

"That goes without saying, we are fellow disciples after all!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately guaranteed.

Fang Yuan nodded and instructed: "Senior brother, Giant Sun's will originated from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, you must never underestimate it. Next, if it tries to sow discord between us, I won't be able to talk and defend myself, you must never believe it!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng muttered: "Junior brother, we are of one family, you do not need to say anything and can rest assured. But from your tone, it seems you have a lot of concern and reservation towards using this method, if you are not too sure, we can still use Fixed Immortal Travel and leave immediately!"

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, revealing a confident expression: "Haha! Senior brother, rest assured, this method has unparalleled might, even the main Giant Sun's will cannot leave unscathed. Just watch."

The two had not used any Gu worms to conceal their conversation. The experts present could not help but reveal shock and doubt.

'A method that can harm the main Giant Sun's will, what exactly is it?' Hei Lou Lan frowned, he might looked crude but was actually astute, and did not carelessly move forward to fight.

Under everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan closed his eyes, slowly withdrawing his palms that were tightly grabbing the supreme true inheritance.

This action immediately increased the pressure on Tai Bai Yun Sheng by several times!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was shocked, but fortunately Fang Yuan had reminded him before, and he was able to quickly exert all his strength to resist the fierce encroachment of Giant Sun's will.

"Junior brother, use your method quickly, I cannot hold on for long!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted, beads of sweat dripping down his face.

In just a few short breaths of time, the golden light on the supreme true inheritance light lump wantonly expanded, becoming the size of a washing basin!

The speed was quick and violent!

"Let me see what deceit you are pulling!" Looking at this state, Hei Lou Lan and the group did not dare to rashly charge ahead at this juncture.

However, they had waited for a dozen breaths but still did not see any terrifying offense from Fang Yuan.

This battlefield had sunk into a strange silence.

The two sides did not speak, there were only the swoosh sounds of the flying true inheritances and the occasional collisions of the true inheritances!

"Damn it, we were tricked!" Ye Lui Sang was furious, "This thief that disguised as Chang Shan Yin is truly crafty. He is already at a dead end and has exhausted all his methods, but is still pretending that he has an unfathomable and profound trump card!"

"Everyone let's go, kill this audacious conspirator!" Gu tribe's leader Gu Guo Long shouted from the side.

The leader, Hei Lou Lan, however, did not move.

Not only was he not moving, his expression even turned grave.

"Could it be..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at Fang Yuan with bewilderment, he was the nearest and thus felt a formless heavenly power suddenly forming around Fang Yuan, gently lifting him up.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had an extremely deep impression of this heavenly power, after all he had personally experienced it not long ago.

"Junior brother, you are shattering your aperture and ascending to immortal at this moment?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's words startled everyone present.

The journey of a Gu Master crossing the mortal realm and ascending to an immortal was extremely dangerous and risky. To think Fang Yuan actually recklessly shattered his aperture at this dangerous moment, charging towards Gu Immortal realm.

"Does this guy have a screw loose?"

"He can't even understand his situation, is he stupid?"

"Did he see no chance of success and used this unusual method to die?"

For a moment, Ye Lui Sang and the others were filled with heavy doubts.

But the next moment, Giant Sun's will's furious roar reverberated over the whole of the true inheritance secluded domain: "Fang Yuan! I curse you to have a terrible death!! You actually shattered your aperture at this moment to attract the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity!! You are actually so bent on destroying True Yang Building. Everyone, kill this sinner quickly, the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity are already showing changes!"

This roar was different from before, besides the overflowing fury, Giant Sun's will's voice now also contained panic!

The fusion of so many heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities would not be a simple addition of one plus one equals two.

The once in ten years blizzard wreaked havoc over the whole of northern plains; its range might be large but its might was not great. Even mortals could rely on some special places to forcibly resist it.

The chaotic lightning balls and restraining smoke, left from Tai Bai Yun Sheng's ascension, were mostly targeting wills and were only troublesome for Giant Sun's will.

But these two merged together and formed snow war tribulation lightning!

This was one of the ten great catastrophes!

This tribulation lightning had terrifying power, and Giant Sun's will had to pay a large price to resist it.

Now, if a new heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity was added on top of snow war tribulation lightning and if these two heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities merged together, the resulting change would have unparalleled power!

Even Giant Sun's will felt fear!! It was after all only a special will left behind by the Immortal Venerable, even if it could kill Gu Immortals, but under the might of heaven, it paled in comparison.

"Quick, old ancestor has spoken, we need to attack together!"

"Follow me, kill these two!"

"Heroes of northern plains, crush these two outsiders to meat-paste."

Hei Lou Lan and the rest were startled awake and started acting according to Giant Sun's will's command, fiercely charging forward.

Before they even neared, their respective Gu worms were already activated, forming a majestic offense. Strength path phantoms, malevolent fiery snakes, terrifying sword lights, pure white snow... all kinds of attacks converged together, seemingly forming beautiful fireworks.

The fatal crisis was approaching him, but Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not spare even a trace of his thoughts to it, and used all his strength to resist the encroachment of the portion of Giant Sun's will in the true inheritance light lump.

Fang Yuan opened his eyes, maneuvering the flying bear phantom as well as activating his killer move.

Six arm heavenly zombie king!

He turned into an eight armed monster, his aura erupted and his will to fight flared.

The flying bear phantom gave a miserable howl before using its gigantic body as a meat shield, blocking the attacks.

The river-like Giant Sun's will was free to move, immediately attacking Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan protected Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and welcomed the river-like Giant Sun's will without evading.

Boom!

The two sides fiercely collided, the resulting explosion let out brilliant golden sparks everywhere.

Large numbers of special will shattered and dissipated.

Fang Yuan also suffered heavy injuries; six of his arms broke apart, his chest caved in, his right lower leg was completely gone and one eye was blinded.

"Fang Yuan, your death is certain this time! You dared to ascend to Gu Immortal at this moment, who do you think you are? A reincarnated Immortal Venerable? Hmph, since you are seeking your own death, I shall help you with it."

The river-like Giant Sun's will formed a python shape that coiled around into a circle, accumulating its power, its whole body radiating with dazzling golden radiance.

Fang Yuan snorted, not replying. The terrifying injuries on his body rapidly recovered at a visible speed.

He had transformed into a heavenly zombie; the feeling of pain was completely gone and death energy replaced his life energy. His recovery speed was thus greatly amplified, having no need for any rank five healing Gu.

Boom, boom, boom...

The intense collisions erupted repeatedly; Fang Yuan and the river-like Giant Sun's will carried out an intense battle.

"Thief, come down now!" Giant Sun's will suddenly transformed into a giant hand and fiercely clawed at Fang Yuan's back.

With a tearing sound.

The eagle wings on Fang Yuan's back were directly torn apart, forming two enormous wounds that revealed his bones.

Eagle rise Gu perished!

Fang Yuan was heavily injured, but he did not budge a bit, instead he fiercely twisted his waist.

Crack... He moved with such strength that he actually broke apart his waist!

Disregarding the injuries on his body, Fang Yuan swung his hammer like fist straight into Giant Sun's will.

Boom.....

In an instant, fierce wind surged and fist shadows flew with unstoppable momentum like a dragon overturning the river, like a fierce tiger leaving the mountain.

The giant hand that Giant Sun's will had condensed into had no time to split apart before it was struck by this vicious strike. The massive will was bombarded by the attack and shattered, suffering huge damage.

Amidst the drizzle of golden sand-like will, Fang Yuan took the chance to pull back like a bolt of lightning.

　

Giant Sun's will had been waiting for a counterattack, but could only roar in fury as Fang Yuan was already far away.

Fang Yuan was not a battle maniac and was as cool-headed as ice, never letting himself be overtaken by the heat of the fight. As the injuries on him rapidly healed, Fang Yuan gasped for breath; the pressure on him was as heavy as a mountain in this battle with Giant Sun's will.

He had already used all his strength but there was no doubt this was the strongest opponent he had faced since his rebirth!

The two organized themselves again and after a few breaths of time, they charged at each other again.

"So what if you are an Immortal Gu? Go and die!" On the other battlefield, Hei Lou Lan's violent shout could be heard.

Tens of strength path phantoms suddenly retreated and entered Hei Lou Lan's body.

Hei Lou Lan's body merged with the strength path phantoms, transforming into a giant phantom within moments.

The giant reached a height of over a hundred feet. The muscles on it were bulging and vivid, and its appearance was exactly similar to Hei Lou Lan.

"Feel my killer move!!" The giant strength path phantom's voice rumbled like thunder; it headed straight towards the flying bear phantom and smashed its right fist at the flying bear phantom's skull.

The flying bear phantom was being held under control by Ye Lui Sang and others; caught unprepared, it was sent rolling down.

Smash.

The giant strength path phantom showered the flying bear phantom with punches; the flying bear phantom was heavily injured after suffering the continuous attacks, and angrily counterattacked.

However, the giant strength path phantom was nimble and displayed a master level attainment in close combat. After a while, the flying bear phantom's body was beaten into such a mess that its original appearance was indistinct.

"The final strike!" The giant strength path phantom raised its right leg and smashed down like an axe.

Boom!

A huge rumbling sound echoed, the flying bear phantom could no longer endure and its stout giant body disappeared, turning back into Gu form and flying away shakily.

The giant strength path phantom grabbed the Immortal Gu and smiled malevolently towards Fang Yuan.

"Hei Lou Lan's true strength has reached such a level!"

"Too terrifying, he can almost destroy an Immortal Gu!"

"My loss in this Imperial Court contest was not unjust..."

Ye Lui Sang and others looked on with wide open eyes.

Hei Lou Lan's battle strength was absolutely not inferior to Fang Yuan's, and was even higher in certain aspects because of his Great Strength True Martial Physique.

Flying Bear Phantom was an Immortal Gu but without any Gu worms as assistance and Fang Yuan not maneuvering it personally, it was normal for it to be captured by Hei Lou Lan.

The flying bear phantom was destroyed, while Tai Bai Yun Sheng was using all his strength to contend with Giant Sun's will for the supreme true inheritance. As such, Fang Yuan who was in an intense battle with the river-like Giant Sun's will was alone and facing danger.

"You have a good head on your shoulders, I will take it as my victory trophy and preserve it." Hei Lou Lan's voice came out from the giant strength path phantom.

It slowly flew towards Fang Yuan.

"Fang Yuan, give up resisting. You no longer have a way out!" The river-like Giant Sun's will spoke.

Although it had fought with Fang Yuan only for a short time, its size was already less than half of before.

One could say Fang Yuan, being able to force the Immortal Venerable's will to this state, had tremendous battle strength which was not inferior to Hei Lou Lan's.

Unfortunately, he was shrouded in a black coffin luck aura and his circumstances were extremely bad. Even if he was greatly resourceful and extremely brave, it seemed that he would be unable to reverse this situation!

"Hahaha..." Fang Yuan threw his head back and laughed loudly!

His laughter resounded through the battlefield, displaying a matchless bravery!

"Giant Sun's will, you want to break my spirit by every possible means, but my heart is like iron and my will is like steel! Our battle has just begun."

The river-like Giant Sun's will did not retort, instead falling into silence.

The giant strength path phantom Hei Lou Lan had transformed into also stopped its movements.

Heaven and earth qi manifested around Fang Yuan.

Gu Masters shattered their aperture to ascend to Gu Immortal realm, which would attract heaven and earth qi. Fang Yuan was inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building which delayed this for a moment.

That short moment was the most dangerous and most difficult time, but Fang Yuan was able to hold on by exerting all of his methods.

In the vicinity of heaven and earth qi, ordinary Gu worms could not be used and their activation would cause a backlash. In severe cases, even Immortal Gu could also perish.

Hei Lou Lan was only using mortal Gu, and had no choice but to stop.

The process of Fang Yuan's immortal ascension had officially begun.

Chapter 627: Top Ten Catastrophes, Chaotic Branching Teeth

Clear and glorious heaven qi, golden earth qi, more and more of them surrounded Fang Yuan.

Hei Lou Lan and the others retreated.

The river-like Giant Sun's will growled endlessly, but did not dare to charge in abruptly.

After the intense battle with Fang Yuan, its mass was reduced by more than half.

It was anxious internally: "Damn it! Unless the main will sends reinforcements over, I alone cannot take down this Fang Yuan."

The battlefield turned silent temporarily.

Fang Yuan saw that the situation had progressed just as he expected, breathing out a huge sigh of relief.

In the contest for Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, after several twists and turns, the current situation was becoming clearer.

Fang Yuan's situation was like walking on a tightrope, intense wind was blowing and he was almost blown away several times, losing his initiative. If not for his brilliant schemes and endless trump cards, he would not have lasted this long.

Especially this time, Fang Yuan gambled his life, bravely going for a mutual defeat, finally managing to get back the initiative.

"My northern plains trip has reached the most crucial climax! Next, my immortal ascension is extremely important, it can almost decide victory and loss in this battle!" Fang Yuan concentrated his mind, just as he had said, the real battle was just beginning.

"Junior brother, don't be too careless!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's tone was solemn, his gaze was anxious as his heart was full of worry.

He had just become an immortal, he was extremely clear about the difficulties of immortal ascension. He knew: If not for Giant Sun's will's help, he would not have succeeded. Even if he had his life's accumulation and that deep foundation!

"Sigh, junior brother is too young and daring, he should not have made this choice! Had I known earlier, I would not have let him take this step! Sigh, hopefully, he had received master's guidance and can succeed luckily..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed in his heart.

Fang Yuan made eye contact with Tai Bai Yun Sheng, nodding his head.

Next, he closed his eyes, his mind entering his aperture.

Ordinary Gu Masters and Gu Immortals, in their entire lives, they can only have one aperture. But Fang Yuan had once taken a major risk in three kings blessed land, obtaining an immense opportunity. Thus, after using the second aperture Immortal Gu, he now had two apertures.

After the imperial court contest, both his apertures were rank five peak stage, crystal purple primeval essence!

There were three steps in immortal ascension, the first was to shatter the aperture.

Fang Yuan shattered the second aperture.

When Gu Masters shatter their aperture, they can only advance with no way of retreating. That is because they only have one aperture.

But Fang Yuan had two.

That means, even if Fang Yuan fails this tribulation, he would lose one aperture, but he would still keep another aperture.

Keeping one aperture could preserve his life.

This was one of the benefits of second aperture Gu.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not know this secret, if he knew, the worry in his heart would dissipate greatly.

Crack!

Crack!

Crack!

Lightning bolts shot down endlessly, targeting Giant Sun's will.

"Fang Yuan you scoundrel, you will die a terrible death!" Giant Sun's will howled, he resisted the tribulation lightning as his golden sand-like will exploded time and time again.

This lightning bolt was extraordinary, it had the appearance of a trident and had great power, as one of the ten great catastrophes.

Originally, snow war tribulation lightning did not strike at such close intervals, one bolt would form every tens of breaths' time. But now, when Fang Yuan shattered his aperture and drew in the heaven and earth qi, a new heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity were formed.

The heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity fused with the once in ten years blizzard, increasing the power of the snow disaster.

Snow war tribulation lightning acted like it was on drugs, in its excitement, several bolts were shot down with less than a breath's interval each time!

Every time he resisted it, Giant Sun's will paid a heavy price.

But he could not leave.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building needed his protection.

Now that Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had lost almost all its functions, it was like an empty shell. If Giant Sun's will's protection was lifted, in just a moment, the entire Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would be crumbled under the terrifying might of the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was an inheritance treasury that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had left behind, with Giant Sun's will as the controller of this building. Its main objective forced Giant Sun's will to resist the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity head on.

This way, he had become Fang Yuan's protector during this tribulation.

Protecting his sworn enemy and helping him to ascension to immortal realm, Giant Sun's will, who was forced by circumstances and had to do this, could feel an immense humiliation and rage in his heart.

"Fang Yuan, you scoundrel, once I survive this heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, I will tear your tendons out, I will drink your blood and eat your flesh!" Giant Sun's will howled, even though there was the sound of thunder, it could not mask his rage.

Very soon, his howling came to an end, it turned into shock: "This, this is the chaotic branching teeth!"

Only to see that in the air filled with lightning and thunder, eighteen spirals appeared.

The spirals spun faster and faster, as they expanded rapidly.

In each of these black spirals, there was a large snow-white beast tooth forming slowly.

A total of eighteen beast teeth, each white as snow, with a huge size like that of ancient trees, over thirty meters tall.

The beast teeth were waiting to strike, and an intense feeling of danger struck Giant Sun's will's heart.

Chaotic branching teeth was also one of the top ten catastrophes, ranked higher than even the snow war tribulation lightning, and had greater might.

"I cannot allow all eighteen chaotic branching teeth to strike at the same time! At that time, even I cannot resist it... I must destroy them in advance!!" Giant Sun's will was full of battle experience, he chose to strike immediately.

He had no hesitation, creating ten wills in the form of dragons, flying about and charging towards the heavenly tribulation in the sky with no fear.

However, along the way, there were wind blades, icy hail, and snow war tribulation lightning that attacked non stop. The ten dragon will suffered heavy casualties along the way, only five made it to the spirals.

In fact, the result of their attacks was not very evident.

Only three succeeded, destroying the spirals. The remaining two dragon wills suffered too much damage, the spirals that they charged towards flickered for a bit before recovering.

The tribulation lightning crackled, the speed of attacks becoming even quicker than before! It was like a wordless mockery towards Giant Sun's will.

"Damn it! Despicable!' Giant Sun's will was helpless, he split out another ten dragons and charged again in desperation.

Within true inheritance secluded domain, it was a scene of serenity.

Fang Yuan shut his eyes, his expression was calm and he breathed in relaxation.

His mind was mostly focused on the shattered second aperture.

"My first aperture is my vital Gu Spring Autumn Cicada. This Gu is incomparably important, if I ascend to immortal realm with it, I will be a time path Gu Immortal. But my knowledge of time path is too limited, and to undergo tribulation with Immortal Gu, I cannot take this risk without any experience."

"Only the second aperture, with the vital Gu all-out effort Gu, I can become a strength path Gu Immortal. Since rebirth, I had studied strength path intensely, although it is not on the level of blood path, I still have the foundation to become an immortal."

This second aperture had already shattered into a mess, forming a hole and sucking in the heaven qi and earth qi.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was less than a hundred years old, but he had the foundation and accumulation to become a Gu Immortal. Fang Yuan had five hundred years of experience, and his knowledge surpassed Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had an immortal inheritance, it was definitely more than sufficient for him to rise to immortal.

"Except that now, it is still not the best time to ascend to immortal." Fang Yuan laughed bitterly in his mind.

Fang Yuan's strength path cultivation had not reached its limits. He had only a hundred jun of strength, and his bones were impermanence bones, his skin was turtle jade wolf skin, and his strength path Gu worms were not all rank five.

All these affected his future potential after becoming an immortal, as well as the size of his immortal aperture, it would be best if he could perfect them. Fang Yuan's original intention was to accumulate his foundation to the absolute limit before taking the risk of immortal ascension after making ample preparation.

Unfortunately, plans do not keep up with changes.

Forced by the situation, Fang Yuan could only do this.

As the heaven and earth qi entered his body, at the same time, Fang Yuan's body was emitting a thick white human qi.

The thickness of the human qi was like a huge balloon, completely covering Fang Yuan's entire body.

Hei Lou Lan saw this and his pupils shrunk.

Ye Lui Sang said in disbelief: "How is this possible, he has such thick human qi, this is even greater than Tai Bai Yun Sheng!"

"To think that junior brother's foundation is so deep. I can see that junior brother had made preparations for this immortal ascension long ago, he is not taking an impulsive risk." Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked with a surprised gaze, his heart settling.

The clear and unrestrained heaven qi, the golden and heavy earth qi, together with the pure white as snow human qi, the three merged and formed a multi-colored lump.

At this point, he had reached the second step of immortal ascension — taking in the qi.

"Damn it, the scoundrel has starting taking in the qi. Why are the reinforcements not here yet?" The river-like Giant Sun's will was burning with anxiety.

He did not dare to act rashly.

Once he was stained by heaven qi, he would melt into air. If he was corroded by earth qi, he would turn into rocks and die.

Fang Yuan, who was the intersection point of the three qi faced dangers after dangers even more so.

He had to balance the three qi at all times, if there were too much heaven and earth qi, he would die. Even human qi, if the balance was off, would cause him to self-detonate.

However, fortune is found within danger, the greater the risks, the greater the opportunities.

The balance of the three qi, the fusion between them was bringing Fang Yuan an unceasing amount of inspiration.

Heaven and earth were the foundation stones that nurtured all life, the fusion of heaven and earth qi filled Fang Yuan's mind with the grand mysteries of the Great Dao.

The three qi were fusing intensely, as Fang Yuan was inside, returning to his usual appearance after recalling the six arm heavenly zombie king killer move.

His injuries were rapidly healing, the healing speed was faster than his healing during six arm heavenly zombie king mode!

The three qi cleansed his body, not just his flesh, but his soul, mind, and will, they were being elevated.

He felt like a baby, being cleansed and returned to a pure state. Fang Yuan's eyes became clearer, the contrast between the black and white parts became more evident. His muscles were reconstructed one by one, the scars on his body fell off, and new skin grew on him. Even his hair started growing wildly, it grew longer and longer, when they were waist long, they broke, before growing again, and breaking, repeating the cycle...

Be it his body, his bones, his organs or his face, they were undergoing a magical transformation.

At the same time, the experiences in his previous five hundred years, as well as the events since rebirth flashed in his mind rapidly.

In just a short amount of time, Fang Yuan revisited his entire life.

A complex feeling that was indescribable, his memories that were deep within his mind all resurfaced, filling Fang Yuan's heart.

In his memories, all those cultivation questions that could not be answered obtained perfect answers like the work of a deity.

At this moment, heaven and earth were impartial, they were generous and imparted the mysterious of the Great Dao towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had to deal with his emotions while cherishing this opportunity to learn more about the mysteries of the Great Dao, and in the meantime balancing the three qi. Should he lose balance, he would die.

Countless Gu Masters failed at this step during their ascension!

Chapter 628: Formidable Hei Lou Lan

In true inheritance secluded domain, Fang Yuan was surrounded by the thick lump of the three colored qi, his body completely hidden.

"Junior brother, you have to control yourself. I am not concerned with you having to deal with the emotional turbulence, but I'm afraid that you are young and brave, and might be greedy towards the mysteries of the Great Dao, forgetting your limits and taking in too much heaven and earth qi." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze was filled with worry.

Heaven and earth qi had already spread to his surroundings, he had to flew away from Fang Yuan slowly.

Giant Sun's will who was fighting with him over the control of the supreme true inheritance slowed his steps.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's pressure reduced, and his situation turned for the better.

"This accursed scoundrel, he actually has so much human qi. Damn it, why hasn't he lost balance yet?" The river-like Giant Sun's will gritted his teeth and cursed.

He was not the only one hoping for such a result, Hei Lou Lan and the others were having the same thoughts.

"This guy is so young, yet he can balance the three qi for so long!"

"He and Tai Bai Yun Sheng address each other as disciple brothers, they must have some extraordinary origin. Don't tell me he is really going to become a Gu Immortal?"

"No way! Is becoming a Gu Immortal so easy! Do you think Ancestor Giant Sun is useless?"

Everyone conversed in secret, not daring to make a move. With such intense heaven and earth qi, once they suffer a backlash, it would be no joke.

Fang Yuan was inside the lump of qi, but his calm face showed a faint smile.

"Incredible, simply incredible..." his eyes were shut tight as he mumbled. All sorts of Great Dao mysteries were flowing into his mind like a warm spring.

In his previous life, Fang Yuan underwent immortal ascension and became a blood path Gu Immortal, this was his second ascension.

With this valuable experience, he was much calmer than any other Gu Master in the world. Compared to usual Gu Masters, he also knew the truth behind this event.

Man is the spirit of all being, they have the greatest spirituality. Gu are the essence of heaven and earth, they are the carriers of the Great Dao.

Any path to longevity was a path of transcendency.

To transcend, one needed accumulation.

And the most basic method of accumulating one's foundation was to learn.

Gu Masters use Gu, nurture Gu, and refine Gu. From Gu, they learn about the mysteries of heaven and earth indirectly.

But when a Gu Master undergoes ascension, they were directly conversing and interacting with heaven and earth.

This interaction was extremely precious, most likely, each person only had one of such an opportunity in their life.

Fang Yuan treasured this opportunity greatly, he grabbed onto it and tried his best to make use of it.

The mysteries of heaven and earth were even deeper and more profound than the depths of the sea. Fang Yuan knew his limits, he did not venture into it aimlessly, but instead, steered towards strength path, deepening his understanding and feeling the true essence of this path.

He had after all, only cultivated strength path on the side in his previous life, even though he cultivated strength path directly in this life, it was only for a short time.

His original attainment in strength path, strictly speaking, was only quasi strength path master.

But making use of this opportunity, his understanding of strength path surged, bursting through the sky! Very quickly, he got past the barrier to strength path master, quickly surpassing master realm and charging towards the realm of grandmaster.

Fang Yuan had no choice but to do this.

The second aperture that he shattered had the rank four all-out effort Gu as its vital Gu. This Gu was of the strength path, if it was put in first during the third step, it would help Fang Yuan become a strength path Gu Immortal.

But this Gu was not rank five, with a lower rank, Fang Yuan could only use a higher strength path attainment to compensate for the difference, otherwise, the third step of putting in Gu would be extremely risky. If the immortal aperture could not be created, this immortal ascension would end in failure.

Outside True Yang Building.

Intense winds were blowing, tribulation lightning was striking!

The heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities formed a cocoon qi lump, the qi lump was extremely huge and completely covered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building within it.

After Fang Yuan shattered his aperture, the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities underwent a new terrifying change.

In order to protect Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Giant Sun's will had no choice but to resist it, now was the crucial moment!

Bam...

Following the intense sounds of the wind, nine snow white chaotic branching teeth shot out together like lightning.

Their speed was so fast only nine shadows could be seen, resembling flashes of lightning.

Giant Sun's will was already mentally prepared, he had been waiting.

The will armor that was shielding Eighty-Eight True Yang Building increased in thickness by many times, becoming ten meters thick.

At the same time, Giant Sun's will split out dozens of will hands, opening the palms and creating a barrier in the air.

Nine chaotic branching teeth shot down at once, during their descent they collided with each other, causing their directions to change randomly, turning left and right, it was unpredictable.

The will hands flew around following them, defending desperately.

The chaotic branching teeth pierced many of the will hands, stabbing the main Giant Sun's will and causing nine deep holes to appear on the thick will armor that was a thousand times tougher than steel.

Giant Sun's will grunted, the will's main body was only chaotic for a moment before calming down.

Looking at his injuries, Giant Sun's will could not help but feel shocked.

Nine wounds of varying depth, two were six meters deep, almost piercing into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it was really a dangerous scene.

"Thankfully, I spared no effort in destroying half of the chaotic branching teeth earlier. Otherwise, if all eighteen moved at once, their trajectory would be even harder to predict, how would I be able to weaken them while in the air?"

Giant Sun's will felt some relief, but his hatred and anger towards Fang Yuan also intensified: "This accursed scoundrel Fang Yuan! I am actually shielding him during his immortal ascension! As long as I recover sufficiently, I will definitely... eh!"

Giant Sun's will stared at the eighteen spirals forming in the air in a daze.

"There is actually a second wave of chaotic branching teeth?!" Seeing this, Giant Sun's will was fuming with anger.

To defend against the chaotic branching teeth earlier, he had expended a sixth of his thoughts. But now there was a second wave!

"Wait, this is?!"

Among the eighteen spirals, another eighteen spirals started forming.

Seeing this, even Giant Sun's will felt suffocated.

"The third wave of chaotic branching teeth came together with the second?!" He howled at the sky, the armor-like main will shook intensely, almost breaking apart. If he could vomit blood, he would have vomited a river by now.

Earlier when defending against the nine chaotic branching teeth, Giant Sun's will had already used his full strength.

Right now, there were a total of thirty-six spirals, thirty-six chaotic branching teeth, this fearsome power could not be calculated by simple addition!

"This scoundrel Fang Yuan! I curse you to die!!" Giant Sun's will almost wanted to discard Eighty-Eight True Yang Building at this moment, directly going to Fang Yuan and killing him without considering the consequences.

But he was not an anger will, but a special will.

He had to think of the big picture, he had to protect this inheritance treasure which was Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

He had to contact the other subsidiary wills and gather all his strength, in order to resist these heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities.

"What? The main will wants to send me to defend against the heavenly tribulations?!" Within true inheritance secluded domain, the river-like Giant Sun's will was still waiting for reinforcement, but the reply from the main will caused his heart to turn cold, like he had fallen into an icy river.

"God damn it!" Giant Sun's will which was contesting with Tai Bai Yun Sheng over the supreme true inheritance felt great regret, but he had to divert most of his strength to the main will.

But to prevent Eighty-Eight True Yang Building from being taken by Tai Bai Yun Sheng, a portion of Giant Sun's will was still needed to maintain the situation inside the true inheritance light lump.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt his pressure decreasing all of a sudden, and heaved a sigh of relief.

"Giant Sun's will has finally stopped expanding! Junior brother, your plan has worked perfectly. It seems that the fusion of three heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities creates terrifying might that would force even Giant Sun's will to defend against it with all his strength. Junior brother, you are worthy of being benefactor's disciple, you need to survive this. The third step of putting in Gu is the most important of all, success or failure will all depend on this!"

As time continued to pass, the three colored qi lump surrounding Fang Yuan started shrinking, until it completely went into the area of Fang Yuan's broken aperture.

"He actually completed the step of taking in the qi, he is at the final step!" Hei Lou Lan and the others were watching by the side, seeing Giant Sun's will retreating, they panicked.

"What do we do now? Do we just watch him become a Gu Immortal?!" Ye Lui Sang screamed.

"Fang Yuan has no more heaven and earth qi around him, we should go and kill him now." Bian Si Xuan suggested, but she made no movement.

Everyone looked at each other, they were shocked, suspicious, and in a difficult spot.

Fang Yuan still had the Gu Immortal Tai Bai Yun Sheng supporting him.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's pressure was lifted, he held the true inheritance light lump as he faced Hei Lou Lan and the rest of the gang, showing an unyielding attitude.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng is not a problem, but once the immortal ascension succeeds, our problems would be endless. He is not a weak healing Gu Immortal like Tai Bai Yun Sheng..." Hei Lou Lan clenched his fists, a fierce light shining in his eyes.

After thinking about it, he made up his mind and shouted: "Attack!"

Saying so, the strength path phantom giant took huge strides forward, attacking.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was crying in his heart, he did not dare to take on Hei Lou Lan's attacks directly, he shouted: "You dare! As long as you come, I will throw this supreme true inheritance at the luck path true inheritance, let's see how you account to Giant Sun's will then!"

Everyone's fighting intent evaporated after hearing Tai Bai Yun Sheng's threat, their morale sinking.

Don't listen to him, we'll leave a few people to protect the luck path true inheritance, the rest will come with me!" Hei Lou Lan snorted, immediately saying.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart sank, it was difficult for him to handle the situation.

"Hahaha..." At this moment, Fang Yuan laughed wildly from behind him.

He had already opened his eyes: "Never mind! Come and chase me. Let's see how many of you are flying masters!"

Eagle rise Gu had already been destroyed, but why would the vigilant him not have spares?

Fang Yuan owned Hu Immortal blessed land and could connect to treasure yellow heaven, he did not lack any mortal Gu.

This sentence was even more demoralising to the gang compared to Tai Bai Yun Sheng. Once they thought of Fang Yuan's flying master attainment, and the huge space that was available in true inheritance secluded domain, all of their morale almost hit rock bottom.

Hei Lou Lan's gaze shone for a bit, but he was unmoved.

He was the Lord of the Imperial Court for this round, he had exemplary talent and a ruthless nature, he would not become dejected with just a few words.

"We will chase him even if we cannot catch him, I want to see how he can undergo immortal ascension under such pressure!" Hei Lou Lan's words lifted the morale once again.

Fang Yuan's expression turned grim, he did not speak anymore.

Hei Lou Lan hit the main point.

During an ordinary immortal ascension, the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity would be all around him, if his enemies wanted to obstruct him, they would face the might of the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity.

But now that Giant Sun's will was blocking the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities outside, it gave Hei Lou Lan and the others an opportunity to intervene.

Although in this true inheritance secluded domain, there was still heaven and earth qi left that could cause backlash in mortal Gu.

But Hei Lou Lan and the others were just like Fang Yuan, they were all using mortal Gu, thus they all faced the same backlash.

At once, the situation changed again.

Although Giant Sun's will left to resist the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities wholeheartedly, Fang Yuan's predicament did not become any easier.

Hei Lou Lan was indeed a formidable character, he was an outstanding person and knew the perfect timing to strike.

Fang Yuan's immortal ascension was stuck between the second and third step, the situation had turned dangerous yet again.

Chapter 629: Formless Hand

"Fang Yuan, why are you running?"

"You cowardly scum, are you afraid? Do you have the guts to fight me for three hundred rounds?!"

"You are unworthy of disguising as Chang Shan Yin. You don't even have one percent of his bravery."

Inside true inheritance secluded domain. Fang Yuan was flying away rapidly while the others chased from behind, taunting him endlessly.

These insults and provocations fell on deaf ears, Fang Yuan's expression was tranquil without any emotions.

He was closely observing his surroundings, true inheritance secluded domain was vast but it was not a flat area and many true inheritance meteors flew around in disorder, even colliding occasionally.

Giant Sun's will had taken control of many true inheritances just before, but there were still many masterless true inheritances left in true inheritance secluded domain.

If Fang Yuan was unfortunately obstructed by these true inheritances, the group of Gu Masters behind him would be able to near him. Once he was encircled, the situation would turn much more dangerous.

Right at this moment, a dark red true inheritance meteor flew towards Fang Yuan.

Wind flower Gu.

Fang Yuan, however, had a slight smile on his face as he inwardly willed.

A gust of wind condensed into a giant flower which suddenly appeared beside him. The wind flower nimbly changed its direction, carrying him with it.

Swoosh—!

A sharp ear-piercing wind breezed past; Fang Yuan brushed past this unparalleled true inheritance light lump.

The unparalleled true inheritance shot forward directly towards the group of Gu Masters behind; the group was caught unprepared and panicked for a moment, dodging and fleeing.

Taking advantage of this time, Fang Yuan increased his speed and rapidly pulled apart the distance between him and the group.

Hei Lou Lan's group naturally was not willing to see this situation. Each of them was an elite; they immediately reacted and sent out countless long range attacks.

Fang Yuan sneered, using the primeval essence in his first aperture.

Flash bug Gu.

This was a rare space path movement Gu and under its effect, Fang Yuan immediately disappeared from the spot.

When he appeared, he was already five hundred steps ahead.

The attacks from Hei Lou Lan and the others thus landed on nothing.

Fang Yuan stopped flash bug Gu and changed to eagle rise Gu.

Flash bug Gu was a rank five Gu but its speed was not great, and it also expended a lot of purple crystal primeval essence to move forward by five hundred steps per use. Its main usage was to make sudden movements to avoid attacks.

To truly speed up and fly for a long distance, eagle rise Gu was still a lot better.

Eagle rise Gu might only be rank four Gu, but there were six wings on Fang Yuan's back; he had simultaneously used three eagle rise Gu!

Eagle rise Gu's speed was very impressive and rapidly transported him away, while also consuming less primeval essence.

The group of Gu Masters chasing Fang Yuan could only gnash their teeth as he rapidly flew away.

"Damn it! This guy is truly slippery, only focusing on running away, he has not even a bit of bravery."

"Didn't he shatter his aperture to ascend to Gu Immortal? How come he still has so much primeval essence left?"

"Hmph, there are many methods for Gu Masters to preserve primeval essence. So what if the aperture is shattered? One just needs to have Gu that can store primeval essence like fish bubble Gu, beggar moth or grave yam Gu."

"My movement Gu can't endure it, the backlash from heaven and earth qi is really terrifying."

Hei Lou Lan sneered: "We are suffering backlash, he is also in the same situation. We will continue chasing without stop. The enemy is a flying master, it is normal for us to not be able to reach him. But as long as we chase closely and not give him time to advance to a Gu Immortal, we will have fulfilled our objective!"

Fang Yuan glanced back and seeing that the pursuers had no intention of giving up, the anxiety in his heart deepened.

Without doubt, he had to admit that Hei Lou Lan was striking at his weak point.

Bursts of pain spread from his second aperture.

The second aperture was already shattered, forming a hole which was occupied by a lump of three colored qi at this moment, waiting for the vital Gu to be put into it and reach the final step, accumulating its foundation till the immortal aperture is born.

If the immortal aperture was not created, Fang Yuan would perish from the backlash of heaven and earth qi.

If the immortal aperture was created, no matter which grade it was, Fang Yuan would have to concentrate on it fully at that moment, causing him to enter a period of weakness where he would be defenseless.

This time could be long or short, depending on the person.

If the enemies took advantage of this time, Fang Yuan's situation would be bleak and was very likely to die in a tragic end!

At present, Hei Lou Lan's group was firmly blocking Fang Yuan at this step.

Fang Yuan did not dare to place in his Gu and could only look on as the extremely compressed three colored lump of qi started to vibrate.

"I can't continue like this! If it is put off any longer, the three colored lump of qi will disperse and all my accumulations used in advancing to Gu Immortal will vanish into thin air." Fang Yuan kept on thinking of one solution after another to get out of this predicament.

Rumble...

Right at this time, true inheritance secluded domain started shaking.

Rumble...

Another tremor soon spread, causing everyone to panic.

"What is going on?"

"What happened, is true inheritance secluded domain collapsing?"

Hei Lou Lan, Ye Lui Sang and others had a worried expression, realizing fully well in their mind: this was the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities outside starting to affect Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were instead overjoyed, this signified Giant Sun's will had already staked all its strength but the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities was so terrifying that even it had reached its limit.

"Damn it, damn it... I barely endured it!" Giant Sun's will gasped for breath with fear and joy, it did not even have the energy to curse Fang Yuan.

The ten meter thick golden armor created by Giant Sun's will that had covered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building tightly was now left with nothing but a thin layer with its luster dimmed.

Thirty-six chaotic branching teeth attacking together was not a simple matter of addition, their overall might was amplified by close to ten times!

During this whole process snow war tribulation lightning attacked crazily like the attacks were free. The lightning which flashed in intervals before had almost become unending like sunlight; one could see the terrifying frequency of snow war tribulation lightning.

Giant Sun's will avoided death narrowly, but there was not even one percent of the original will remaining.

He used all his strength and put in all of his effort to destroy eleven spirals in advance. The remaining chaotic branching teeth erupted together, Giant Sun's will used all his ability and blocked most of them, but he could not block seven of them.

Seven scars appeared on Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Four scars even directly penetrated through True Yang Building, opening up four passages.

The tremor Fang Yuan and the rest felt in true inheritance secluded domain originated from this.

"My Eighty-Eight True Yang Building..." Giant Sun's will's heart bled at the sight and almost howled out in grief.

The losses were too severe, not only were the numbers of Gu worms destroyed extremely huge, two immortal Gu were also destroyed.

Who knew how long it would take to replenish these Gu worms and restore Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to its complete form.

"Fang Yuan, you insufferable bastard. You are undergoing the tribulation, yet I was the one who bore the consequences! I will make sure you regret being born into this world!"

Giant Sun's will cursed fiercely in his heart.

The giant cocoon formed from the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities had already thinned.

Several rays of light pierced through the layers of dark clouds and shone down on the damaged Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities were slowly dissipating.

Giant Sun's will felt a huge stone lifting off his heart and was joyous to the point of crying: "The heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities have finally ended!"

"I managed to endure it! Although Eighty-Eight True Yang Building suffered heavy damage, the fundamental Gu worms haven't been lost, and the mortal Gu might have been destroyed in large numbers, but they can be replenished. The destroyed immortal Gu are rather troublesome to obtain, but they also can be refined again. Even if others refine them first, I can use other Gu worms to replace them. The situation is set, now I shall get rid of the otherworldly demon then teach that scum Fang Yuan his place!"

The heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities were dissipating in front of his eyes, Giant Sun's will saw the time to take revenge was here and his mood took a turn for the better.

However, right at this time, a light blue giant hand gradually appeared in front of Giant Sun's will.

"Thi...This is...?!"

The remaining Giant Sun's will trembled intensely, even more frightened than seeing seventy or even eighty chaotic branching teeth at once.

"This is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's killer move — Formless Hand. This accursed Fang Yuan, how is his luck so bad that he attracted this disaster!"

Rank nine Gu Immortals were invincible under the heavens and could leave behind unique traces in the whole world.

Even after death, some of their killer moves could emerge again during heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities.

"I got it! This Fang Yuan is too audacious, he was set on killing the child of luck Ma Hong Yun and suffered the backlash from fortune rivalling heaven Gu, causing his luck to be completely messed up, thus attracting such terrifying a heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity!"

Giant Sun's will felt extremely agonized when he realized the cause.

Going to the bottom of this, it was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable who left behind fortune rivaling heaven Gu. Under an absurd combination of different factors, Giant Sun's will was actually suffering a loss from his own arrangement!

"Back then, the whole world was helpless when Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable used formless hand to rob countless Gu worms. Fortunately, this formless hand only has five fingers, thus at most, it can only seize rank five Gu, Gu, Gu... oh heavens!"

Giant Sun's will's pitch suddenly rose an octave higher, crying out in shock.

The heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity slowly dissipated, large numbers of formless hands appeared one after another.

Two, three... twenty, thirty... two hundred, three hundred...

Innumerable formless hands appeared, covering the whole sky!

Among them, one finger to five fingered formless hands occupied the majority.

There were sixteen six fingered formless hands and nine seven fingered formless hands.

There were even three eight fingered formless hands!

"Impossible! Even if Fang Yuan was targeted by fortune rivaling heaven Gu and his luck became terrible, it could not have gotten to this extent!" Giant Sun's will shouted in an incredulous tone.

"It's over, everything is finished!" Giant Sun's will howled, if he could cry, his face would be filled with tears right now.

Instantly, the large number of Giant Sun's will dispersed and fell down from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building like sand.

This was the self-collapse of a will!

There was not even a trace of fighting spirit left, it could not endure such an impact.

The heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities had not ended, but were transforming into this final tribulation.

Formless hands!

The remaining Giant Sun's will curled up into a lump, exposing Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Inside true inheritance secluded domain, Fang Yuan and the others were still in the dark, not knowing anything that occurred outside.

The chase was still continuing.

Due to the backlash of heaven and earth qi, the loss of Gu worms on both sides had reached the hundreds. But they were still persisting firmly.

Fang Yuan had almost no movement Gu left, but he had already found a way to resolve this predicament!

He led the pursuers to make a large detour before suddenly changing direction and flying towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Senior brother, quickly open your immortal aperture and let me in. I can evade these pursuers and smoothly advance to a Gu Immortal there!" Fang Yuan secretly transmitted his voice.

"This..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not help but hesitate.

The immortal aperture was the foundation of a Gu Immortal. If Fang Yuan was let in and he failed, the resulting destruction would have to be endured by Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Senior brother, what are you hesitating for at such a crucial moment? Once I advance to a Gu Immortal, we will have the strength to survive this danger. Don't worry, I have complete assurance in advancing successfully!" Fang Yuan shouted.

Chapter 630: Chaotic and Dangerous Situation

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was already bound firmly on Fang Yuan's chariot, and thinking of Fixed Immortal Travel that was with Fang Yuan, he had no choice but to accept Fang Yuan's request.

Fang Yuan was overjoyed and charged into Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture.

"Damn it!" The pursuers paled at this sight.

"This scum is too crafty, actually hiding in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture. We can't hunt him now!" Ye Lui Sang helplessly shouted.

"Then, we shall slaughter an immortal! Kill Tai Bai Yun Sheng!!" Hei Lou Lan's eyes glinted ominously, killing intent pervading from his body.

The giant strength path phantom he had turned into charged towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng with overwhelming momentum, like a bear pouncing at its prey!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was scared witless, quickly fleeing with the supreme true inheritance light lump.

"Don't forget that I am also a flying master!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng had learned from Fang Yuan and shouted loudly while flying away.

The pursuers' momentum was involuntarily destroyed.

Someone powerlessly cursed: "F*ck, two flying masters appeared in this Imperial Court contest and both of them had to be these two!"

Only Hei Lou Lan was provoked by the remark, his battle intent soared to an unprecedented level.

'Looks like I have to use my full strength as well!' His expression was solemn as he made a resolution and punched fiercely.

The fist qi surged majestically like a mountain peak!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng nimbly dodged it without receiving any injury.

But the barrage of grand fist qi suddenly transformed into giant strength path phantoms.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was caught unprepared and in a short moment was completely surrounded by these giant strength path phantoms.

"What bad luck." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's face turned pale white.

"Who could have thought Hei Lou Lan's strength had actually reached such a powerful level! Sixteen giant strength path phantoms, this strength can truly slaughter an immortal!" Ye Lui Sang and the others were greatly shocked at this scene.

"Huff huff huff..." Hei Lou Lan gasped for breath, the giant strength path phantom on him had already dissipated. This move clearly used a lot of his energy and strength.

Even the Great Strength True Martial Physique of the ten extreme physiques could not endure its usage.

His fat body flickered with a layer of faint black light; that was the power of Immortal Gu Dark Limit, helping him to suppress and conceal the Great Strength True Martial Physique.

"What a close call, I almost broke the seal of dark limit Gu!" Hei Lou Lan rejoiced inwardly, a vicious gaze flashing on his eyes as he looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng, "Your death is assured now! My grand plan of revenge will start from you, Tai Bai Yun Sheng!"

However, a change occurred right at this moment!

Giant light blue hands suddenly appeared in true inheritance secluded domain.

The dense giant light blue hands soon attracted everyone's gazes.

"What is that!"

"What kind of thing?"

Whoosh.

An ordinary true inheritance that was flying like a meteor collided into a giant light blue hand.

The giant light blue hand opened its palm and grabbed this true inheritance, holding it so tightly the true inheritance could not even budge.

The giant light blue hand paused for a breath of time before flying away swiftly.

Under everyone's gazes, it left behind a trail of gorgeous blue light while its speed kept on increasing.

After it moved thousands of steps away, it suddenly disappeared without a trace, even the true inheritance it was holding was gone.

Everyone's pupils involuntarily shrunk at this sight.

"These giant hands are so terrifying, they easily subdue the true inheritance!"

"I know, this is definitely Ancestor Giant Sun's ability. Haven't you noticed these giant light blue hands are similar to the flying snow hands?"

"Haha, Ancestor Giant Sun has made his move. It seems the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity has already passed, these two scoundrels are finished now!!"

Some people made guesses which were quickly approved by everyone. However, right when they were cheering, a miserable shriek spread to their ears.

Everyone looked at the source of the voice and saw that a Gu Master in the outer periphery was grabbed by the giant light blue hand.

Shortly after, the giant hand seemed to have grabbed something, flying far away with a clenched fist.

That Gu Master let out a miserable howl: "My... that hand seized all my Gu worms!!"

"What!?"

There was a commotion.

Soon, the second victim appeared.

"My vital Gu was actually seized... puff!" He spurted a mouthful of blood. Vital Gu was closely related to the Gu Master's life and when it was forcibly seized by the giant hand, the Gu Master immediately suffered backlash.

The hands fell down like rain, beginning to wantonly seize Gu worms.

"Run away..." Everyone dispersed in confusion.

"Isn't this Ancestor Giant Sun's ability!? Could it be that this is a heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity?" Many cried out in shock.

"What kind of heavenly tribulation is this, it can actually seize Gu worms!!" Someone shouted in bewilderment. The importance of Gu worms to Gu Masters was self-evident.

"Quick, store your Gu worms into your apertures!" Someone reminded in panic.

However, everyone soon discovered even after storing in the aperture, the Gu worms were still being seized.

The giant light blue hands were formless. They did not inflict the slightest injuries and only captured Gu worms. Once the Gu worm was captured by them, the Gu worm would immediately lose connection with the Gu Master.

"What kind of tribulation are these giant light blue hands? Can it seize even Immortal Gu?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not make out any details on these giant light blue hands and was very nervous from the scene unfolding in front of him.

At this time, three giant hands moved towards him. He evaded in panic.

Even as a flying Gu Master, he was soon in danger, his face perspiring heavily.

The giant hands were very fast and extremely nimble; the crucial point was they could sneak attack like flash bug Gu, making it very hard to defend against them.

Even Tai Bai Yun Sheng was cutting out a sorry figure, there was no need to mention other Gu Masters.

"There seems to be information of this in the tribe records..." Hei Lou Lan frowned. He could not dodge in time and was grabbed by a four fingered giant hand.

For a moment, he could not budge.

The giant light blue hand seemingly had no substance and like wind brushing past one's face, it caused no harm to Hei Lou Lan's body.

However, Hei Lou Lan felt his head go dizzy, instantly losing connection with a rank four Gu.

"Oh no." Hei Lou Lan inwardly exclaimed, the Gu that was seized might only be rank four but it was very important. It was one of the necessary Gu worms to use his strength path killer move.

Roar!

Hei Lou Lan suddenly let out a beastly roar.

Rank five — fixed sound Gu!

A formless soundwave rapidly chased after the four fingered giant hand and locked it in place like a formless iron chain.

"I don't care what all these hands are, I'll destroy them!" Hei Lou Lan gave a loud shout to raise his spirits, and turned into giant strength path phantom once more.

The giant grabbed the giant light blue hand with its house sized fist, and clenched!

The giant light blue hand flickered twice before shattering apart like glass. Hei Lou Lan immediately sensed that crucial Gu worm.

The shattered giant light blue hand fell apart like ice melting into water.

Hei Lou Lan smoothly grabbed the Gu worm and was just feeling joyous when five formless hands suddenly appeared behind him.

His face turned pale instantly. He fiercely turned his body and delivered a horizontal strike with his arm!

He used all his strength in this strike!

Wind erupted, and soundwaves burst out like thunder.

But when the strike touched the formless hands, the giant arm directly passed through like they were image of the moon in the water.

Hei Lou Lan was stupefied, the formless hands quickly moved and grabbed specific parts of the giant strength path phantom.

Hei Lou Lan was paralyzed once more.

Next moment, the giant strength path phantom collapsed with a loud sound.

His killer move was broken!

"My Gu worms... puff!" Hei Lou Lan spurted out large amounts of blood.

His vital Gu was seized which was the core Gu of his strength path killer move! Besides it, four other crucial Gu worms were also seized.

What gave Hei Lou Lan the most heartache was false emotion fake will Gu and wooden chicken Gu, two Immortal Gu, were also seized!

"Stop right now!" Hei Lou Lan exerted all his strength to chase the hands, the matter of Fang Yuan thrown out of his mind.

The giant light blue hands moved everywhere, seizing Gu worms.

The Gu Masters fled and evaded in disorder.

A rumble erupted in true inheritance secluded domain, threads of light shone down as the True Yang Building began to crumble.

"No, I absolutely can't let Eighty-Eight True Yang Building perish! Formless hands cannot be attacked, but when they grab a Gu worm and clench their fist, they can be destroyed. As long as I can protect the several rank eight core Gu worms, with enough time, I will be able to rebuild True Yang Building!"

Outside the tower, the remnant Giant Sun's will curled up in a ball and was accumulating its energy.

The enormous True Yang Building was like an old man with a foot in the grave, letting the formless hands fly in, grab the Gu worms and fly away.

The beautiful and grand True Yang Building soon turned into a nibbled giant corn; its surface was a mess, filled with holes.

The formless hands continued to rain down endlessly.

True Yang Building's complete destruction was not far away.

Inside Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture blessed land, however, was a scene of tranquility.

Fang Yuan waited for a while before carefully transferring his second vital Gu.

All-out effort Gu had a beetle-like shape with an oval body and an arching carapace. The majestic horn on its head appeared dignified and powerful. It had three pairs of strong legs, and its entire body was brown which shone with a metallic luster.

Fang Yuan obtained this Gu back in southern border, later he refined it rank four which allowed him to casually strike out with beast strength phantoms.

"Go." Fang Yuan softly spoke.

All-out effort Gu obeyed Fang Yuan's intent, charging towards the extremely compressed three colored qi lump.

BOOM!!!

Fang Yuan's body shook intensely as lightning seemed to have burst in his mind.

The qi lump exploded loudly and like the process of creation after destruction, it gave birth to an immortal aperture!

The sky in the immortal aperture was orange yellow and a white mountain stood tall on the earth.

Since the immortal aperture was newly born, the space inside was limited, but it soon rapidly expanded all around.

Like a newborn baby, it demanded nutrition intensely.

The immortal aperture's nourishment was the heaven and earth Qi.

"Senior brother, let me out quick." Fang Yuan immediately sent his voice.

"You succeeded!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was overjoyed before warning, "You need to be careful when you come out, the situation now is quite dangerous!"

Fang Yuan's vision changed as he was let out of the immortal aperture by Tai Bai Yun Sheng; the next moment, he appeared beside Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"This, this is formless hand?!" Five hundred years of experience was not for show, Fang Yuan immediately recognized the origin of the giant light blue hands and turned pale with fright.

Feeling his aura, a six fingered formless hand suddenly appeared above Fang Yuan and grabbed!

Chapter 631: Striking a fortune

The six fingered formless hand's appearance was so sudden that Fang Yuan only had the time to raise his head.

The light blue radiance shone down on his face as his sight was filled with the giant light blue hand.

The formless hand did not show any notions of stopping, grabbing towards Fang Yuan, completely shrouding over his body.

"Junior brother!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted in fright.

The next moment, however, this six fingered formless fist loosened up and spread open.

Fang Yuan's figure showed up five hundred steps away. The six fingered formless hand had grabbed at nothing.

Flash bug Gu!

This Gu was a rare rank five space path movement Gu. Fang Yuan had to spend a lot of efforts to purchase it in treasure yellow heaven.

"Hufff..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng let out a breath of turbid air, a giant stone lifted off his heart.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng knew Fang Yuan was unable to react properly because he had just came out. In truth, it was nothing difficult for flying masters to evade these formless hands.

"Close call!" Fang Yuan's body let out cold sweat from the fright.

He had much more understanding of formless hands than others; as such, he knew their threat level clearly!

"Formless hand is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's killer move; it can range from one finger to nine fingers, respectively able to seize rank one to rank nine Gu worms! They can even seize the vital Gu without any problems. If that six fingered formless hand succeeded in grabbing me, I would have definitely lost either Spring Autumn Cicada or Fixed Immortal Travel... my luck is too bad, it actually provoked such a catastrophe!"

Fang Yuan rapidly flew, dodging the pursuit of the formless hand while observing his surroundings.

True inheritance secluded domain had already fallen into complete chaos.

True inheritance meteors and formless hands filled one's sight; Gu Masters flew around in disorder - some were evading the formless hands, some cried out in grief after their Gu worms were seized, while some used all their strength to attack the formless hands.

"It seems that they have found out already! Once a formless hand captures a Gu worm, it will clench its fist; this is the moment it can be attacked! When it is in its spread out palm form, it is almost completely immune to all attacks and can only be dodged."

Fang Yuan recalled the relevant information on formless hands.

He was very familiar with the formless hands. In his previous life, Ma Hong Yun had successively obtained a portion of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance, also obtaining a similar method of capturing Gu worms. He had used this method many times in the great battle of the five regions, resulting in the disastrous loss of many strong enemies and making them flee.

Fang Yuan had thus researched a lot on this.

Fang Yuan continued to dodge, use flash bug Gu, wind flower Gu, eagle rise Gu and so on before he was able to pull apart a huge distance, making the six fingered formless hand chasing him to change its target.

He immediately sent a portion of his consciousness to inspect his immortal aperture.

There were remnants of heaven and earth qi in true inheritance secluded domain.

Ever since Fang Yuan came out, his immortal aperture had been crazily absorbing these heaven and earth qi, growing rapidly.

In just a short while, his immortal aperture had expanded to over 2000km2 and was still growing.

At the same time, the time flow inside the immortal aperture was starting to become faster than the outside world. From a one to one ratio, it increased to six times as fast.

"Damn it." Fang Yuan suddenly frowned and his face paled.

The change in the immortal aperture was going smoothly, but the problem appeared in the first aperture; more accurately, the problem was the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Spring Autumn Cicada was recovering rapidly and the first aperture was already showing signs of being unable to bear the huge pressure from it!

"Oh no! When an immortal aperture is born, not only does the space enlarge, the time flow also changes. The change in the time flow is the main reason an immortal aperture can turn into a small world and attract a tributary of the river of time! Spring Autumn Cicada feeds on the water of the river of time, and now being so close to the source, it is able to drink a lot and accelerate its recovery speed!"

Fang Yuan was able to instantly understand what was going on.

Since the last activation of Spring Autumn Cicada which had fortunately succeeded, it had been slowly recovering.

It has been a long time since Fang Yuan arrived in northern plains; Spring Autumn Cicada was gradually recovering causing the pressure on the first aperture to increase day by day.

The first aperture was already at rank five peak stage and should have been able to endure for some time according to Fang Yuan's estimation. But this unforeseen event had greatly shifted the time limit to an earlier date!

Since rebirth, Spring Autumn Cicada had been a hidden danger to Fang Yuan. Now that Fang Yuan was advancing to a Gu Immortal, this hidden danger had expanded to a serious danger that directly pushed itself to Fang Yuan's sight.

"Damn it." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth. He suddenly descended; a formless hand passed by his hair, grabbing at the air.

For now, Fang Yuan had no way to deal with this situation.

The immortal aperture must be successfully created, otherwise all his efforts would go to waste. Without a Gu Immortal's strength, it would be impossible for him to continue contending.

However, Spring Autumn Cicada also could not be ignored.

Crack...

A huge sound echoed in true inheritance secluded domain like some important thing had shattered, causing palpitation in everyone's heart.

Everyone paused and hurriedly looked up.

Like an egg shell that was smashed, countless cracks appeared on true inheritance secluded domain. The cracks rapidly enlarged and let the outside world's light flow in.

At the same time, many formless hands also squeezed in through the cracks, a seven fingered formless hand among them!

The Gu Masters let out shocked cries at the sight of so many giant light blue hands.

"Why are there so many giant hands?"

"This is bad, look, a seven fingered giant hand has actually squeezed in!"

With the endless giant light blue hands flying in true inheritance secluded domain, everyone's situation had become even more perilous.

Hei Lou Lan's expression was grave and even Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt an intense suffocation.

Flying masters were not omnipotent.

With so many formless hands, the difficult in evading them increased greatly.

Moreover, the longer they spent, the more likely it was for them to make an error under such a strained state.

"This is turning worse!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was gloomy, what he was afraid of came, he made a mistake in the crucial time.

His sole remaining escape path was blocked by six formless hands.

At this moment of crisis, Tai Bai Yun Sheng gritted his teeth and directly crashed towards a three fingered formless hand.

The formless hand grabbed him; Tai Bai Yun Sheng was immediately paralyzed.

But this time period was extremely short and soon, the three fingered formless hand flew away with a clenched fist. Out of danger, Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately burst out with his greatest speed and escaped through this gap.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's back was soaked with cold sweat from this thrilling situation.

Even Tai Bai Yun Sheng was in such a predicament, let alone others.

All the Gu Masters met with calamity, at worst, not even one of their Gu worms remained.

Without Gu worms, Gu Master's battle strength plunged down to the very bottom. And even if they had a lot of primeval essence, it would be of no use.

"Save me!" A Gu Master looked on with fright a true inheritance that was flying right towards him.

All his Gu worms were already seized by the formless hands. At this moment of life and death, he cried out for help while swinging his arms crazily to speed up his flight, but his movement speed was no faster than a snail in comparison to the true inheritance.

The surrounding Gu Masters heard his plea for help, but right now they had no way to help however much they wanted to.

Thud!

There was no unexpected event; the unlucky Gu Master was directly crushed into meat paste by the true inheritance.

This blue colored true inheritance did not stop after crushing the Gu Master and kept on flying away.

On its way, formless hands kept on obstructing its path while it kept on evading.

The wild newborn Gu will in the true inheritance also sensed the deadly threat of the heavenly tribulation formless hands, and did its best to escape.

However, the will of Gu worms was not as intelligent as humans.

The blue colored true inheritance evaded several formless hands before it was finally grabbed by a five fingered formless hand.

The formless hand clenched its fist tightly but did not stop at the place.

The true inheritance light lump's speed was too fast; the formless hand was pulled in its inertia, except that the speed was greatly reduced.

The five fingered formless hand flew away with a Gu worm. But even more formless hands pounced down and covered the true inheritance light lump.

One hand was not enough, another came followed by the next. Soon, ten formless hands were tightly grabbing the true inheritance light lump.

The true inheritance light lump continued to slow until it came to a stop.

The formless hands suddenly separated and flew in all directions with clenched fists.

There was nothing left at the spot, the blue colored true inheritance was already robbed clean.

At this moment, Fang Yuan snickered and flew towards the target he had his eyes on, and started attacking fiercely.

A formless fist was broken by his attacks and revealed the Gu it was holding.

Fang Yuan immediately reacted and grabbed it.

This was a rank five mortal Gu and after he refined it, he stored it in his pocket.

Flash bug Gu!

He disappeared from the spot and suddenly appeared three hundred steps away, right beside another formless fist.

Bam bam bam.

He punched heavily and broke the formless fist in three punches, leaving after grabbing the Gu.

It was an Immortal Gu!

Almost at the very next moment, a formless hand pounced at him, and naturally it was in vain.

Fang Yuan moved like lightning, occasionally soaring like a sparrow and occasionally piercing forward like an eagle.

He was dodging the formless hands while also taking any chance to strike a fortune, grabbing many Gu worms of the true inheritance.

However, the formless fists were very fast and the opportunity to destroy them was fleeting.

The blue colored true inheritance was a good opportunity Fang Yuan ran into, but he only had enough time to break three formless fists, obtaining two mortal Gu and an Immortal Gu.

While Fang Yuan was occupied with breaking the formless fist, the other formless fists had already flown far away and Fang Yuan was not able to chase after them.

"Suppress!"

Fang Yuan transferred his will into the Gu worms to temporarily suppress them.

He did not have the time to refine these Gu worms, let alone study their uses.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's sight was covered with blue light.

Maybe it was because Fang Yuan was too active and attention drawing, eight formless hands attacked him together!

Fang Yuan's heart jumped and he quickly evaded.

He moved and stopped at times, changing his directions madly; his vision kept on changing intensely, one moment he was above while the next he was below. He almost made himself go dizzy.

He spent tremendous effort before he was able to get rid of the formless hands.

He had just stabilized his breathing when suddenly, there was the sound of wind!

A formless hand was flying right towards him.

Fang Yuan was just about to dodge, but his pupils enlarged rapidly the next moment. This was a formless fist!

He laughed heartily and flapped his six wings, directly punching towards the formless fist. He obtained a rank five Gu after breaking the formless fist.

The Gu worm was vibrating in his hand and struggled intensely, attempting to escape.

Fang Yuan sent a portion of his will inside, but was not able to suppress it.

He immediately frowned as he realized this Gu was not a wild Gu, but a Gu Master's Gu worm. Because the Gu worm had someone else's will, the difficulty in refining it was several times greater than refining wild Gu, and even temporarily suppressing it was difficult!

"Let go of my Gu!" A familiar voice sounded by Fang Yuan's ears at this moment.

Fang Yuan looked at the source of the voice, and immediately smiled.

He saw Hei Lou Lan flying towards him hurriedly and furiously, his gaze fixed on the Gu in Fang Yuan's hand.

Chapter 632: Coexistence of Pain and Joy

Hei Lou Lan's heart was filled with incessant grievances.

He had outstanding battle strength along with an extremely powerful long range strength path killer move, it was just that they were not enough to cover his weakness in the movement aspect.

More accurately speaking, Hei Lou Lan cultivated strength and dark path which were generally not impressive in movement ability.

But in the present situation, only flying masters could barely survive. Hei Lou Lan's weakness was thus completely revealed under the pursuit of the formless hands.

The formless hands wantonly seized the Gu worms in Hei Lou Lan's body.

He had destroyed many formless hands and chased after many, but at the same time, new formless hands would appear to grab even more of his Gu worms.

Right now, Hei Lou Lan was flying fiercely like a berserk bear, his expression was one of malevolence and anger.

He knew Fang Yuan had big advantage in this situation, but he could not give up. The reason was that the Gu worm Fang Yuan had captured was, very unfortunately, Hei Lou Lan's vital Gu!

The vital Gu was closely interlinked to the Gu Master's life. Once it was destroyed, the Gu Master would immediately suffer heavy injuries. By grabbing this Gu, it was akin to Fang Yuan controlling a huge weakness of Hei Lou Lan.

Speaking of this vital Gu, it had gone through many difficulties as well; being seized by the formless hands many times while Hei Lou Lan seized it back again.

Counting the number of times, this was already the sixth time this vital Gu had been seized. Only this time, an accident happened, it landed in Fang Yuan's hand.

His vital Gu was with the enemy, this was a very serious situation and it needed to be retrieved!

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with a cold light.

He did not know the rank five Gu in his hands was Hei Lou Lan's vital Gu, but he could tell the huge importance of this Gu from Hei Lou Lan's behavior.

"Hmph! You want to take back this Gu? Keep on dreaming." Fang Yuan moved the six wings on his back and rose up, flying far away.

Hei Lou Lan had hunted down Fang Yuan again and again before; the hatred between them was already very deep.

But this moment was not a good time to kill Hei Lou Lan.

There were more and more formless hands, Fang Yuan was already feeling difficulty in dodging them. If he fought under this situation, he would surely have to pay an extremely disastrous price even if he succeeded.

It was more so when Hei Lou Lan had Great Strength True Martial Physique, if he was forced into a corner and self-detonated, Fang Yuan would have to suffer the terrible consequences.

"Let's see how long he can continue chasing me!" Fang Yuan snorted, and forcibly suppressed the restless Gu worm in his hand.

Soon, he shook off Hei Lou Lan. While dodging the formless hands on the way, he sent a portion of his consciousness into his immortal aperture.

The immortal aperture was growing without pause.

Ever since Fang Yuan exited Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture, his immortal aperture had been continuously absorbing heaven and earth qi. Now, it was already over 2600km2; the sky was orange and yellow while the earth was rugged with steep white stone mountain ranges that stood tall and lofty.

The terrain of the immortal aperture was related to the Gu Master's paths, accumulation, temperament and comprehension.

This was the first time Fang Yuan became a strength path Gu Immortal and he only roughly understood it now, only knowing the general situation. If he wanted to have a deeper understanding, he needed to research in the future

"The time flow has reached one to twelve ratio. One day in the outside world is twelve days inside the immortal aperture. The growth rate is gradually slowing down…" Fang Yuan assessed.

By now, he had almost absorbed all the heaven and earth qi in true inheritance secluded domain.

He was now waiting for the immortal aperture to stabilize completely which was of the most importance. Once he possessed a Gu Immortal's battle strength, everything would change.

"I will let you hold on to my Gu for the moment, I will get it back no matter what!" Hei Lou Lan could only roar helplessly as he looked at Fang Yuan fly further and further away.

He was obstructed by the formless hands when he chased and had lost many Gu worms. It was already very difficult for him to evade the formless hands, it was no wonder he would suffer the consequences when he chased after Fang Yuan under such conditions.

Hei Lou Lan helplessly gave up. If he still persisted in chasing, it would definitely make Fang Yuan suspicious. And if Fang Yuan guessed the Gu was Hei Lou Lan's vital Gu, the situation would turn even worse.

"I can only rely on my connection to my vital Gu and slowly get near him while dodging the formless hands, then I will ambush this damned thief!"

Hei Lou Lan gritted his teeth till they made cracking noises, while thinking of all kinds of schemes.

Formless hands could seize Gu worms but could not refine them. Once the formless hand was broken apart, the Gu worm would be released upon which the Gu Master would be able to immediately sense the Gu and use his will to recall them.

Fang Yuan forcibly suppressed Hei Lou Lan's vital Gu, but had no time or energy to spare to refine it. Thus, Hei Lou Lan still was connected with the Gu worm, and had hope of turning the situation around.

Time passed, the formless hands had completely gained control of the situation in true inheritance secluded domain. Giant light blue hands could be seen everywhere like swarms of bees hovering around.

Be it Gu Masters or true inheritance light lumps, they only had the choice of escaping.

"Spring Autumn Cicada…" Fang Yuan's mouth was dry as the pressure in him continued to increase.

Following the growth of the immortal aperture, Spring Autumn Cicada continued to absorb the water of the river of time, causing the pressure in the first aperture to continue to increase. There were already many cracks on the first aperture's walls.

To decrease the pressure on the first aperture as much as possible, Fang Yuan had already emptied out all the primeval essence in the aperture.

He flew rapidly, using tens of movement Gu which had huge demand towards primeval essence.

"Fortunately I had already planned and prepared long before this, and bought large numbers of beggar moths. But even so, I need to pay attention to my primeval essence. The consequences will be unimaginable if my primeval essence is completely exhausted!"

These beggar moths were Gu worms used to store primeval essence.

They looked like moths, but their wings had round holes. These holes made the beggar moth look tattered, resembling a beggar's clothings.

In truth, however, the more holes there were on the beggar moth's wings, the better. More holes meant the beggar moths could store higher rank primeval essence.

In the mortal world, these beggar moths were limited in supply. But Fang Yuan possessed Hu Immortal blessed land and was able to buy groups of beggar moths in treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan directly purchased a group; although there were not many rank five and rank four beggar moths, rank three and rank two were huge in numbers.

Fang Yuan had close to a thousand beggar moths and had brought almost all of them with him.

Mortals could not buy them and would also find it hard to bear the expenses of raising Gu. But Fang Yuan had a Gu Immortal's assets in Hu Immortal blessed land, and it was easy for him to raise them.

Not only beggar moths, he also had a lot of spare eagle rise Gu and other Gu.

Fang Yuan would keep his eagle rise Gu after using them for certain time and activate another eagle rise Gu.

There were six wings on his back and it looked like he was using three eagle rise Gu, but in truth, he was using more than a dozen eagle rise Gu in turns.

This was because of the heaven and earth qi.

Using Gu worms under this situation would be met with the backlash from heaven and earth qi, the Gu might even perish if they were used for too long.

Fang Yuan's immortal aperture was growing, as such he was the center of the gathering heaven and earth qi; causing the backlash force on him to be very high.

Thus, by alternating the use of Gu like eagle rise Gu, he could prolong their duration to the greatest limit.

It was again thanks to having Hu Immortal blessed land, having the capital of an immortal, that he could be so extravagant.

The backlash of heaven and earth qi was also one of the barriers for a Gu Master to advance to Gu Immortal.

When Tai Bai Yun Sheng faced the tribulations in his ascension, his Gu worms perished in large numbers. If not for Fang Yuan's support, he would already have no more Gu worms to use after using them all up in facing chaotic lightning balls outside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

If a Gu Master was lucky enough to advance to a Gu Immortal, all their mortal Gu would normally be destroyed.

Advancing to a Gu Immortal was extremely risky and there was a high price to be paid.

In lots of cases, a newly advanced Gu Immortal would have nothing on him. Almost all the Gu worms they accumulated before would be completely used up.

Six Arm Heavenly Zombie King!

Fang Yuan suddenly turned into heavenly zombie form while flying and evading; his six wings soared and he raised his eight arms.

Bam.

The next moment, he directly clashed against a formless fist!

Fang Yuan did not feel any pain and directly shattered the formless fist, obtaining a Gu.

Fang Yuan was overjoyed when he saw the Gu.

This was the third wild Immortal Gu he had obtained after exiting Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture. He was unable to examine it closely, but he stored it in his pocket after suppressing it.

Right now, he had the internal danger of Spring Autumn Cicada while on the outside, there was the formless hand disaster. He had to concentrate completely on flying, as well as pay attention to his primeval essence and the condition of his Gu worms.

But he could not deny his plentiful harvests.

Fang Yuan was deeply realizing what was called the coexistence of pain and joy.

His flying master attainment was a great help to him in this situation.

"Where is Ma Hong Yun?" Fang Yuan stored the third Immortal Gu and looked around him with insatiable greed.

Luck path supreme true inheritance had all along been of extreme interest to him.

Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had, to a large extent, relied on this to dominate the lands and become invincible in the world.

Previously, Fang Yuan had no way to do anything about this luck path true inheritance but now borrowing the strength of formless hands, he could seize the luck path Gu worms. This was an extremely rare opportunity!

However, even after searching all over whenever he had the chance, he did not see even the shadow of the luck path true inheritance.

Clearly, luck path true inheritance was also moving around.

The supreme true inheritance might be protecting Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, but it was only an acknowledgement of Fortune Rivaling Heaven; and it was still being controlled by a wild will. It was an instinct for wild Gu worms to dodge heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities.

It was a scene of chaos in the large true inheritance secluded domain; there were formless hands everywhere, true inheritance meteors, fleeing Gu Masters or dazzling attacks towards the clenched formless fists, all these were obstructing Fang Yuan's vision.

Fang Yuan also had to evade the formless hands and could not casually search. Both sides were on the move, thus it was actually normal for them to not bump into each other.

Crack, crack…

The sound of something cracking, like the cracking of egg shell, started to spread.

The cracks in true inheritance secluded domain were enlarging; it was only at one side at first, but now the cracks had gradually spread to cover all sides.

More and more giant light blue hands squeezed in through the cracks.

Time passed, the losses to Fang Yuan's Gu worms were also becoming more severe.

On the one hand, because of the backlash from heaven and earth qi, especially the movement Gu worms, even after being used in turn, they had reached the limit and many perished.

On the other hand, the quantity of formless hands had surpassed the point of qualitative change; sometimes, many formless hands would appear together and block all escape paths. Fang Yuan was thus grabbed two-three times.

But every time he was grabbed, he would intentionally choose the formless hand with the least fingers, prioritizing his safety and letting his Gu worm be taken of his own accord.

Chapter 633: Finally becoming a Gu Immortal

As time continued to pass, Fang Yuan had no more opportunities to go shatter formless fists. He was busy running from the pursuit of the formless hands.

"Return my Gu!" By some coincidence, Hei Lou Lan appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan sneered and activated wind flower Gu.

A translucent wind flower appeared beside him and quickly changed direction, taking him with it.

Whoosh!

With the wind flower Gu's help, Fang Yuan's speed remained the same when he changed his direction, and was able to avoid Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan, however, was very happy: "I am finally lucky for once! He actually ran that direction!"

Fang Yuan had not flown far away before his speed rapidly declined.

"This is..."

His expression changed as he sensed that he had fallen into a dark vortex.

This was the trap Hei Lou Lan had set using a one time expenditure Gu, specially used to trap enemies.

The formless hands were less than a hundred steps away.

Fang Yuan snorted and without losing his composure, used flash bug Gu; he disappeared from the spot and appeared five hundred steps away the next moment.

After getting out of his predicament, Fang Yuan immediately increased his speed, but not even a few breaths later, he once again fell into a dark vortex.

He again used flash bug Gu to free himself.

But following that, he fell in the third dark vortex again.

True inheritance secluded domain was originally a place filled with darkness, as such dark vortexes were extremely concealed here. Without someone running into them, they would remain still and there would be no way to sense them. But once someone ran into them, they would form a sinking force like one had stepped into a swamp or quicksand.

"You can't run away! I have placed countless traps all over the entirety of the surroundings!" Hei Lou Lan shouted while rapidly flying towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was suffering the consequences of a lack of investigation. He shouted furiously: "You are seeking your own death, don't blame me!"

He activated six arm heavenly zombie king and forcefully freed himself from the vortex, charging straight towards Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan felt a chill before it turned into joy. He was not afraid of Fang Yuan attacking him, but afraid of Fang Yuan fleeing all the time and not give him the chance to fight.

New and old hatred overlapped; both sides wanted nothing more than to kill each other.

However, they had not even fought yet, when Hei Lou Lan suddenly changed his direction and fled.

Shortly, Fang Yuan's expression also changed and retreated towards the back extremely quickly.

Too horrifying!

A large group of formless hands whooshed down from above, their numbers were at least five to six hundred!

The light blue radiance dyed the surrounding space into a scene of blue.

The formless hand group divided into two, chasing after Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan.

Fang Yuan was facing an unprecedented crisis.

He did not dare to fly in between the formless hands. There were too many formless hands, even a light movement could easily seal all his paths.

Fang Yuan could only fly forward swiftly, with the large group of giant light blue hands closely chasing him.

"No, don't come here!" Ye Lui Sang shouted in panic. He was moving with three other Gu Masters, and coordinating with each other, he was barely able to ensure the safety of his fire path Immortal Gu; however, now he suddenly saw Fang Yuan flying towards them!

And when he saw the group of formless hands behind Fang Yuan, Ye Lui Sang's heart nearly jumped out in shock.

Fang Yuan not only increased his speed, he also quickly made his move; long range attacks sealed the best escape routes of Ye Lui Sang's group and also greatly slowed down their speed.

Next, Fang Yuan turned a little and flew past them, continuing to fly swiftly.

Ye Lui Sang's group was escaping with all their strength, but it was nowhere near enough.

"No—!" This unlucky Ye Lui tribe leader let out a miserable scream as hundreds of formless hands filled his vision.

Like a burst of strong wind wreaking havoc or like locusts passing through the fields, the giant light blue hands plundered Ye Lui Sang's group and continued to chase after Fang Yuan.

Ye Lui Sang's group stood on the spot with dazed expressions. There were too many formless hands and in just a few breaths of time, all their Gu worms were seized.

In an instant, they had become completely penniless. Although they still had primeval essence remaining in their apertures, there was nothing to use them on!

"How will I report to supreme tribe elder when I return?!" Ye Lui Sang's heart was filled with fear and bewilderment.

His fire path Immortal Gu was lent to him by Ye Lui tribe's supreme tribe elder Ye Lui Lai to help him obtain victory in this Imperial Court contest.

The value of the Immortal Gu was self-evident.

Ye Lui Sang lost in the contest, but to preserve the Immortal Gu, he had to bear the disgrace of siding with Hei Lou Lan who was also a super tribe leader like him.

And now, because of Fang Yuan sending the disaster towards him, the fire path Immortal Gu he had protected with his heart and soul was gone!

Fang Yuan flew rapidly before glancing behind him; he felt relieved when he saw the formless hands had decreased in number.

This was the contribution of Ye Lui Sang's group.

Fang Yuan saw hope in getting rid of this group of formless hands.

That was to draw the disaster towards others!

He had flying master attainment while others did not.

"Eh? That is!" While fleeing, Fang Yuan finally discovered a trace of Ma Hong Yun.

The luck path supreme true inheritance was shielding Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, while dodging and flying away from many formless hands chasing it. Of course, when compared to the group chasing Fang Yuan, it paled in comparison.

Without the least bit of hesitation, Fang Yuan immediately flew towards Ma Hong Yun.

Sensing an even greater danger, the luck path true inheritance light lump instinctively changed its direction.

However, Fang Yuan chased it relentlessly and with extremely deft movements, he was able to gradually get closer.

"Let us go, I beg you, please let us go!" Ma Hong Yun's pleading came from within the luck path true inheritance.

"Don't come over, don't come over!" Zhao Lian Yun was also shivering in fear.

Fang Yuan's heart was tough like iron and cold as steel, how could he be swayed?

His speed suddenly increased violently as he made a beautiful arc beside the luck path true inheritance.

The formless hand group was immediately attracted to the aura of the luck path true inheritance and flocked to it.

"We're finished!" Both of Ma and Zhao's faces turned as they looked at the hundreds of formless hands blocking their escape routes, attacking like a storm.

"Hahaha, luck path supreme true inheritance!" Fang Yuan made a full circle, before flying back.

"My immortal aperture has almost finished forming, this is truly wonderful, I can use it to store the luck path Immortal Gu!" Fang Yuan's gaze burned looking at the formless hands shrouding the luck path true inheritance.

Whooosh whoosh whoosh...

Soon, many formless fists started flying away.

Fang Yuan immediately started using all his methods to seize the Gu.

One, two... five, six... the number soon crossed ten.

Fang Yuan knew he would not be able to catch all the luck path Gu worms, but he was satisfied at having such a harvest.

"Wait a moment, a six fingered formless fist!"

Fang Yuan suddenly discovered a major target. The six fingers signified this fist was holding a rank six luck path Immortal Gu!

Fang Yuan's eyes reddened and his breathing sped up as he used all his strength to chase the six fingered fist. He turned into six arm heavenly zombie king and directly pounced towards the fist. His eight arms burst out with fist shadows as he rained down violent punches!

The formless fist shattered and as expected, revealed a luck path Immortal Gu.

"Haha!" Fang Yuan laughed heartily as he quickly grabbed it.

However, right at this instant, a six fingered formless hand flew over and grabbed Fang Yuan! Its timing was impeccable as Fang Yuan's guard was slightly relaxed due to happiness; the result was extreme joy turning into sorrow!

Fang Yuan felt his mind go blank and cursed out; the time seemed to have stretched out extremely long at this moment.

After two breaths, the six fingered formless fist flew away from him and Fang Yuan recovered the ability to move.

Fang Yuan immediately unfolded his six wings and left the spot immediately.

He hurriedly glanced behind him and saw fifty to sixty formless hands crashing into each other at the spot where he had just been before.

If he had even the slightest hesitation...

Fang Yuan's forehead was soaked with cold sweat.

He then examined his body and the discovery caused him to turn gloomy. The Gu that was seized was not any of the Immortal Gu he had seized or Spring Autumn Cicada, it was Fixed Immortal Travel.

"This damned luck!" Fang Yuan cursed. Fixed Immortal Travel was his primary method to leave this place and return to Hu Immortal blessed land!

He must get it back!

Fang Yuan temporarily suppressed the luck path Immortal Gu and stored it in his pocket, then he stared at that six fingered formless fist and gave chase.

When one walks by the river, how could one's shoes not get wet?

Fortunately, his immortal aperture finished stabilizing during the chase.

Fang Yuan's risky attempt at advancing to Gu Immortal ended in success, at this moment he had become a true strength path Gu Immortal!

His strength path immortal aperture was very huge with about 3500km² of area. The sky was orange-yellow and there were all sorts of lofty, tall and straight mountains on the ground made of white stones with not even a blade of grass on them.

An invisible tributary of the river of time was pulled into the immortal aperture, supporting the normal operations of this small world.

In comparison to the outside world, the flow of time here was one to sixteen.

The most important point was there were twenty-two green grape immortal essence beads!

"This is a medium grade blessed land..." Fang Yuan sighed.

When a Gu Master advanced to Gu Immortal, their immortal aperture could be classified into three grades.

A small blessed land has a size of 2000km² at the maximum, can draw in a small tributary of the river of time and create over ten beads of immortal essence, while being a land of few resources.

Medium grade can have a size of 2700km² to 4000km², draw in a slightly bigger tributary of the river of time, create over twenty beads of immortal essence and have plentiful resources.

High grade blessed land can have a size of 4700km² to 6000km² , draw in a large tributary of the river of time and create over thirty beads of immortal essence. There will be plenty of heaven and earth qi remaining which can mutually interact and refine a mortal Gu into Immortal Gu during a burst of inspiration!

When Tai Bai Yun Sheng advanced to Gu Immortal, he refined two Immortal Gu; no doubt, his was a high grade blessed land.

Fang Yuan's strength path immortal aperture, however, was a medium grade blessed land.

"I might have much more human qi compared to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but he received the help of human qi Gu and his human qi was able to greatly surpass mine. I received the protection of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and Giant Sun's will; this was both an advantage and a disadvantage. Large amounts of heaven and earth qi were isolated outside and only a small part was able to seep into true inheritance secluded domain which was absorbed by me." Thoughts flashed Fang Yuan's mind like sparks.

Giant Sun's will was after all forced to help Fang Yuan resist the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity due to helplessness.

It absolutely would not kindly allow the heaven and earth qi to enter true inheritance secluded domain which could provide Fang Yuan with more potential.

"Besides this, there is also another important factor - Spring Autumn Cicada."

Spring Autumn Cicada absorbed the water of the tributary of river of time which was akin to cutting off the nourishment and greatly weakened the accomplishment of the strength path immortal aperture.

Thus, Fang Yuan's strength path immortal aperture's time flow had one to sixteen ratio which was lower than normal standard.

Chapter 634: Wind Veil of Assimilation

Fang Yuan felt no regret towards obtaining a medium grade blessed land.

This was for the best!

Within the first aperture, Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure had already reached its limits, the first aperture's walls were full of cracks. If he continued, he might cause the aperture to explode.

If it was a high grade blessed land, it could refine an Immortal Gu and create a heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity within the blessed land.

Fang Yuan's predicament was extremely dangerous, he had both internal and external threats. If his immortal aperture had a heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity wrecking havoc inside, Fang Yuan would surely become too distracted, it would be fortunate if he only suffered a great loss, but most likely he would lose his life.

"Regardless, becoming a strength path Gu Immortal means I have the ability to interfere in the battle now." Fang Yuan sighed deeply, throwing all of his Gu worms, be it mortal or Immortal Gu, into his strength path immortal aperture.

The immortal aperture had a huge space, it could easily hold Immortal Gu.

Next, Fang Yuan willed and used a bead of green grape immortal essence.

Immediately afterwards, the green grape immortal essence spread and filled the entire blessed land, turning into almost limitless primeval essence.

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh of relief, from this moment on, he no longer had to worry about primeval essence expenditure, he could use mortal Gu without any restraints anymore.

This was the biggest difference between mortal and immortal.

"At the same time, after becoming an immortal, the heaven and earth qi were all consumed, thus there would no longer be any threat of a backlash!" Fang Yuan's aura was surging, his eyes were shining with brilliance.

His body shook slightly, and another pair of eagle wings grew on his back.

Flying with eight wings, Fang Yuan's speed become faster again, chasing after Fixed Immortal Travel.

Seeing that he was about to reach his target, Tai Bai Yun Sheng called out for help behind him.

"Junior brother, assist me, that hand took away my Immortal Gu Landscape as Before!"

Fang Yuan turned around and saw a six fingered formless fist flying towards his left. Tai Bai Yun Sheng was dragging the supreme true inheritance light lump as he chased after it desperately.

Fang Yuan hesitated for a moment, this six fingered formless fist was right beside him, if he did not help, he would not be able to explain himself.

He immediately activated the wind flower Gu, barely turning around.

His speed was simply too fast, even the wind flower Gu in his immortal aperture could not take it, as many petals fell out.

Fang Yuan caught up to the six fingered formless fist and smashed at it, breaking it open and rescuing Landscape as Before.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was overjoyed upon seeing this: "Great, junior brother, if not for your help..."

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, shouting anxiously: "Senior brother, dodge!"

Too late!

An eight fingered formless hand flew over and grabbed onto Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was immobilized, his face was full of shock and fear. During this time, hundreds of formless hands flew over and encircled Tai Bai Yun Sheng!

At the same time, large numbers of formless hands were flying over from far away.

"Damn it... not only was Tai Bai Yun Sheng caught, he had the supreme true inheritance with him. This is bad, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is going to be destroyed! I have to take back Fixed Immortal Travel quickly!" Fang Yuan did not dare to save him, his eyes flashed with a cold light as he placed the landscape as before Gu into his immortal aperture and turned around to leave.

Fixed Immortal Travel Gu was the best method to escape, it was more important than any other Immortal Gu right now in Fang Yuan's heart!

Fang Yuan flew rapidly, about to reach the formless fist.

"After I take Fixed Immortal Travel, I will leave, who cares about Tai Bai Yun Sheng anymore!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance, he had made up his mind.

True inheritance secluded domain was at the deepest part of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and there were already so many formless hands here, not to mention the outside world.

He had obtained enough benefits, and he had even successfully advanced to an immortal, if he continued staying here, he might lose his life.

Fang Yuan had the intention to retreat already.

But just when he was about to succeed, Hei Lou Lan blocked his path.

"Don't think that I'll be afraid just because you became an immortal! Return my Gu worm to me now and I'll give way immediately!" Hei Lou Lan screamed.

"You are courting death!!" Fang Yuan stared furiously, he wanted to tear Hei Lou Lan into several pieces, but his logic dictated him to change directions and swerve around Hei Lou Lan, continuing his pursuit.

Hei Lou Lan snickered, he was unable to catch up to Fang Yuan, but in terms of long range methods, he had his ways to obstructing Fang Yuan in his chase.

Fang Yuan was obstructed by Hei Lou Lan time and again, he had to change his direction.

"Is this worth it? Just return my Gu to me and you'll be able to reach this formless fist. Don't forget, after the formless fist flies for a certain distance, it will vanish along with the Gu worm." Hei Lou Lan urged.

He was extremely anxious, his vital Gu was in Fang Yuan's hands, but he had to control himself and mask his anxiety.

Fang Yuan shouted out in anger, his expression still as water.

There was no way he would return the Gu worm to Hei Lou Lan.

The more Hei Lou Lan cared about this Gu, the more important this Gu was to him.

Hei Lou Lan was a huge enemy, even if he returned the Gu worm, if he did not keep his promise and continued obstructing Fang Yuan, what then?

Fang Yuan could only make detours and continue chasing after his target.

Bam!!!

Right at this moment, there was a huge sound.

True inheritance secluded domain completely broke apart, instantly exploding.

Eye piercing sunlight filled everyone's vision. At once, Fang Yuan and the others were caught off guard, their entire vision turned white.

In such a situation, who would dare to shut their eyes completely?

Even though their eyes were overflowing with tears due to the intensity, they had to open a slit.

As the white light faded slowly, from their blurred vision, everyone could see that they were floating in the air.

"Save us!" Many Gu Masters cried out desperately for help.

They were all unlucky people who had their Gu worms taken away. Without Gu worms, this rapid descent would cause them to die upon impact with the ground.

Nobody lent a hand to help them. Those Gu Masters who were barely floating in the air could only care about themselves, as they looked around in shock.

In the sky, there were thousands of formless hands, closely packed together.

On the ground, smoke was rising and there was debris of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building everywhere. These broken walls and structures were disintegrating, turning back into Gu worms.

The number of Gu worms was too many, each tile could split up into an ant's nest worth of Gu worms.

"Oh my heavens!"

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapsed!"

"Oh Longevity Heaven, why is this happening?"

Everyone was flustered and shocked, when suddenly a bright golden rainbow shot up in the sky!

"Leave behind the Immortal Gu!" The remaining Giant Sun's will had been storing energy for this moment, he finally made his move!

The golden rainbow shot out like lightning, in the blink of an eye, it destroyed one formless fist and obtained the Immortal Gu within.

Divert disaster Gu!

Giant Sun's will entered the Gu and quickly activated it.

Divert disaster Gu shot out pillars of light and shone everywhere.

The formless hands that were swept by the light pillars shrunk in size and their speed fell. Those formless hands that were hit by the light pillar disintegrated rapidly and the Gu worms within were released.

At once, Giant Sun's will regained several Immortal Gu!

"Otherworldly demon! Luck path true inheritance!!" Giant Sun's will looked at the luck path true inheritance that was trapped by the formless hands, as well as Ma and Zhao who were inside the light lump.

Without a trace of hesitation, he flew over with killing intent.

"My Fixed Immortal Travel..." Fang Yuan's heart sank to rock bottom.

He lost his target.

The formless fist that contained Fixed Immortal Travel had gone missing, it had flew away with Fixed Immortal Travel into the unknown.

Fang Yuan had completely lost Fixed Immortal Travel!

"Damn it!" Fang Yuan controlled his heartache as he forced himself to calm down.

Without Fixed Immortal Travel, he could still use the stargate to return to Hu Immortal blessed land, but this stargate needed to be sustained, so if Fang Yuan wanted to leave this place, he first needed to find a safe environment.

"Old Ancestor is here, you have no way out now. Return my Gu worm to me and I can still help you ask for mercy." Hei Lou Lan flew over, shouting.

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with cold light.

Hei Lou Lan's words reminded him, his biggest threat now were the formless hands, followed by Giant Sun's will.

Although the current Giant Sun's will was heavily damaged and was not even a tiny fraction of its original state, it was still not something Fang Yuan could take on!

The will that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind was too grand and majestic. Even though it had undergone such tremendous weakening, even though Fang Yuan was now a Gu Immortal, he was still not its match.

Most importantly, it was currently snatching Immortal Gu all over the place, once it activates the Gu, its battle strength would surge!

"Ordinary Gu worms need primeval essence or immortal essence to activate. No matter how powerful Giant Sun's will is, he is still a will and needs to use the rank nine yellow apricot immortal essence that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had left behind."

Fang Yuan's gaze was like an eagle, he looked towards Giant Sun's will who was far away.

He had just taken a look when a formless hand flew over.

Fang Yuan flapped his wings, evading successfully.

"Damn it!" Hei Lou Lan cursed ruthlessly, he had also suffered the attacks of three formless hands along the way.

True inheritance secluded domain was broken apart, the number of formless hands in the air increased by at least ten times!

These formless hands attacked, causing Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan to be dodging them with all their effort, they could not spare the energy to care about other things.

Bam bam bam...

Wind blades danced in the air, cutting apart several formless hands.

The Gu that were caught earlier were released, while Giant Sun's will was like a golden dragon, pouncing on them.

He had much of Giant Sun's immortal essence, he had the capability to instantly refine Gu worms when he got them, his battle strength surged and his aura was like a rainbow.

"Otherworldly demon! Luck path true inheritance!" Soon, Giant Sun's will found Ma and Zhao.

They were surrounded by countless formless hands, the originally large true inheritance light lump had shrunk by at least a third of its size.

Giant Sun's will howled loudly, as several Immortal Gu and hundreds of rank five mortal Gu were used together at once.

The light of divert disaster shot straight, a thousand wind blades danced in formation, a bright red fire crow spread its wings and flew while screeching...

All sorts of attacks surrounded the luck path true inheritance like the falling petals of a flower.

Once any formless hands flew out, they would be instantly destroyed, and the Gu worm within would be taken by Giant Sun's will.

"Oh no, this luck path true inheritance originally belonged to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. If Giant Sun's will obtains it, it would truly be a tiger gaining wings, or a flood dragon entering the sea!" Fang Yuan flew rapidly, taking a look at this scene, his heart turned heavy.

He looked around, but realized that to leave this place, he needed the stargate Gu.

"Imperial Court blessed land is on the brink of destruction, the outer fringe of the blessed land is already blowing with winds of assimilation, forming a huge circular wind veil. This wind has tremendous force, even if I am a Gu Immortal, I cannot resist it, I cannot force my way out!"

Chapter 635: Important Decision

Imperial Court blessed land was the number one blessed land of northern plains, it had deep foundations and tremendous fortune.

Despite this, after Fang Yuan entered it, first, there was the contest of the land spirit, Frost Jade Peacock, and Giant Sun's will.

Next, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng underwent immortal ascension and took in the heaven and earth qi of the blessed land.

Furthermore, there was the once in ten years blizzard ravaging the blessed land, and it even fused with Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Fang Yuan's tribulations to form a terrifying heavenly tribulation.

Frost Jade Peacock was able to endure it for so long, that was really quite a miracle already. Imperial Court blessed land's destruction was a foregone conclusion, now that the wind veil was formed, Imperial Court blessed land was surrounded like a sphere, and the walls of the sphere were extremely thick, at least hundreds of meters.

Even if the formless hands flew there, they would be crushed into bits, being assimilated into wind and lead to growing the strength of the winds of assimilation.

Even with flash bug Gu, Fang Yuan could not get through it.

However, this wind veil also formed an isolation barrier and prevented outside forces from intervening.

At this moment, thousands of meters above the ground, in the sky.

Three Gu Immortals looked down at the grand winds of assimilation that was like a giant dark green bowl inverted on the ground with a grim expression.

The wind veil's surface was very tranquil, but no one dared to underestimate the power of the winds of assimilation!

"Imperial Court blessed land's destruction is unavoidable! What happened inside? How did it become like this?!" One of the Gu Immortals, an elderly man, looked with a furious gaze as his brows were tightly folded.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Imperial Court blessed land, they were the arrangement of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to benefit his descendants.

As descendants with Huang Jin bloodline, they had already considered Imperial Court blessed land as their territory since long ago.

But now, the domain that held great treasures had been destroyed, these righteous path Gu Immortals of northern plains' super tribes were like dormant volcanoes turning active.

"Very evidently, this is a huge scheme. Our investigations earlier have shown that the most suspicious person is that Wolf King Chang Shan Yin. We have enough evidence to conclude that this person is an impersonator, the real Chang Shan Yin had died long ago!" Another young Gu Immortal said solemnly.

After pausing for a while, he continued: "Obviously, not just Chang Shan Yin, but other than him, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Bian Si Xuan and the others are also suspicious. This scheme is very deep, it involves the forces of central continent!! According to what we've learnt, there are at least three of the ancient sects in central continent plotting against the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building for the last hundred years!"

Central continent Gu Immortals' secret plot expended a lot of their effort and resources, to create the loopholes and setups. In the end, Fang Yuan made use of these arrangements in advance, all of their hard work had gone to the benefit of someone else.

Northern plains Gu Immortals were not to be trifled with.

Imperial Court blessed land, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, they were the spiritual symbols of northern plains, they were extremely important.

The moment something happened to Imperial Court blessed land and the happenings inside were exposed to the outside world, northern plains' forces all paid close attention to it.

Unfortunately, they were all outside, and the situation had advanced too quickly, it was already too late by the time they wanted to save Imperial Court blessed land.

"Sigh..." The leader of the Gu Immortals sighed deeply.

He was good looking with red lips and white teeth, but for some reason, he had the appearance of a child, the aura he was emitting was extremely powerful, he was subtly the leader of the three.

"The most important thing now is not to investigate these matters, but to consider the ways to salvage this situation! Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was the arrangement of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, a rank eight Immortal Gu House, it is profound and mysterious, its heavenly power is not something we can understand. Although the winds of assimilation this time are fierce, forming a wind veil, it might not be able to destroy Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. We will stay here and look for an opportunity to help, while being careful of any unexpected situations."

The child Gu Immortal's words made the elderly man and the young man Gu Immortal breathe in deeply.

"Lord Tong Zu, you are absolutely right. Our Chanyu tribe has the immortal killer move — Winged Blade, as long as we activate it together, we will be able to forcefully break the wind veil of assimilation." The young man Gu Immortal said this, unable to conceal his pride.

"The winds of assimilation is not to be underestimated, even with winged blade, we only have one chance to attack. I have made my calculations, the injury that we cause on this wind veil of assimilation would recover in only eight breaths of time." The elderly man was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he could make deductions and predictions.

The leader of the three, Chanyu Tong Zu, nodded slightly: "Right now, Hei tribe, Ye Lui tribe, Dong Fang tribe and others are surrounding the wind veil, all these righteous path super tribes have sent their Gu Immortals. There is also the number one demonic path force Snowy Mountain, they sent six Gu Immortals, attempting to take advantage of the situation. Don't underestimate them, we have our trump cards, so do they. When we use the winged blade, we have to prevent them from taking advantage of us."

　　...

"The luck path true inheritance cannot fall in the hands of the otherworldly demon, all these are mine, mine!" Giant Sun's will shouted loudly, his voice reverberated over the entire battlefield.

He turned into a golden dragon, taking form at will. Sometimes, seventeen to eighteen small dragons were created, while at the next moment, they combined into a giant dragon!

He carried Giant Sun's immortal essence, using it without holding back.

More than ten Immortal Gu were embedded on the dragon's body, there were two on its dragon horns, one in each of its eyes, and six to seven in its scales.

Blazing flames, divert disaster light beam, frost energy, all sorts of attacks were unleashed unceasingly.

At this point, Giant Sun's will could finally use his full strength.

Giant Sun's will had suppressed his anger for too long, he released all of it at this moment!

First, he had to get rid of the otherworldly demon, and because of the luck path true inheritance's importance, Giant Sun's will first surrounded Ma and Zhao.

Large numbers of formless hands covered the luck path true inheritance tightly, at times, formless fists that captured luck path Gu worms flew out.

Giant Sun's will was like a golden dragon, surrounding the luck path true inheritance and coiling around it, destroying all of the formless fists that came out.

There were many formless fists, even Giant Sun's will could only choose some and attack those, trying to free more Immortal Gu to raise his battle strength.

But near the giant will dragon, there were also large numbers of formless hands.

When Giant Sun's will snatches these Gu worms back, the formless hands would steal them again. During this contest, the two were fighting intensely and occupied the sky.

Below this battle, the remaining surviving Gu Masters were fighting with a smaller number of formless hands.

Even though Giant Sun's will attracted most of the formless hands, the Gu Masters were not having an easier time.

With the destruction of true inheritance secluded domain, the Gu Masters were completely exposed and out in the open, they were attacked by even more formless hands.

The formless hands were almost immune to all attacks, they flew in the sky and pierced through rocks, nothing could obstruct them. Only after stealing a Gu worm would they form into a fist and be susceptible to attacks.

But the speed of the formless fists was very fast, not all Gu Masters could chase after them and destroy them successfully.

Fang Yuan, Hei Lou Lan, and the others were a minority, they were geniuses among geniuses.

"Old ancestor, please help... ahh—!"

A shrill scream could suddenly be heard.

Everyone could not help but raise their heads and look.

Only to see that a Gu Master from a super tribe, one who bears a pure bloodline, was left with no other choice after being chased by the formless hands and flew into the sky to seek help from Giant Sun's will. But in the end, he was the first to be slaughtered by Giant Sun's will after he activated the Immortal Gu to attack.

"Such might..." Hei Lou Lan raised his head and looked, even with his Great Strength True Martial Physique, he did not dare to get close to Giant Sun's will.

Giant Sun's will had completely erupted, his attacks were fierce and carried tremendous might. His entire mind was on the luck path true inheritance, while competing with the formless hands, he had no energy to care about Giant Sun's bloodline descendants.

"So painful..." At this moment, Ye Lui Sang drew in a breath of cold air, crawling up from the ground.

The Gu worms on his entire body were stolen, he had fallen from the sky. Thankfully, his body was once tempered using Gu worms, thus he only suffered bone fractures while keeping his life.

Looking at this unlucky person who died, he suddenly felt extremely glad. At least, compared to this unlucky guy, he was still alive!

Being alive was more important than anything.

Fang Yuan could feel an immense mental pressure.

"Damn it..." He gritted his teeth in annoyance, he wanted to leave but had no way to break out of this predicament.

"Thankfully, Giant Sun's will did not target me at the start, but instead went after that otherworldly demon Zhao Lian Yun, while also wanting to protect the luck path true inheritance."

Fang Yuan was very clear in his heart, once Giant Sun's will gets rid of this problem, he would not let him off.

By then, he would be like a sheep standing near a tiger, or a rabbit near a python.

"Giant Sun's will alone cannot activate so many Immortal Gu. Even though I became a Gu Immortal, if we fought head on, I would still not be Giant Sun's will's match. That is unless I cut away his connection with Giant Sun's immortal essence!"

Fang Yuan's mind was very sharp.

But unfortunately, there were too many formless hands, he had to exert himself in dealing with them.

Other than Giant Sun's will, he was the one with the most Immortal Gu, their aura was attracting the attack of many formless hands.

At the same time, Hei Lou Lan's continuous attacks were also quite a problem.

He had the Great Strength True Martial Physique of the ten extreme physiques, a true child of heaven, he could be thought of as the matured version of Bai Ning Bing. Be it his battle capabilities or foundation and accumulation, they were very outstanding.

He had heaven defying battle strength, even Tai Bai Yun Sheng was not his match, the power of his self-detonation could slay an immortal!

After being obstructed once again by Hei Lou Lan, Fang Yuan's gaze towards him became more ominous.

At the same time, Fang Yuan thought to himself: "This Hei Lou Lan has an absurd number of Gu worms. He had many of his Gu worms taken away, yet he still has so many remaining!"

There was a reason for this of course.

Hei Lou Lan's sole purpose was to enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and obtain a strength path Immortal Gu, before attempting his immortal ascension in Imperial Court blessed land.

Thus, he made ample preparation, especially with his father's help, he accumulated many Gu worms.

He considered the backlash of the heaven and earth qi during his immortal ascension which would lead to the death of Gu worms, thus he prepared a lot of Gu worms, more than what anyone could imagine.

"Junior brother, save me!" After dodging for a while, Fang Yuan heard Tai Bai Yun Sheng's cry for help.

It turns out, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was trapped by the formless hands, floating in the air as he desperately defended himself.

Eventually, his Gu worms were all taken away.

After losing the support of his Gu worms, even as a Gu Immortal, he started falling towards the ground.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was his only alliance mate, he could not abandon him yet.

Fang Yuan immediately made a turn and took a risk to save him.

But who knew that during that period, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's anxious shout could be heard: "Quick, junior brother, take back my Immortal Gu Man as Before!"

Fang Yuan's heart jumped, seeing that a six fingered formless fist was flying out.

If at this moment, Fang Yuan chooses to save Tai Bai Yun Sheng, then he would lose the best opportunity to take back man as before Immortal Gu. Most likely, after he saves Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Man as Before would be transported away by formless fist.

To save Tai Bai Yun Sheng, or to take back the Immortal Gu Man as Before?

At this moment, Fang Yuan had to make an important decision.

Chapter 636: Shocking Change

To save Tai Bai Yun Sheng, or take back Man as Before?

At this instant, Fang Yuan hesitated.

Man as Before, this Gu was extremely famous even though it was a mortal Gu. Now that it had become an Immortal Gu, its ability was even greater.

According to what Tai Bai Yun Sheng had said earlier, when it was a mortal Gu, it could turn a Gu Master's condition back to a state in the past. After becoming an Immortal Gu, it could not only affect others but even himself.

This 'himself' naturally meant Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a Gu Immortal, it was not hard to deduce that the Immortal Gu Man as Before could affect Gu Immortals as well!

As a Gu worm that can heal a Gu Immortal, the value of Man as Before need not be mentioned. In fact, its value far surpassed ordinary Immortal Gu!

Thus, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was so anxious, forgetting his own predicament and reminding Fang Yuan to take back Man as Before.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng's words were merely out of anxiety, he said it without truly considering the consequences.

In the case that Fang Yuan really abandoned him and attempted to retrieve Man as Before Immortal Gu, Tai Bai Yun Sheng would be in great danger.

Even though the essence of a Gu Master's life undergoes a qualitative change when becoming a Gu Immortal, if he fell from such a high altitude, even if Tai Bai Yun Sheng survived, he would be gravely injured.

And don't forget that there were many other Gu Masters who were remaining on the ground.

"Taking back Man as Before would use up a lot of time. Even if I retrieve Man as Before, if this causes a rift between me and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, what should I do then?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted out of anxiety, once he was in grave danger and his life was at risk, he would immediately realize: Compared to the Immortal Gu, his life was more important. If at that moment, he saw his 'junior brother' chasing the Immortal Gu and giving up on saving himself, how would he think?

A person's heart is very fickle and ever changing.

Even though this sentence was said by Tai Bai Yun Sheng himself, when thinking of the circumstances and seeing things from another's shoes, he would feel doubt and suspicion.

"So be it if I still had Fixed Immortal Travel, but now that I have lost it, and the wind veil of assimilation is still contracting, isolating us from the outside world, I will need to use a stargate to leave this place and connect it to Hu Immortal blessed land!"

Fang Yuan was facing great difficulty.

To open the stargate, he would need to use starlight firefly Gu.

The formless hands were flying about and ravaging the place, they were an unstoppable force.

Once the starlight firefly Gu appeared, the formless hands would show up like flies. Even as a Gu Immortal, Fang Yuan had no confidence in protecting them from the formless hands.

"But now that the wind veil of assimilation has been formed, there is no more heaven and earth qi, even though there are a lot of formless hands, no new ones will appear. Furthermore, with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building breaking apart and dissolving into different Gu worms that are flying around..."

The formless hands had no energy source, they could not be sustained.

Fang Yuan was a veteran demonic path cultivator with five hundred years of experience, he naturally had good insight.

"Once the formless hands weaken, Giant Sun's will would become the strongest force in this battlefield. By then, after he gets rid of Ma and Zhao, retrieving the luck path true inheritance, he would come after me!"

By then, Giant Sun's will would have Giant Sun's immortal essence and many Immortal Gu, he would truly be the strongest foe.

As the weaker party, Fang Yuan had to choose to cooperate against this strong foe, to resist the enemy with numbers.

In this entire battlefield, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was the only suitable person.

Even though he was a healing Gu Immortal, he was still a Gu Immortal!

Even though his Gu worms were all stolen, Fang Yuan could lend him some.

Moreover, Hei Lou Lan and the other blood related descendants were all Giant Sun's will's natural allies. No matter how well Fang Yuan could speak, in such a short time and in such a situation, they would not switch sides.

After thinking so deeply, in reality, merely a short moment passed.

Fang Yuan moved like lightning, without hesitation, he flew towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was falling.

"Junior brother, you... sigh!" Seeing Fang Yuan make such a choice, Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had calmed down looked with shining eyes, he was touched and wanted to say something, but eventually ended up sighing.

Along the way, many formless hands were obstructing them, but Fang Yuan twisted left and right, he was agile like a bird, he quickly shortened the distance between him and Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

But right at this moment, the figure of a person suddenly appeared around Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Old fool, you have finally fallen into my hands!" The figure quickly turned solid as Hei Lou Lan grabbed Tai Bai Yun Sheng by the collar, capturing him.

Although Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a Gu Immortal, he had no Gu worms on him, it was simply too easy for Hei Lou Lan!

Hei Lou Lan quickly activated his Gu worm, sealing Tai Bai Yun Sheng's four limbs and making him faint.

Seeing the captive in his hands, Hei Lou Lan was overjoyed.

He was able to capture Tai Bai Yun Sheng under such chaotic circumstances mostly due to luck. But the result was already a success, now Hei Lou Lan's mind was full of ways to threaten Fang Yuan, to use this captive to take back his vital Gu!

But he had just raised his head and had yet to speak, before he saw Fang Yuan's body turning around and flying high up into the air.

"Hei Lou Lan captured Tai Bai Yun Sheng, it is obviously because he wants to threaten me and ask for that Gu worm!" Fang Yuan had guessed Hei Lou Lan's intention at the first moment.

His heart sank, but he was still as calm as ever.

Since Hei Lou Lan had such an objective, he would not cause harm to Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life. That means, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was safe for the time being.

In that case, the most important thing for Fang Yuan now was to retrieve the Immortal Gu Man as Before!

He dodged left and right, avoiding the formless hands' attacks. His eight wings flapped intensely as wind flower Gu and flash bug Gu were used in turns, eventually after fifteen minutes, after exerting all of his strength, with great difficulty he smashed the formless fist and took back the man as before Immortal Gu.

Because he obtained Tai Bai Yun Sheng's trust, man as before Immortal Gu did not struggle in Fang Yuan's hands.

Fang Yuan did not use his will to suppress it, he placed it into the strength path immortal aperture.

"Your senior brother's life is in my hands, quickly return my Gu worm!" At this point, Hei Lou Lan finally caught up and had the chance to issue a threat.

He was full of sweat, chasing Fang Yuan was not easy.

Especially when his movement speed was insufficient, and he still had to carry Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

He thought he understood Fang Yuan's objectives, he was very confident in himself.

Just as he said that, a formless hand flew over to him, Hei Lou Lan did not dare to resist it head on and had to dodge. This way, the imposing aura that he had tried to create was immediately weakened.

Fang Yuan's figure was like a lightning shadow, moving around the formless hands easily, when he got close to Hei Lou Lan, he was expressionless, but he was sighing over the inconvenience in his heart.

Fang Yuan knew that he could not resist Giant Sun's will alone, he needed Tai Bai Yun Sheng's help.

But now that Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a captive, Fang Yuan was quite restricted.

Although he had man as before Immortal Gu, he was not given permission by Tai Bai Yun Sheng to 'use the Gu'. If he could use it, when Hei Lou Lan kills the captive and Tai Bai Yun Sheng dies, Fang Yuan could revive Tai Bai Yun Sheng using Man as Before.

But there was a major problem here.

Using Immortal Gu Man as Before required immortal essence.

To revive a mortal, there was no issue. But to revive an immortal, the immortal essence expenditure would surely be huge.

Fang Yuan only had twenty-two beads of green grape immortal essence. He used up one in diffusing it into endless primeval essence, thus he only had twenty-one left.

This was his greatest assurance in fighting Giant Sun's will.

But to revive Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he would need to use at least ten green grape immortal essence!

Unless there was no choice, Fang Yuan did not want to do that.

Hei Lou Lan was truly a formidable character, it was no fluke that he was the person who became the victor of the Imperial Court contest. He had overwhelming talent and ability, once an opportunity appeared, he knew how to grab onto it.

"Don't tell me, I really have to return his Gu worm?"

Once that thought appeared, Fang Yuan suppressed it.

Hei Lou Lan was so anxious about that Gu, it was surely something extraordinary. Fang Yuan was not willing to return it just like that.

Most importantly, Hei Lou Lan was not trustworthy!

As time passed, Giant Sun's will and the formless hands' battle intensified.

Giant Sun's will originated from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he was very ruthless and wise, now that his original strength could be displayed fully, he showed off a matchless disposition.

He drew support from the luck path true inheritance light lump, and while fighting against the formless hands, he took back control of the one and only copy of the luck path true inheritance.

After so long, the luck path true inheritance light lump was still quite intact.

There were simply too many Gu worms inside this true inheritance, it was shocking. In just this short while, six luck path Immortal Gu were already taken by the formless hands.

No wonder it was the one and only copy.

Immortal Gu were unique, even for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he exerted all his efforts and could only elevate the true inheritance to this extent.

Three of the six Immortal Gu were retrieved by Giant Sun's will when he broke the formless fists. Giant Sun's will could only watch as the other three were taken away by the formless fists.

"Damn it! Too hateful!" Giant Sun's will got more furious as he fought, he had already hated Zhao Lian Yun to the depths of his soul, now he no longer cared about Ma Hong Yun's life.

"I want to see how long this luck path true inheritance can protect you for!" Giant Sun's will gritted his teeth.

If not for him wanting to protect the luck path true inheritance and being unable to attack all out, he would've destroyed this light lump and killed Ma and Zhao.

Ma and Zhao hugged each other, towards this situation, there was nothing they could do but to await death.

The great pressure was a huge turmoil on their hearts, their feelings for each other rapidly grew.

But this was useless.

The Frost Jade Peacock that recognised them as its master had already died.

The size of the luck path true inheritance light lump was less than a third of what it had been originally. Seeing that death was approaching closer and closer, Ma and Zhao lost any hopes of surviving.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were at a stalemate, they were bargaining. Both sides were very distrustful of each other, this talk was progressing very slowly.

Clang—!

Right at this moment, from outside the wind veil, there was the sound of a blade.

The sound of the blade was crisp and sharp, it reverberated in everyone's ears.

"What?"

"This is!"

Everyone raised their heads, they were attracted by this strange event, even the giant dragon of Giant Sun's will stopped its attacks.

Only to see that above them, on the wind veil of assimilation, there was a huge opening created by a blade.

Everyone could see the outside sky of northern plains through the opening caused by the blade.

In the sky, three Gu Immortals from Chanyu tribe were breathing roughly.

This was the immortal killer move that they activated — Winged Blade!

Around them, there were a dozen or so Gu Immortals.

It turns out that when the three of them were colluding not too long ago, other righteous path Gu Immortals approached them. Because Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were very sincere and put in a lot of effort, they came to an agreement quickly and thus chose to attack earlier than expected.

With the blade opening, the inside and outside world were connected.

This was a huge influence to anyone in the battlefield!

The ones who reacted faster than Fang Yuan and the other humans were the Gu worms!

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was an ownerless object, after being destroyed by the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, the walls collapsed and turned into large number of wild Gu worms.

At this crucial moment, using their instincts, these Gu worms flew into the air, towards the opening.

During the process, formless hands were capturing them all over the place.

"This is the best chance to charge through the wind veil and escape from this dangerous place!" The Gu Masters' eyes were glowing.

"Ah! So many Gu worms, these are all formed from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!" Northern plains Gu Immortals watched with burning and shining eyes.

Chapter 637: Huge Shocking Change

Originally, within the wind veil of assimilation, the Gu worms were lifeless.

Now, a huge opening was cut into the wind veil of assimilation, opening a link outside to northern plains, the Gu worms all went into a frenzy, frantically rushing towards the opening.

Formless hands arrived, attempting to grab them along the way.

Nearly half of the Gu worms were captured by the formless hands, and carried off by the formless fists, vanishing into thin air.

Despite this, the majority of the Gu worms managed to rush out of the opening, escaping this dangerous area surrounded by the wind veil of assimilation, and arriving in the outside world of northern plains.

"Come to me, be mine!"

"So many Gu worms, eh, that is an Immortal Gu?!"

"Stop at once! Do not fight, distribute the Gu according to our prior arrangement, no one should act recklessly!!"

The northern plains Gu Immortals saw a cluster of Gu worms, like an unceasing torrent of water rushing forth, they were already in a state of shocked ecstasy.

They struck at once, repeatedly shouting, competing against each other, and displaying all kinds of methods.

Fang Yuan raised his head to look, and saw a scene of Gu Immortals madly fighting over Gu worms.

"There are more than twenty Gu Immortals... they probably used the immortal killer move winged blade; this killer move is a first class attacking method of northern plains, during the battle of the five regions in the future, many central continent Gu Immortals died from it." His expression was grim, his eyes were flickering with cold light, the memories of his previous life was still vivid within his mind.

Winds of assimilation, the number one wind in the world, they were able to assimilate all things, there are few methods capable of restraining it.

But the immortal killer move winged blade had peerless might, it was a rare method that was even able to cleave open the wind veil of assimilation!

"Naturally, this is also because the wind veil of assimilation had not formed for a long time, the wind walls are still not too thick, given a longer period of time, even the winged blade will be unable to damage it."

Winds of assimilation, they were a wind that blew when immortal apertures faced destruction.

Once the wind gained momentum, and there was enough wind blowing, even rank eight Gu Immortals would struggle to resist it.

As for rank nine Gu Immortals, they were the rulers of the world, they were invincible beings! No matter how strong the winds of assimilation became, it could do nothing to them.

This shocking change was out of Fang Yuan's expectations, to him, this was not a method of escaping.

He had caused harm to Giant Sun's will and caused the collapse of Eight-Eight True Yang Building, he was the culprit behind Imperial Court blessed land's destruction! Once he went outside, and got caught by the angry northern plains Gu Immortals, he would end up facing a terrible fate. By then, even death would be a luxury.

He placed his attention on Hei Lou Lan now.

If Hei Lou Lan got distracted now, Fang Yuan would launch a sneak attack and take back Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

But Hei Lou Lan's eyes were fixed on Fang Yuan without a single bit of distraction.

His objective this time was to obtain a strength path Immortal Gu and become a Gu Immortal. But he was did not excel in movement and could not break the formless fists.

However, he had made an agreement with Giant Sun's will, as long as he helped him, Giant Sun's will would give him a strength path Immortal Gu as a reward.

This was also the sole reason why Hei Lou Lan had followed Giant Sun's will since the battle began.

"This fellow..." Fang Yuan had no opportunity at all, he could only grit his teeth.

Right at this moment, there was a transmission from above the wind veil, but the voice was choppy: "Hei Lou Lan... my son... father is here... to bring you back..."

Hei Lou Lan's own father, the supreme tribe elder of northern plains' super tribe, Hei tribe, a legendary figure in northern plains who was also the famous main character of the love story, Su Xian's Night Elopement — Hei Cheng!

He was rank seven and cultivated dark path, his eyes were like ink while his face was like jade, he had a handsome appearance and looked carefree.

At this moment, he was floating in the air, keeping some Gu worms while calling out Hei Lou Lan's name with much worry: "Don't worry... father... has already found the strength path Immortal Gu for you..."

But Hei Lou Lan snorted coldly when he heard his father's call.

He pretended he did not hear Hei Cheng's words, instead it triggered his anger as his expression turned into one of hatred.

Filled with the deep intent of revenge, he growled at Fang Yuan: "My patience is running out, do you still want your senior brother's life? Quickly hand over my Gu worm to me, otherwise I will kill him!"

He obviously had to save Tai Bai Yun Sheng, this was the only useful reinforcement that Fang Yuan could use to resist Giant Sun's will.

Thus, Fang Yuan shouted: "I can give the Gu to you, but you must wake my senior brother up first and let him run a thousand steps away from here!"

His suggestion was immediately denied by Hei Lou Lan: "Impossible! You have to pass the Gu to me first, otherwise I will crush his skull directly!"

Both sides did not trust each other.

Fang Yuan wanted Hei Lou Lan to release Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but Hei Lou Lan was afraid of Fang Yuan's movement speed.

Hei Lou Lan wanted Fang Yuan to return the Gu first, but Fang Yuan was afraid of Hei Lou Lan playing tricks.

Of course, there was the most common way to settle this.

That was for both parties to act at the same time, releasing Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the Gu together.

But in this environment, where formless hands were flying around everywhere, who would dare to let their Gu worms fly around?

It was not that Fang Yuan did not want to save Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but the discussion was always stuck at this stage.

Fang Yuan raised his head to look, and the scene was making his heart sink: "Oh no... the formless hands disappear after capturing Gu worms. The formless hands will continue to decrease in number, and soon, Giant Sun's will would gain control of the situation!"

Not only was Hei Lou Lan anxious, Fang Yuan was also starting to become anxious.

Giant Sun's will was a special will, exterminating the otherworldly demon was his top priority. This objective ruled above his desire to live.

The dragon made of will roared, it ignored the passage above its head as it coiled around the luck path true inheritance.

The remaining luck path Gu worms were the true inheritance's core.

Giant Sun's will did not dare to be careless.

"Are we going to die?!" Seeing the luck path true inheritance light lump reduce to a thin layer, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun felt that all hope was lost.

But right at this moment!

The true inheritance light lump burst out with a dazzling light, the light was so strong it could blind everyone's vision.

With a whoosh, the true inheritance light lump carried Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, flying up and turning into a rainbow of light, charging towards the opening in the wind veil.

The luck path true inheritance was governed by the will of a wild Gu, it had a very strong instinct for survival.

"Don't even think about it!" The dragon of Giant Sun's will shouted furiously, without hesitation, it gave chase immediately!

The true inheritance light lump was really fast, Giant Sun's will could not catch up to it.

Seeing that true inheritance light lump was about to get out of the wind veil of assimilation and escape into northern plains, Giant Sun's will finally let go of his reservations and set his mind on exterminating the otherworldly demon Zhao Lian Yun!

This was the primary objective that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had given to the special will!

When one could not get the best of both worlds, Giant Sun's will had no choice but to discard one to achieve the other objective!

Giant Sun's immortal essence was injected into all the Immortal Gu, as the dragon of will shined with a dozen spots of lights. In three breaths of time, the light expanded rapidly, ready to attack.

The will dragon's aura surged, as it readied itself, a shockingly powerful attack was about to be launched!

But, right at this moment.

From among the group of Gu worms, another true inheritance light lump appeared suddenly!

This true inheritance light lump was about the size of an adult, it was a supreme true inheritance!

This supreme true inheritance gave off a thin layer of light.

This light was not dazzling in brightness alone, but it kept changing into different colors. The light was also very dense, and it covered a huge area, forming a giant halo.

The supreme true inheritance along with the halo crashed fiercely into the dragon of Giant Sun's will.

Crack crack crack...

Under the halo's effect, Giant Sun's will rapidly expanded and exploded, leaving behind the sound of firecrackers.

The giant halo with the supreme true inheritance as its center attacked the dragon of Giant Sun's will, and attempted to cut the dragon into two at its waist.

Giant Sun's will howled, falling into extreme anger and shock.

It had broken into two, originally the dozen Immortal Gu were ready to attack, but their lethal attacks had been cancelled already.

"Rank nine wisdom Gu!" Fang Yuan's expression was unchanging, but his heart jumped.

From the appearance of this supreme true inheritance, its true identity had been exposed.

Within the true inheritance secluded domain, there were only thee supreme true inheritances.

One was Eight-Eight True Yang Building itself, it had already been broken up by the formless hands. This was also why Eight-Eight True Yang Building had collapsed completely and split back into Gu worms.

The other was the luck path true inheritance, it had once fuelled Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's glorious success. Right now, it was heading towards the opening in the wind veil of assimilation, rushing for its freedom.

The final one was the rank nine wisdom Gu, Fang Yuan had once seen it inside the true inheritance secluded domain, if not for Mo Yao's will reminding him back then, he may have nearly lost his life under wisdom Gu's influence.

Being as high as rank nine, wisdom Gu which was recorded inside \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> was definitely extraordinary.

It gave off the light of wisdom.

Basking in this light, lifeforms would lose their lifespan rapidly, thoughts would be created and destroyed in their minds quickly, they would collide with each other and create the sparks of wisdom in the process.

When a person thinks, countless thoughts would be created, destroyed, or collide into each other, to obtain the results of thinking.

Wisdom path, with this principle, became one of the paths of Gu Masters.

The light of wisdom would increase the number of thoughts to the limit, the speed of thinking would be raised to the limit, and the collisions would occur at the most rapid rate. By reducing the time to think greatly, one could attain greater effects.

This was the true effect of wisdom Gu!

"That's right, wisdom Gu also has a wild will, and had been hiding since long ago. Now that the wind veil of assimilation is broken, it is instinctively trying to escape. Except that it had remained silent until now before suddenly striking!" Fang Yuan realized at once.

Fang Yuan felt no shock towards how wisdom Gu was able to easily deal great damage to Giant Sun's will.

It has been mentioned previously — wisdom path is classified into thought, will, and emotion.

What were wills made up of?

Multiple thoughts!

Under the shining light of wisdom, these thoughts collided intensely, they expanded and faced destruction rapidly.

If the light was shone on humans, new thoughts would develop in their minds.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was dead!

This was only a will that he left behind!

This special will was just like the formless hands, without a source of energy!

Under the light of wisdom, these thoughts collided at an extremely fast face, they were rapidly destroyed but no new thoughts were generated. The dragon of Giant Sun's will was thus easily snapped into two.

It could be said that wisdom Gu directly countered Giant Sun's will!

"But this advantage is not enough to take down Giant Sun's will, unless..." Fang Yuan's gaze was sharp as an eagle, he looked up while enduring the piercing light from the inheritance.

Indeed!

He saw that in the sky, up to a hundred beads of immortal essence were falling down.

These yellow immortal essence were skull sized, each was filled to the brim and they had their auras concealed. Fang Yuan's rank six green grape immortal essence could not hold a candle to them.

These were rank nine yellow apricot immortal essence!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's immortal essence which he had left behind!

Chapter 638: Unfilial Descendants

Immortal Gu normally required immortal essence to activate. Under most circumstances, will could not activate Gu worms alone. Even Giant Sun's will was not exempt from this rule.

The reason the dragon of Giant Sun's will could activate Immortal Gu was because it was holding Giant Sun's immortal essence.

However, the wisdom Gu's attack cut apart the dragon of Giant Sun's will into two and actually revealed it was holding Giant Sun's immortal essence.

"As expected of wisdom Gu! Such an amazing result in just one move!!" Fang Yuan's gaze brightened and praised wisdom Gu inwardly.

He had also thought of cutting apart the connection between Giant Sun's immortal essence and Giant Sun's will, but he did not have enough strength to do so.

However, wisdom Gu accomplished it!

Wisdom Gu was not the slightest bit afraid of formless hands. The most terrifying formless hands only had eight fingers while wisdom Gu was a rank nine Immortal Gu and could only be grabbed by nine fingered formless hands.

However, wisdom Gu was extremely fragile despite being rank nine. It was not an offense oriented Gu and could still be destroyed.

It wanted freedom and wanted to soar to the skies, and the dragon of Giant Sun's will which possessed many Immortal Gu was its primary obstacle.

From wisdom Gu's perspective, dealing with the dragon of Giant Sun's will was of the utmost importance.

Thus, it concealed itself and waited for an opportunity to strike. It remained inconspicuous when it did not make a move, but when it made a move, it was extremely shocking, striking the weak point of the Giant Sun's will dragon and cutting its connection with Giant Sun's immortal essence in one move, thereby causing the Immortal Gu controlled by Giant Sun's will, more than ten in number, to be of no use.

Giant Sun's will let out a furious roar at the heavy damage!

However, it did not turn around to attack wisdom Gu and instead relentlessly chased after the luck path true inheritance which was holding Ma and Zhao.

Giant Sun's will instantly condensed into a huge golden hand that struck towards Ma and Zhao like a meteor.

For a moment, the whole battle situation turned into this

The wind veil of assimilation was separating the ruins of Imperial Court blessed land from the outside world of northern plains.

In the outside world were northern plains' Gu Immortals.

Inside was the ruins of Imperial Court blessed land.

There was a giant tear in the wind veil of assimilation from which countless Gu worms flew out, sparking conflicts among the Gu Immortals.

Inside the wind veil.

At the highest point was the luck path true inheritance which had turned into a rainbow and flew rapidly towards the tear in the wind veil of assimilation, it was already close to it.

In the middle was the huge hand of Giant Sun's will which could no longer activate Immortal Gu.

Below Giant Sun's will was wisdom Gu which was following closely.

Even further below in the mid-air was the deadlock between Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan.

On the ground were dozens of surviving Gu Masters. Formless hands were attracted towards the Gu worms that filled the sky, and as such the Gu Masters' situation was a lot better.

The huge hand of Giant Sun's will which had burst out with all its strength was rapidly closing the distance between it and the luck path true inheritance.

Crackle crackle crackle...

Giant Sun's will was bursting out with explosive sounds.

Wisdom Gu was not far below and Giant Sun's will had all along been under the light of wisdom; its thoughts violently collided and perished.

The huge hand of Giant Sun's will was shrinking rapidly at a visible speed.

However, the light of wisdom Gu was not just exhausting Giant Sun's will, the intense collisions of the will was further increasing the speed and power of the huge hand of Giant Sun's will.

Finally, when the luck path true inheritance was just about to charge into the wind veil, the huge hand of Giant Sun's will was able to block its path.

"None of you can escape, die!" The huge hand of Giant Sun's will grabbed down with extreme killing intent, not caring that the luck path true inheritance was a unique existence and just focused on killing Ma and Zhao.

"Are we going to die?!" Ma and Zhao hugged each other, terror and shock filled them as they looked at the giant hand falling down upon them.

Boom!

Powerful attacks rained down like a hailstorm, smashing down ruthlessly at the huge hand of Giant Sun's will.

"You unfilial descendants!!" Giant Sun's will let out a furious roar as its giant hand collapsed.

The luck path true inheritance carried Ma and Zhao, and flew through the wind veil of assimilation to the outside world of northern plains.

"These are Immortal Gu!"

"Grab the Immortal Gu!"

"They are mine, all mine!!"

How could the righteous path Gu Immortals whose hearts were filled with greed know about the identity of the giant hand of will. Even if they knew, would they just look on as the huge hand of will crushed the Immortal Gu?

A man whose heart cannot be satisfied is like a snake trying to swallow an elephant!

The luck path true inheritance was brimming with dense Immortal Gu aura which further intensified the greed of the northern plains' Gu Immortals.

"Fight!"

"Courting death, who dares to seize the Immortal Gu in front of me?!"

"You shameless bastards! Did you guys forget the agreement we made earlier?"

Verbal agreements between Gu Immortals were already fragile; who would comply with such agreements in front of huge profits?

The northern plains' Gu Immortals removed all consideration for face and grabbed at the luck path true inheritance!

The majestic auras of the Gu Immortals collided against each other.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun blacked out, almost fainting on the spot.

They had left the wolf's nest and entered the tiger's den!

"Eh? This aura and radiance, I am not wrong, this definitely is connected to luck path! Everyone move together!" Suddenly, a long and loud whooshing sound rang out.

Over ten Gu Immortals appeared.

At the lead was an old Gu Immortal with a snow-white beard that reached the toes.

The righteous path Gu Immortals narrowed their eyes at the sight of this man. Someone cried out in surprise, introducing this man's origins: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu, you actually came in person!"

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was the leader of Snowy Mountain blessed land, a rank eight Gu Immortal and the number one demonic path Gu Immortal of northern plains!

Following him were Snowy Mountain blessed land's demonic path Gu Immortals, legendary experts whose names were known far and wide.

"Imperial Court blessed land is about to be destroyed, of course I have to come and reap some benefits! Enough nonsense, strike!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu screamed out before leading the group behind him to join in the fight.

The scene turned even more chaotic.

Righteous and demonic factions battled with all sorts of Gu worms flying about. The luck path true inheritance changed hands several times; Ma and Zhao were in a precarious situation, walking on the edge of life and death.

"Don't fight, inside the wind veil of assimilation there are definitely many more Immortal Gu!" A Gu Immortal shouted in the chaos.

"The three immortals of Chanyu, make your move. The wind veil of assimilation is closing up!" Another Gu Immortal gave a reminder from within the chaotic battlefield.

The three Chanyu immortals had gathered with the Gu Immortal Tong Zu as the lead. They hurriedly glanced below when they heard the reminder.

Sure enough, the tear on the wind veil of assimilation was already closing up and there was only a thin crack remaining.

The tear that winged blade had created was extremely large, but the wind veil of assimilation's recovery speed was very fast.

Gu Immortal Tong Zu had estimated the cut would be closed in eight breaths of time. And from the looks of it, it indeed took around eight breaths.

If they used the winged blade now, they would be able to open up a tear again. However, Chanyu tribe's three immortals showed no signs of using it.

This immortal path killer move had extremely terrifying power, but the price to pay was equally large, consuming a lot of immortal essence. And in this chaotic situation, the three Chanyu immortals did not dare to use it again so as to keep it in reserve to intimidate enemies.

"Brother Hei Cheng, what are we going to do now?" Hei tribe's Gu Immortal, Hei Bai, lost his cool when he saw the wind veil of assimilation closing up, and hurriedly consulted Gu Immortal Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng was silent, his expression extremely unsightly.

Hei Bai had been seeking Immortal Gu Wooden Chicken since long ago, they had also received information from Hei Lou Lan that he had already obtained the Immortal Gu. But the wind veil of assimilation was now closed, Hei Lou Lan had not escaped when he had the chance, causing Hei Bai's plan to be fruitless.

Hei Cheng did not have the ability to cut apart the wind veil of assimilation.

His voice turned extremely gloomy: "Brother Hei Bai, you still have a chance. Those formless hands inside the wind veil are extremely likely to have seized wooden chicken Gu. When they travel through space and their energy is used up, the captured Gu worms will also be freed."

The investigative abilities of Gu Immortals were much stronger than that of Gu Masters.

After the tear was opened on the wind veil of assimilation, they had immediately glanced at the dangers within the wind veil. And because of the formless hands as well, they did not dare to enter the wind veil and risk themselves.

"It's like that?" Hei Bai's eyes brightened before he thought of something, "Then nephew Hei Lou Lan..."

Hei Cheng didn't speak, but his expression turned even more gloomy.

......

Hei Lou Lan did not grab the opportunity to escape the wind veil of assimilation, this made Fang Yuan inwardly shocked.

However, he did not have the time to ponder over this and threw it to the back of his mind.

He fixed his gaze on the falling immortal essence of Giant Sun.

His mind was filled completely with the thoughts of this immortal essence of Giant Sun.

Gu Masters cannot use the primeval essence of others. Gu Immortals were also unable to use the immortal essence of others.

After Fang Yuan obtained Hu Immortal blessed land, he had obtained a lot of green grape immortal essence left behind by Hu Immortal. But only the land spirit, Little Hu Immortal, could use this immortal essence.

Land spirits were formed from a Gu Immortal's obsession. Giant Sun's immortal essence also could only be used by Giant Sun's will. Even if Fang Yuan obtained this immortal essence, he would not be able to use them.

But this did not affect Fang Yuan's resolve to seize the immortal essence of Giant Sun even a little bit!

"I can't use it, but as long I seize all this immortal essence, the power of Giant Sun's will will drop down to twenty to thirty percent!!" Fang Yuan soared to the sky, crazily activating all sorts of movement Gu to increase his speed.

This exceptionally good opportunity was created by wisdom Gu, Fang Yuan would not be worthy of being an authoritative figure of the demonic path if he did not grab this chance.

"You dare!!" Attacked by his own descendants, and now sensing what Fang Yuan was attempting, Giant Sun's will was furious as well as anxious.

Without immortal essence, it was not able to activate Immortal Gu and could only use the power of its special will to battle.

It understood the severity of this more than anyone else!

Fang Yuan's extremely fast speed gave Giant Sun's will an unprecedented fear!

"Damn it, it's too late!" The will condensed back together into a giant hand which fell down like a meteor.

"Hahaha...." Fang Yuan threw his head back and laughed loudly, he was less than a hundred steps away from Giant Sun's immortal essence.

Even if Giant Sun's will was mighty, Fang Yuan was not worried.

Because between Fang Yuan and Giant Sun's will was the rank nine wisdom Gu!

"Wisdom Gu is the bane of Giant Sun's will, Giant Sun's will would have to detour around wisdom Gu which would waste a lot more time! Hei Lou Lan does not have high speed and he still has to hold Tai Bai Yun Sheng, so he can't chase me. The only worry is the formless hands..."

Fang Yuan thought of every possible scenario with his understanding of the whole situation.

Wind whistled past, Giant Sun's immortal essence was already within reach!

Chapter 639: Giant Sun flaunts his might, Fang Yuan receives help

Seeing that he was about to succeed, Fang Yuan's lips curled into a faint smile.

But that did not stop unexpected events from happening.

Wisdom Gu quickly descended, as the light of wisdom shrouded Fang Yuan.

Once he entered the wisdom halo, Fang Yuan's thoughts were created and destroyed intensely, he aged rapidly.

"This?!" Fang Yuan was shocked, raising his head to take a look, he saw wisdom Gu descending towards himself.

Meanwhile, Giant Sun's will which had lost a huge portion of its body shrunk into a tiny ball and followed closely after.

In reality, Giant Sun's will knew that if he took a detour around wisdom Gu, he would not be able to stop Fang Yuan. Thus, he forcefully got close to wisdom Gu and used a technique to send it flying.

Although wisdom Gu countered Giant Sun's will, Giant Sun's will was large enough and after paying a huge price, he could barely come into contact with wisdom Gu by risking his life.

This way, wisdom Gu was like a rubber ball flying straight for Fang Yuan, it became greatly troublesome for Fang Yuan now.

"As expected of Giant Sun!" Seeing wisdom Gu approaching himself, Fang Yuan could not help but praise Giant Sun's will's decision.

He laughed heartily, his heart was extremely resolute.

If you, Giant Sun, could make such a sacrifice, why can't I, Gu Yue Fang Yuan?

Thus, Fang Yuan endured the light of wisdom and used his method to sweep away all of the falling immortal essence of Giant Sun!

Immediately afterwards, he used wind flower Gu to change his direction, moving to the side and trying to get away from wisdom Gu.

Wisdom Gu continued to descend, as Fang Yuan narrowly passed by it.

"Cough cough cough..." Fang Yuan coughed non stop, he was finally out of the range of the light of wisdom. But his face no longer had the appearance of a young man, anyone who saw him would think he was a middle aged man.

The closer one was to wisdom Gu, the more intense the light of wisdom would be.

Earlier when Fang Yuan was inside the true inheritance secluded domain, he was still a great number of steps away from wisdom Gu, but in just a few breaths' time, he lost two years of his life.

Earlier, he was so close to wisdom Gu, and had endured the light of wisdom for such a long time, thus he lost more than ten years of lifespan.

Ordinary people only had a hundred years of lifespan.

In order to snatch Giant Sun's immortal essence, Fang Yuan paid a heavy price!

"Little scoundrel, die!" Drawing an arc in the air like lightning, Giant Sun's will pounced like an eagle.

Fang Yuan immediately felt an intense sensation of danger and death assaulting him, at the crucial moment, he only had time to activate six arm heavenly zombie king.

Bam!

With a loud bang, Fang Yuan was swatted like a fly.

Crashing down like a meteor, he landed heavily on the ground, forming a huge crater.

Rocks were sent flying as dust clouds formed.

Fang Yuan was lying in the deepest part of the crater, he regained his senses three breaths of time later.

Out of his eight arms, six were broken. His entire back was in a terrible state, his spine and ribcages could be seen. He was dizzy, he could barely think — the attack of Giant Sun's will earlier had not just targeted his body, but a large amount of special wills entered his mind, trying to destroy it and affect his cognitive ability!

While only barely conscious, Fang Yuan actually dodged without thinking about it.

The next moment, Giant Sun's will in the form of a huge golden axe swung down from high in the sky, cutting away Fang Yuan's left arm and left leg.

If Fang Yuan did not dodge in time, perhaps he would have been split into two by this attack.

As his consciousness recovered, Fang Yuan quickly used his sole remaining palm to support himself, his immense strength pushing his body out of the crater.

But as he was doing so, Giant Sun's will turned into a huge golden hammer, flying into the sky and slamming towards Fang Yuan.

Bam!

Fang Yuan was like a giant elephant who was hit while running, his ribcage was completely broken while his intestines were crushed to bits due to the impact.

At the same time, in his mind, he was invaded by Giant Sun's will again, as he fell into greater confusion.

Fang Yuan was like a rubber ball that was slammed on the ground, he rolled along the ground as he flew, causing a long trail to appear on the ground where he was sent flying.

The intense collision caused his clothes to be torn, and he was covered in dust.

Eventually, he sprawled on the ground weakly, motionless. His broken bones and hanging flesh were all exposed, as blood flowed, they were not red, instead, his blood had a deep green color due to six arm heavenly zombie king.

His expression was distorted, his fangs were exposed as he struggled in pain.

At this moment, there was a huge battle in Fang Yuan's mind, the battle of wills was intense, and Giant Sun's will had the upper hand.

Fang Yuan was taking a beating passively, although he resisted stubbornly, he could barely think clearly now.

Only after he exterminated the portion of Giant Sun's will in his mind could he reawaken and regain his consciousness.

But Giant Sun's will would not give him such a chance.

It condensed into a golden sword, sixteen meters long and six meters wide, it gave off an indomitable aura, and had the ability to judge all beings.

"This, this is Giant Sun's will's true battle strength? This is too terrifying..." Far away, Hei Lou Lan held the unconscious Tai Bai Yun Sheng as he said with a tongue-tied expression.

Giant Sun's will had refined many Immortal Gu, and was struck by wisdom Gu and also attacked by a group of over twenty Gu Immortals, in the end, he had to make a sacrifice and forcefully charge ahead to send wisdom Gu flying.

After all these, he had suffered great injuries, his mass was a miniscule fraction compared to the time he was slumbering.

But even so, Fang Yuan had no way of fighting back. And without using a single Immortal Gu, no wonder Hei Lou Lan watched with such nervousness, this battle strength was simply too terrifying!

But immediately after, Hei Lou Lan calmed down: "No, the special will is not this strong. But earlier, Ancestor Giant Sun struck at the perfect moment, while he was unprepared, he dealt a serious blow. The scoundrel wanted to retaliate, but he could not think as his mind was already invaded by the special will, falling into chaos. If he was prepared and had ample time to react, it would not have ended this way!"

"The main factor was because he inherited Old Ancestor's battle experience, he is ruthless and decisive, once he finds an opening, he would strike at the opponent's weakness and give him no chance of fighting back! Especially the will invading the mind, this is too scary, it is simply impossible to fight back. It seems that I need to be careful about this when fighting a wisdom path Gu Master!"

Hei Lou Lan reminded himself as he landed slowly on the ground.

He looked at the sword of will, it was floating and eventually landed above Fang Yuan, the tip of the blade was right on top of his brain.

"This guy is finished." Hei Lou Lan muttered softly; the great foe before him had landed in such a state because of a mistake that was strictly not his fault. He felt some relief, some joy, and even a slight sadness.

The strength of Giant Sun's will was due to the battle experience that it had inherited from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Although Fang Yuan had five hundred years of experience, in this aspect, Giant Sun's will was much stronger than him and had much greater experience.

Once Giant Sun's will gets a chance, he would attack consecutively and gain the upper hand, expanding on his advantage and preventing Fang Yuan from recovering any of his footing!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was not only lucky, this aspect of him displayed his invincible nature, his firm and domineering battle talent.

"It's over." Hei Lou Lan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was in his arms.

Inside the wind veil of assimilation, he was Fang Yuan's only ally, but now he was unconscious.

Hei Lou Lan threw him onto the ground casually, his gaze fixed on the sword of Giant Sun's will.

Without hesitation, the sword of Giant Sun's will shot down soundlessly, the tip of the sword pointed at Fang Yuan's brain.

Even though Fang Yuan was in six arm heavenly zombie king state, and had transformed into the body of a zombie, but once his head was pierced, Giant Sun's will would completely destroy his brain, along with his entire soul.

This was a truly fatal blow!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had fainted, Fang Yuan was unconscious, he had no way to fight back.

But just when the sword's tip was about to reach Fang Yuan's forehead, with just an inch away, a water wall suddenly appeared.

At the same time, a shrill woman's voice could be heard: "With me here, don't think of taking his life!"

"Who is this?" Hei Lou Lan gasped, he looked at the water wall with shock, the surface of the water wall had turned into a spiral, coiling around the sword tip and preventing the sword of Giant Sun's will from descending.

At the same time, a strong aura burst out from Fang Yuan's body.

Giant Sun's will pulled back the sword, retreating several hundred steps away rapidly.

He stood in the air for a moment before saying in a low voice, as he remembered: "It's you! Over ten thousand years ago, you barged into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, you were the one who freed fortune rivalling heaven Gu!!"

Mo Yao laughed delicately: "I'm surprised you remember."

Saying this, the water wall turned into a liquid armor that covered Fang Yuan's body.

A light blue glow surrounded Fang Yuan, causing his wounds to heal rapidly, his broken limbs, flesh and bones were all rapidly healing.

Giant Sun's will was able to remember because Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had recording Gu worms that filmed all that had happened inside it.

When Mo Yao explored Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, she did not wake up Giant Sun's will. But this time, after Fang Yuan woke up Giant Sun's will, he used the respective Gu worms to look through the records, learning what had happened.

Mo Yao's voice, appearance, Fang Yuan's name as well as his wicked deeds inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Giant Sun's will was very aware of all of them, that was why he was able to expose the secret of the Chang Shan Yin impersonation.

Giant Sun's will was extremely furious: "You unscrupulous and shameless thieves, you have been targeting my True Yang Building for tens of thousands of years! Die!"

Giant Sun's will attacked with rage, the golden sword flew like lightning, piercing the air and drawing a golden rainbow in the air.

The rainbow hit the liquid armor, causing ripples on it, but could not pierce the armor's protection.

Fang Yuan slowly woke up.

"This is... the rank seven Immortal Gu House Water Pavilion?" He looked at the liquid armor on him and realized.

It turns out that since an unknown time ago, Water Pavilion had been on him.

When he was in a chaotic state and his life was at risk, Mo Yao's will activated Water Pavilion and protected him.

Giant Sun's will could control Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Mo Yao's will could naturally manipulate Water Pavilion.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's yellow apricot immortal essence, how could Water Pavilion not have Fairy Mo Yao's red date immortal essence?

"Lad, you are finally awake. The immortal essence that my main body had left behind is limited, Water Pavilion's consumption is too great, quickly take over the battle, I will defend your mind!" Mo Yao's will said.

Chapter 640: Fang Yuan vs Giant Sun’s will (1/2)

"Hmph, I could escape death all thanks to you, fairy!" Fang Yuan squinted, his eyes shining with cold light.

He loosened his joints, rubbing his palms as his newly born bones creaked, his battle intent surged again!

"If you want to repay me, return Water Pavilion to Spirit Affinity House." Mo Yao's will sighed: "Quickly battle!"

"Hahaha, okay!" Fang Yuan howled, jumping up.

He had turned into six arm heavenly zombie king form, it had great physical strength. With green eyes and fangs, he looked extremely vicious and ruthless.

The water armor shrunk into a lump, before turning into a helmet, protecting his head. This way, he was no longer afraid of Giant Sun's will's mental attack.

Without any worries left, Fang Yuan took huge steps forward, raising his fists and punching at Giant Sun's will!

Swoosh.

The expected impact did not occur, instead, there was a light sound.

Giant Sun's will was very experienced, he did not fight with Fang Yuan directly. At the crucial moment, the sword turned into a golden ribbon and coiled around Fang Yuan's wrist lightly, before flying away like a flash of light.

Fang Yuan's hammer-like fist was cut apart around the wrist and fell on the ground.

Even with the defense of Fang Yuan's six arm heavenly zombie king, it could not match Giant Sun's will's sharpness.

Fang Yuan rolled away and quickly picked up his hand.

The injury on his arm was oozing with green blood slowly. Fang Yuan paid attention to Giant Sun's will while pressing the fist back onto the wound on his arm.

The flesh on the wound quickly mended and healed, even the bones started to join together.

This was the strong regenerative ability of six arm heavenly zombie king.

But why would Giant Sun's will give Fang Yuan time to recover? The will turned into a sword resembling a rainbow and charged at Fang Yuan again.

Fang Yuan squinted, he pushed with his legs as his body shot into the sky.

The sword rainbow followed closely behind him, chasing relentlessly.

Fang Yuan activated four eagle rise Gu at the same time, but the sword rainbow was faster, as their distance was pulled closer.

Fang Yuan activated wind flower Gu again.

He had already lost track of which wind flower Gu this was, all in all, he had already expended a lot of them.

Wind flower Gu allowed Fang Yuan to change directions rapidly, but the sword rainbow of will was even more agile, not only did their distance not become larger, the rainbow made use of this chance to catch up to Fang Yuan.

At once, the two sides fought intensely in the air, exchanging blows.

The sword rainbow of will drew a golden arc in the air, circling around Fang Yuan and attacking from time to time.

Fang Yuan was completely at a disadvantage, six arm heavenly zombie king's strong defense was extremely weak when matched against the sword rainbow of will.

Flesh kept falling from the sky.

These were all cut off from Fang Yuan's body by the sword rainbow of will.

Thankfully, after activating six arm heavenly zombie king, Fang Yuan lost his sense of pain. Together with Water Pavilion as a helmet, Giant Sun's will did not manage to succeed in attacking Fang Yuan's mind.

"You're not making any progress!" Seeing that Fang Yuan was not taking back the lead, in fact he was taking more of a beating and finding fewer and fewer chances to retaliate, Mo Yao's will was getting anxious.

"Easy for you to say!" Fang Yuan snorted, his gaze becoming more ruthless.

Giant Sun's will was different from ordinary enemies, he hardly had any mass and was extremely quick, even when turning. Fang Yuan's flying master attainment was nothing compared to it.

Giant Sun's will did not have a fixed form, it could turn into a sword rainbow to cut, an axe to chop, a rain of needles for a wide range attack, or even a hammer for a strong blow.

The most troublesome thing was that he could split and form at will. Suddenly, he could split into two or three sword rainbows and do a pincer attack, distracting Fang Yuan. At times, he could turn into one hammer and one sword. The hammer would strike at Fang Yuan's defense while the sword would shoot like lightning, all sorts of combinations were used flexibly, with absolutely no errors.

One could say, he fully displayed the advantages and abilities of a will in battle.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan had been reborn, and walked on the strength and enslavement paths. He was skilled at fighting head on, attacking fists with fists, or using numbers to suppress the enemy.

But meeting this kind of enemy was something he had no methods to deal with.

He was at a disadvantage, taking hits passively, that was very natural.

In the sky, Fang Yuan's green-black figure clashed with Giant Sun's will's golden rainbow, forming a large battle arena.

Great numbers of Gu worms were still flying around, their instincts were telling them to give way to Fang Yuan and Giant Sun's will, while avoiding the attacks of the formless hands.

"Even though so many Gu worms flew out, there are still countless Gu worm groups left here, I cannot begin to imagine how many Immortal Gu were used to form Eighty-Eight True Yang Building." Ye Lui Sang raised his head and sighed, the injuries on his body had mostly healed.

At the crucial moment, his status of being the leader of a super tribe worked, Ye Lui Sang obtained the help of other Gu Masters.

"There are not many formless hands left, although we have lost many Gu worms, there are so many Gu worms here, we can capture them now and regain our battle strength!" Some Gu Masters suggested.

This suggestion was quickly supported by the other Gu Masters: "We need to work together sincerely, we need to be fast! The wind veil of assimilation is getting thicker, it is spreading and the space in here will continue to shrink."

Hei Lou Lan looked at the unconscious Tai Bai Yun Sheng, walking over: "The wind veil of assimilation is not something us mortals can deal with, to escape with our lives, we need Ancestor Giant Sun's strength!"

Everyone was silent.

Above them, in the air, Fang Yuan and Giant Sun's will were engaging in fierce combat, at times, furious growls and shouting could be heard.

Be it Fang Yuan or Giant Sun's will's terrifying battle strength, everyone was scared, they subconsciously avoided those two and did not want to interfere in the battle of these two top experts.

But Hei Lou Lan's words were extremely true.

Relying on the mortal Gu that they subdue, no matter how many they have, they cannot break the wind veil of assimilation.

Hei Lou Lan asked again: "Don't worry, how can this scoundrel be Ancestor Giant Sun's match? Can't you see that ancestor is having the upper hand all along?"

Everyone's eyes were shining. The battle situation was very visible in the sky, everyone could clearly tell what was happening.

Hei Lou Lan changed the direction of the conversation: "Although ancestor has the upper hand, he cannot turn the advantage into victory. The root of the problem is that ancestor's immortal essence has been completely taken by that scoundrel, ancestor has over a dozen Immortal Gu, but he cannot use any of them."

Everyone nodded, they agreed with Hei Lou Lan's analysis.

Ye Lui Sang asked: "Then what do we do next?"

Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily, displaying Tai Bai Yun Sheng in his hands: "I have captured this old thief, he is that guy's senior brother, they share a tight bond. Our ability is limited, we can only try to help old ancestor. My suggestion is still the same, we should capture Gu worms first to increase our strength! In order to cooperate well, we should report all of the Gu worms that we have now! I will start."

Gu Masters were normally very secretive about the Gu worms that they owned.

This was important information, once it was exposed, others could use it against them and they might lose their lives.

However, this was a special circumstance where their lives were about to be lost.

Thus, everyone could only do this to increase the hopes of their survival.

Hei Lou Lan was a natural leader and had a fierce reputation, as he took the lead to expose his own Gu worms, the remaining Gu Masters followed along and Hei Lou Lan was able to recruit these people into his force once again.

Hei Lou Lan had great ambitions.

He wanted to ascend to immortal and needed a strength path Immortal Gu for it, thus he needed to rely on Giant Sun's will. These people were the pawns that he needed to fulfill his ambition.

In the sky, the battle was already at its climax.

"I've caught you!" Fang Yuan howled, pouncing down as his six arms that were tougher than steel grabbed the sword made of Giant Sun's will at lightning speed.

But Giant Sun's will instantly split apart, Fang Yuan's long awaited counterattack only destroyed a bit of his thoughts.

"Damn it!" Fang Yuan cursed, Giant Sun's will could split and gather together, it was agile beyond belief, Fang Yuan did not have methods to deal with him, thus most of the time he could only be a punching bag without any feasible counterattacks, he did not manage to make any progress.

"Sigh, if there is no other choice, we can only undergo a drawn out battle." Mo Yao's will said: "Giant Sun's will has no source of energy, during the battle, he needs to think, that will accelerate the collision of his thoughts and thus the expenditure of them."

Fang Yuan was concentrating on the fight while denying Mo Yao's suggestion: "We cannot afford to drag this on! Don't forget six arm heavenly zombie king's weakness, it can only be used for thirty minutes. Once that time passes, the backlash of the killer move would make me a zombie. If I completely turn into six arm heavenly zombie king form, the entire body would be zombified and both my apertures including my immortal aperture would lose all life force, my cultivation will be cut off from advancing further!"

Mo Yao retorted: "You underestimate yourself, don't forget that you are a strength path Gu Immortal, the essence of your life has undergone a qualitative change. Thus, the time that you can use the killer move has also been extended, it is far from thirty minutes. My rough estimate is that you have about an hour in length!"

"Even so, we cannot delay this, don't forget that the wind veil of assimilation is getting thicker, shrinking the space in here. My methods cannot counter the special will, does your Water Pavilion have any methods?" Fang Yuan asked.

Mo Yao heaved a long sigh: "Although Water Pavilion is a rank seven Immortal Gu House, it is not skilled at attacking, but rather, its ability lies in concealment and movement. Most importantly, my main body only left behind twenty or so beads of red date immortal essence. After sustaining the Immortal Gu House's operations over the years, there are only five left. If you want to use Water Pavilion to turn this around, you should dispel this thought! Watch out!!"

Mo Yao suddenly alerted, but it was too late.

Giant Sun's will feigned an attack and attracted most of Fang Yuan's attention, but it suddenly made a turn and got behind him, attacking brutally.

Fang Yuan vomited out a mouthful of green zombie blood, his eight eagle wings were smashed to bits, and his spine was completely shattered, his back was caved in and his chest was caving out of his body.

The intense force caused him to descend rapidly.

Fang Yuan quickly mobilized his Gu worm, attempting to fly into the sky.

But why would Giant Sun's will give him this chance?

It would beat the dog while it was down, the golden rainbow coiled around Fang Yuan as it attacked. Fang Yuan raised his eight arms to cover his whole body while curling up and was barely able to protect himself.

Giant Sun's will changed shape freely, slashing, cutting, slamming, piercing, all sorts of attacks caused Fang Yuan's eight arms to be destroyed, the six arm heavenly zombie king's body was tattered as there were many injuries on him from the front to back.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan had turned into six arm heavenly zombie king form, otherwise with his human body, he would have already had a tragic death.

Fighting with Giant Sun's will gave Fang Yuan great pressure, only by using six arm heavenly zombie king non-stop could he barely keep up.